ByAimee/O PicchiMoneyWatch/O February/O 4/O ,/O 2015/O ,/O 12:03/O PM/O Want/O to/O annoy/O the/O taxman/O ?/O 
Try/O this/O For/O Wichita/LOCATION Falls/LOCATION ,/O Texas/LOCATION ,/O resident/O Timothy/PERSON Andrew/PERSON Norris/PERSON ,/O a/O trip/O to/O the/O clink/O started/O with/O some/O folded/O $/O 1/O bills/O ./O 
Norris/PERSON ,/O 27/O ,/O was/O arrested/O after/O he/O tried/O to/O pay/O his/O $/O 600/O property/O tax/O bill/O with/O tightly/O folded/O $/O 1/O bills/O ./O 
While/O it/O 's/O unclear/O exactly/O what/O types/O of/O folds/O he/O used/O ,/O the/O bills/O were/O so/O tightly/O folded/O that/O the/O affidavit/O said/O it/O ``/O required/O tax/O office/O personnel/O approximately/O six/O minutes/O to/O unfold/O each/O bill/O ./O ''/O 
That/O 's/O a/O lot/O of/O man/O power/O --/O 60/O hours/O --/O simply/O to/O get/O the/O bills/O straightened/O out/O ,/O and/O the/O county/O tax/O assessor/O was/O n't/O amused/O ./O 
Norris/PERSON was/O n't/O taken/O in/O for/O his/O unusual/O method/O of/O paying/O his/O taxes/O ,/O it/O 's/O worth/O noting/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O Wichita/ORGANIZATION Falls/ORGANIZATION Times/ORGANIZATION Record/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION he/O was/O arrested/O for/O disrupting/O the/O operation/O and/O efficiency/O of/O the/O tax/O office/O after/O county/O tax/O assessor/O collector/O Tommy/PERSON Smyth/PERSON asked/O Norris/PERSON to/O leave/O ./O 
Norris/PERSON refused/O ,/O which/O led/O to/O a/O tussle/O between/O the/O two/O ./O 
Norris/PERSON ended/O up/O with/O an/O additional/O charge/O of/O resisting/O arrest/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O paper/O ./O 
For/O his/O efforts/O ,/O Norris/PERSON ended/O up/O with/O bail/O set/O at/O $/O 500/O ./O 
Smyth/PERSON did/O n't/O immediately/O return/O a/O request/O for/O comment/O ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O clear/O why/O Norris/PERSON decided/O to/O pay/O with/O tightly/O folded/O bills/O ,/O but/O it/O could/O be/O that/O he/O viewed/O it/O as/O a/O form/O of/O protest/O against/O paying/O taxes/O ./O 
Federal/O law/O lets/O people/O pay/O taxes/O in/O coins/O and/O currency/O ,/O although/O paying/O with/O quarters/O or/O pennies/O might/O not/O exactly/O enhance/O your/O popularity/O with/O tax/O officials/O ./O 
And/O other/O people/O have/O used/O physical/O currency/O to/O make/O a/O point/O about/O paying/O taxes/O ./O 
One/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION man/O ,/O Rob/PERSON Fernandes/PERSON ,/O last/O year/O paid/O his/O $/O 7,143/O in/O property/O taxes/O with/O $/O 1/O bills/O and/O coins/O ,/O hauling/O in/O a/O satchel/O of/O the/O currency/O to/O his/O local/O tax/O office/O ./O 
Fernandes/PERSON told/O the/O Philadelphia/ORGANIZATION Inquirer/ORGANIZATION that/O he/O decided/O to/O pay/O with/O $/O 1/O bills/O because/O he/O believed/O school/O taxes/O were/O ``/O stolen/O ''/O from/O him/O given/O that/O his/O family/O homeschools/O its/O children/O ./O 
``/O We/O homeschool/O our/O kids/O ,/O so/O we/O do/O n't/O even/O use/O the/O public/O school/O system/O ,/O yet/O I/O 'm/O being/O forced/O to/O pay/O all/O this/O money/O into/O a/O public/O school/O system/O that/O I/O do/O n't/O use/O ,/O do/O n't/O want/O ,/O do/O n't/O need/O ./O 
And/O I/O do/O n't/O think/O that/O 's/O really/O either/O fair/O ,/O just/O or/O even/O ethical/O ,/O ''/O Fernandes/PERSON said/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Online/O toll/O protest/O gains/O thousands/O of/O supporters/O Kathy/PERSON Sundstrom/PERSON |/O 13th/O Feb/O 2015/O 8:03/O AM/O UNDER/O FIRE/O :/O Electronic/O toll/O collection/O may/O be/O simple/O but/O many/O drivers/O are/O complaining/O it/O 's/O not/O foolproof/O ,/O and/O have/O signed/O an/O online/O protest/O against/O go/O via/O ./O 
UNDER/O FIRE/O :/O Electronic/O toll/O collection/O may/O be/O simple/O but/O many/O drivers/O are/O complaining/O it/O 's/O not/O foolproof/O ,/O and/O have/O signed/O an/O online/O protest/O against/O go/O via/O ./O 
LISA/PERSON MARTIN/PERSON AAP/O AN/O ONLINE/O petition/O to/O protest/O road/O toll/O company/O go/O via/O 's/O ``/O unexplainable/O fees/O and/O charges/O ''/O has/O gained/O thousands/O of/O supporters/O in/O days/O ,/O many/O from/O the/O Sunshine/LOCATION Coast/LOCATION ./O 
The/O Change.org/O petition/O started/O by/O the/O Gold/ORGANIZATION Coast/ORGANIZATION 's/O Ebony/PERSON Weekes/PERSON six/O days/O ago/O already/O has/O more/O than/O 18,200/O supporters/O ./O 
Ms/O Weekes/PERSON '/O story/O of/O how/O she/O racked/O up/O fines/O totalling/O more/O than/O $/O 2000/O obviously/O struck/O a/O chord/O with/O road/O users/O ./O 
She/O had/O bought/O a/O new/O car/O and/O took/O the/O transponder/O tag/O out/O of/O her/O old/O car/O and/O put/O it/O in/O the/O new/O one/O ./O 
She/O moved/O houses/O and/O went/O to/O Queensland/ORGANIZATION Transport/ORGANIZATION to/O update/O her/O address/O and/O then/O started/O receiving/O bills/O from/O go/O via/O ,/O SPER/ORGANIZATION and/O the/O government/O ./O 
``/O Each/O bill/O had/O a/O photo/O of/O my/O car/O and/O a/O bill/O of/O $/O 219/O for/O a/O $/O 1.61/O toll/O ./O 
They/O claim/O it/O was/O toll/O evasion/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
Her/O attempts/O to/O deal/O with/O go/O via/O were/O unsuccessful/O and/O has/O now/O discovered/O many/O others/O in/O the/O same/O boat/O ./O 
Mike/PERSON Smith/PERSON from/O Aroona/ORGANIZATION signed/O the/O petition/O and/O said/O it/O was/O ``/O outright/O theft/O ''/O ./O 
Maxine/PERSON Duthie/PERSON from/O Twin/O Waters/O also/O agreed/O it/O was/O ``/O disgusting/O ''/O ./O 
In/O response/O to/O questions/O from/O the/O Daily/O ,/O a/O go/O via/O spokeswoman/O said/O they/O took/O customer/O complaints/O seriously/O ./O 
``/O While/O we/O are/O aware/O of/O the/O customer/O petition/O ,/O we/O can/O not/O discuss/O an/O individual/O customer/O 's/O toll/O payment/O management/O publicly/O ./O ''/O 
She/O said/O if/O the/O toll/O invoice/O was/O not/O in/O place/O it/O escalated/O to/O the/O government/O 's/O SPER/O process/O and/O ``/O at/O this/O stage/O ,/O all/O monies/O owing/O is/O to/O the/O government/O ,/O not/O go/O via/O ''/O ./O 
``/O We/O believe/O that/O we/O have/O a/O fair/O and/O reasonable/O process/O in/O place/O to/O manage/O customer/O inquiries/O and/O complaints/O ./O 
We/O encourage/O any/O customers/O who/O believe/O they/O have/O been/O unfairly/O charged/O for/O tolls/O to/O contact/O us/O immediately/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
``/O If/O a/O customer/O is/O still/O dissatisfied/O with/O the/O outcome/O ,/O they/O can/O contact/O the/O independent/O Tolling/ORGANIZATION Customer/ORGANIZATION Ombudsman/ORGANIZATION at/O tollingombudsman.com.au/O or/O 1800/O 145/O 009/O ./O 
``/O To/O date/O the/O Ombudsman/O has/O not/O reported/O any/O adverse/O findings/O against/O go/O via/O ./O ''/O 
The/O only/O man/O who/O appears/O to/O have/O any/O success/O with/O go/O via/O and/O tolls/O is/O former/O Noosa/LOCATION councillor/O ,/O Bob/PERSON Jarvis/PERSON ./O 
Mr/O Jarvis/PERSON made/O headlines/O across/O the/O world/O last/O year/O after/O not/O having/O paid/O a/O toll/O in/O three/O years/O because/O he/O was/O claiming/O his/O constitutional/O right/O to/O pay/O in/O coins/O ./O 
It/O appears/O his/O one-man/O campaign/O has/O been/O successful/O as/O he/O said/O yesterday/O he/O had/O n't/O had/O a/O letter/O from/O go/O via/O for/O eight/O months/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O there/O should/O be/O a/O crackdown/O on/O unfair/O toll/O fines/O ?/O 
unique_identifier/O Strathearn/O Hotel/O -/O Paid/O in/O pennies/O and/O now/O left/O in/O the/O dark/O The/O Strathearn/LOCATION Hotel/LOCATION in/O Kirkcaldy/LOCATION closed/O its/O doors/O to/O the/O public/O last/O week/O ./O 
The/O Strathearn/LOCATION Hotel/LOCATION in/O Kirkcaldy/LOCATION closed/O its/O doors/O to/O the/O public/O last/O week/O ./O 
Maggie/PERSON Millar/PERSON maggie.millar@jpress.co.uk/O 09:00/O Thursday/O 28/O May/O 2015/O */O Former/O staff/O at/O a/O defunct/O Kirkcaldy/LOCATION hotel/O had/O to/O beg/O for/O wages/O -/O and/O then/O suffer/O the/O humiliation/O of/O being/O paid/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
*/O Leaseholders/O Tina/PERSON Syme/PERSON and/O Stephen/PERSON Stewart/PERSON bailed/O out/O of/O the/O Strathearn/LOCATION Hotel/LOCATION in/O Wishart/LOCATION Place/LOCATION last/O weekend/O amid/O claims/O of/O crippling/O debt/O ./O 
After/O the/O way/O they/O 've/O treated/O us/O I/O do/O n't/O feel/O sorry/O for/O them/O anymore/O Former/O Strathearn/O chef/O Shocked/O staff/O were/O given/O just/O a/O few/O hours/O '/O notice/O of/O the/O closure/O ,/O but/O head/O chef/O Michael/PERSON Cummins/PERSON told/O the/O Press/O he/O suspected/O the/O pair/O had/O been/O planning/O the/O move/O for/O weeks/O ./O 
The/O father-of-four/O ,/O who/O is/O owed/O #/O 4000/O ,/O said/O :/O ``/O I/O started/O working/O at/O the/O hotel/O in/O December/O on/O a/O salaried/O contract/O but/O it/O got/O to/O the/O stage/O where/O I/O had/O to/O ask/O for/O wages/O -/O they/O would/O pay/O #/O 70/O a/O week/O to/O my/O bank/O and/O any/O loose/O change/O available/O ./O 
The/O most/O I/O was/O ever/O paid/O in/O a/O week/O was/O #/O 100/O ./O ''/O 
Tina/PERSON Syme/PERSON and/O Stephen/PERSON Stewart/PERSON took/O over/O the/O Strathearn/LOCATION Hotel/LOCATION in/O April/O last/O year/O ,/O inheriting/O a/O team/O of/O around/O 10/O staff/O ./O 
Over/O the/O course/O of/O a/O year/O that/O number/O dwindled/O to/O just/O four/O ./O 
Sources/O say/O the/O hotel/O stopped/O paying/O wages/O properly/O last/O September/O ./O 
One/O former/O employee/O said/O a/O colleague/O who/O threatened/O to/O report/O his/O bosses/O to/O the/O Inland/O Revenue/O was/O deliberately/O paid/O #/O 250/O in/O copper/O coins/O ./O 
One/O source/O said/O :/O ``/O There/O was/O always/O an/O excuse/O ./O 
At/O Christmas/O they/O -LSB-/O Tina/PERSON and/O Stephen/PERSON -RSB-/PERSON said/O they/O had/O spent/O too/O much/O money/O on/O the/O kids/O '/O Christmas/O presents/O ./O ''/O 
``/O Staff/O threatened/O to/O strike/O ./O 
Those/O with/O children/O got/O paid/O in/O #/O 1/O and/O #/O 2/O coins/O ./O ''/O 
However/O ,/O staff/O report/O that/O they/O were/O struggling/O to/O deal/O with/O brisk/O trade/O ./O 
A/O former/O chef/O handed/O in/O her/O notice/O after/O being/O forced/O to/O work/O from/O 7.00/O a.m./O until/O 9.00/O p.m./O without/O a/O break/O for/O 17/O days/O in/O a/O row/O ./O 
She/O said/O :/O ``/O And/O then/O I/O 'd/O not/O be/O getting/O paid/O for/O it/O ./O 
``/O I/O was/O having/O to/O borrow/O money/O from/O my/O parents/O !/O 
``/O They/O would/O never/O speak/O to/O us/O ;/O just/O sit/O in/O their/O office/O all/O the/O time/O and/O eat/O their/O profits/O ./O 
``/O To/O a/O certain/O degree/O I/O felt/O sorry/O for/O them/O but/O after/O the/O way/O they/O 've/O treated/O us/O I/O do/O n't/O feel/O sorry/O for/O them/O any/O more/O ./O ''/O 
According/O to/O another/O source/O ,/O matters/O came/O to/O a/O head/O last/O weekend/O when/O the/O barman/O discovered/O no/O float/O in/O the/O tills/O and/O phoned/O Bruce/PERSON Taverns/PERSON to/O report/O a/O suspected/O moonlight/O flit/O ./O 
He/O said/O :/O ``/O The/O pair/O came/O back/O on/O the/O Sunday/O afternoon/O and/O told/O staff/O they/O were/O closing/O and/O it/O was/O goodbye/O Vienna/LOCATION ./O 
``/O A/O girl/O on/O Sunday/O paid/O a/O deposit/O for/O her/O wedding/O half/O an/O hour/O before/O they/O beetled/O off/O !/O ''/O 
*/O Customers/O ``/O gutted/O ''/O after/O showdown/O with/O bosses/O */O Hotel/O bosses/O who/O were/O last/O seen/O doing/O a/O ``/O runner/O ''/O from/O the/O Strathearn/O were/O forced/O into/O a/O showdown/O with/O angry/O customers/O ./O 
Lochore/PERSON couple/O Sabrina/PERSON Roberts/PERSON and/O Kevin/PERSON Mercer/PERSON ,/O who/O learned/O via/O Facebook/ORGANIZATION that/O their/O wedding/O had/O been/O cancelled/O ,/O said/O the/O meeting/O on/O Friday/O left/O them/O feeling/O ``/O gutted/O ''/O ./O 
Tina/PERSON Syme/PERSON and/O Stephen/PERSON Stewart/PERSON were/O in/O attendance/O but/O ,/O according/O to/O Mr/O Mercer/PERSON ,/O it/O appeared/O owners/O Bruce/PERSON Taverns/PERSON had/O forced/O them/O to/O show/O up/O ./O 
He/O said/O :/O ``/O It/O was/O obvious/O they/O did/O n't/O want/O to/O be/O there/O ./O 
``/O Tina/PERSON was/O sitting/O there/O in/O tears/O but/O you/O could/O see/O it/O was/O fake/O ./O 
``/O She/O said/O she/O had/O been/O left/O with/O nowhere/O to/O stay/O but/O she/O had/O turned/O up/O to/O the/O meeting/O in/O a/O brand/O new/O Land/O Rover/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O beyond/O a/O joke/O -/O I/O was/O so/O angry/O ./O ''/O 
Neither/O Bruce/O Taverns/O nor/O the/O leaseholders/O have/O elected/O to/O issue/O a/O statement/O to/O the/O Press/O ./O 
However/O ,/O Mr/O Mercer/PERSON said/O he/O knew/O two/O couples/O due/O to/O have/O their/O wedding/O at/O the/O Strathearn/LOCATION within/O three/O weeks/O had/O been/O given/O a/O refund/O ./O 
He/O and/O Sabrina/PERSON -/O as/O parents/O of/O six/O children/O -/O had/O struggled/O to/O save/O the/O cash/O for/O their/O October/O date/O ./O 
The/O meeting/O was/O not/O as/O favourable/O for/O them/O ./O 
``/O We/O ,/O and/O another/O couple/O who/O paid/O #/O 2000/O for/O a/O wedding/O in/O September/O ,/O have/O been/O told/O we/O might/O get/O something/O back/O next/O month/O ,/O ''/O Mr/O Mercer/PERSON explained/O ./O 
``/O But/O I/O ca/O n't/O see/O it/O -/O all/O trust/O is/O gone/O ./O ''/O 
He/O added/O :/O ``/O The/O leaseholders/O tried/O to/O blame/O Bruce/PERSON Taverns/PERSON for/O the/O hotel/O closing/O without/O notice/O ./O 
``/O But/O Bruce/PERSON Taverns/PERSON said/O the/O leaseholders/O were/O in/O so/O much/O debt/O ,/O they/O were/O left/O with/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O close/O it/O down/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O University/O student/O protests/O parking/O fines/O with/O 11,000/O pennies/O By/O Lauriel/PERSON Cleveland/PERSON ,/O CNN/ORGANIZATION Updated/O 6:57/O PM/O ET/O ,/O Fri/O July/O 10/O ,/O 2015/O Stephen/PERSON Coyle/PERSON used/O 60/O pounds/O of/O pennies/O to/O pay/O off/O his/O parking/O fines/O in/O a/O protest/O ./O 
Story/O highlights/O */O After/O receiving/O two/O parking/O fines/O ,/O a/O University/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION North/ORGANIZATION Carolina-Charlotte/ORGANIZATION student/O paid/O his/O fine/O in/O 11,000/O pennies/O */O It/O took/O three/O hours/O and/O 40/O minutes/O for/O parking/O services/O workers/O to/O count/O the/O pennies/O -LRB-/O CNN/ORGANIZATION -RRB-/O When/O Stephen/PERSON Coyle/PERSON received/O two/O parking/O tickets/O on/O the/O University/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION North/ORGANIZATION Carolina-Charlotte/ORGANIZATION 's/O campus/O ,/O he/O jokingly/O told/O parking/O officials/O that/O he/O would/O pay/O them/O back/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
It/O proved/O to/O be/O no/O joke/O ./O 
On/O July/O 2/O ,/O Coyle/PERSON filled/O three/O buckets/O with/O 60/O pounds/O of/O pennies/O and/O took/O them/O to/O the/O school/O 's/O Parking/ORGANIZATION Services/ORGANIZATION office/O to/O pay/O a/O total/O of/O $/O 110/O in/O parking/O fines/O ./O 
The/O penny/O payoff/O was/O born/O when/O Coyle/PERSON ,/O 26/O ,/O and/O a/O group/O of/O friends/O did/O research/O on/O parking/O fine/O allocations/O and/O came/O across/O the/O school/O 's/O parking/O services/O website/O ./O 
``/O According/O to/O North/LOCATION Carolina/LOCATION law/O ,/O the/O University/ORGANIZATION is/O only/O allowed/O to/O retain/O 20/O %/O of/O the/O money/O collected/O from/O parking/O citations/O ./O 
The/O remaining/O 80/O %/O must/O be/O remitted/O to/O the/O state/O to/O support/O local/O public/O schools/O -LRB-/O elementary/O ,/O middle/O and/O high/O schools/O -RRB-/O ,/O ''/O according/O to/O the/O website/O ./O 
The/O mathematics/O and/O actuarial/O science/O major/O serves/O in/O leadership/O roles/O for/O two/O campus/O organizations/O and/O was/O disappointed/O in/O this/O information/O ./O 
``/O The/O funding/O is/O n't/O there/O for/O students/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O Why/O are/O we/O investing/O in/O other/O schools/O when/O we/O 're/O in/O just/O as/O much/O need/O on/O our/O campus/O ?/O 
The/O money/O from/O the/O student/O body/O should/O go/O into/O the/O student/O body/O ./O 
I/O feel/O like/O it/O 's/O the/O community/O and/O the/O taxpayers/O jobs/O to/O put/O money/O into/O our/O local/O schools/O ./O ''/O 
Coyle/PERSON 's/O first/O parking/O ticket/O was/O on/O May/O 27/O for/O parking/O without/O a/O visible/O pass/O ./O 
It/O was/O $/O 80/O ./O 
The/O second/O offense/O came/O just/O weeks/O later/O on/O June/O 16/O :/O permit/O not/O registered/O to/O vehicle/O ./O 
That/O added/O another/O $/O 30/O ./O 
Student/O Stephen/PERSON Coyle/PERSON started/O a/O protest/O on/O his/O campus/O by/O paying/O a/O fine/O using/O 11,000/O pennies/O ./O 
Although/O he/O was/O hesitant/O to/O pay/O off/O his/O fines/O in/O pennies/O ,/O Coyle/PERSON told/O CNN/ORGANIZATION he/O realized/O it/O would/O be/O the/O only/O stunt/O that/O would/O get/O attention/O ./O 
``/O I/O called/O my/O bank/O and/O asked/O them/O if/O they/O had/O a/O sufficient/O amount/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
They/O thought/O I/O was/O joking/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O drove/O to/O several/O banks/O and/O amassed/O five/O boxes/O of/O pennies/O ,/O more/O than/O enough/O to/O cover/O the/O $/O 110/O fee/O ./O 
Off/O to/O the/O Parking/O Services/O office/O he/O went/O ./O 
``/O The/O manager/O was/O clearly/O agitated/O ,/O but/O everyone/O else/O was/O well-receiving/O ./O ''/O 
He/O said/O that/O for/O three/O hours/O and/O 40/O minutes/O ,/O he/O watched/O two/O people/O count/O 11,00/O pennies/O and/O the/O fine/O was/O paid/O off/O ./O 
Workers/O in/O the/O school/O 's/O Parking/ORGANIZATION Services/ORGANIZATION office/O declined/O to/O talk/O with/O CNN/ORGANIZATION on/O Friday/O ,/O and/O a/O call/O to/O the/O school/O 's/O public/O relations/O office/O was/O not/O immediately/O returned/O ./O 
Coyle/PERSON spent/O $/O 125/O on/O five/O boxes/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
Coyle/PERSON is/O hoping/O to/O gain/O enough/O attention/O from/O his/O university/O to/O have/O the/O state/O statute/O overturned/O so/O that/O money/O can/O go/O back/O into/O resources/O for/O the/O student/O body/O ./O 
He/O told/O CNN/ORGANIZATION that/O another/O student/O approached/O him/O to/O report/O he/O was/O in/O the/O process/O of/O going/O to/O banks/O to/O collect/O enough/O pennies/O to/O pay/O off/O a/O $/O 300/O ticket/O after/O hearing/O about/O the/O protest/O of/O where/O the/O money/O from/O fines/O is/O going/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Parking/O fine/O ca/O n't/O be/O paid/O with/O pennies/O ,/O town/O says/O ,/O but/O dimes/O are/O OK/O PennLive/O staff/O and/O wire/O reports/O By/O PennLive/PERSON staff/O and/O wire/O reports/O The/O Patriot-News/O on/O August/O 13/O ,/O 2015/O at/O 10:08/O AM/O ,/O updated/O August/O 13/O ,/O 2015/O at/O 10:19/O AM/O CHAMBERSBURG/LOCATION ,/O Pa./LOCATION --/O A/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION borough/O incorrectly/O put/O the/O brakes/O on/O a/O disgruntled/O handyman/O 's/O attempt/O at/O paying/O his/O $/O 25/O parking/O fine/O with/O 50/O rolls/O of/O pennies/O ,/O its/O manager/O says/O ./O 
Chambersburg/LOCATION rejects/O Justin/PERSON Greene/PERSON 's/O pennies/O as/O payment/O for/O a/O parking/O ticket/O ./O 
AP/Public/O Opinion/O ,/O Chambersburg/LOCATION Chambersburg/LOCATION officials/O told/O Justin/PERSON Greene/PERSON his/O passive-aggressive/O payment/O of/O 2,500/O pennies/O was/O n't/O allowed/O under/O a/O federal/O rule/O designating/O the/O copper/O coins/O as/O small/O change/O --/O not/O tender/O for/O debts/O greater/O than/O 25/O cents/O ./O 
Greene/PERSON tells/O Wednesday/O 's/O Chambersburg/ORGANIZATION Public/ORGANIZATION Opinion/ORGANIZATION he/O tried/O paying/O with/O pennies/O because/O the/O $/O 25/O ticket/O seemed/O high/O for/O the/O violation/O :/O parking/O on/O the/O wrong/O side/O of/O the/O street/O for/O 10/O minutes/O ./O 
The/O borough/O 's/O finance/O director/O says/O Greene/PERSON could/O have/O paid/O in/O quarters/O and/O dimes/O instead/O --/O just/O not/O pennies/O ./O 
However/O ,/O Borough/O Manager/O Jeffrey/PERSON Stonehill/PERSON sent/O newspapers/O a/O letter/O Wednesday/O saying/O that/O the/O finance/O director/O was/O incorrect/O and/O that/O pennies/O can/O be/O accepted/O as/O payment/O ./O 
However/O ,/O Stonehill/PERSON wrote/O ,/O ``/O I/O do/O not/O support/O this/O citizen/O 's/O protest/O ./O 
He/O is/O quoted/O in/O the/O newspaper/O admitting/O to/O illegally/O parking/O the/O wrong/O way/O on/O a/O street/O ./O 
Finally/O ,/O tormenting/O a/O borough/O cashier/O ,/O rather/O than/O pleading/O not/O guilty/O to/O the/O offense/O in/O a/O court/O of/O law/O ,/O which/O is/O his/O right/O ,/O is/O not/O an/O appropriate/O protest/O ,/O in/O my/O opinion/O ./O ''/O 
Greene/PERSON tells/O the/O newspaper/O he/O still/O has/O n't/O paid/O the/O fine/O ./O 
He/O says/O he/O 's/O still/O trying/O to/O think/O of/O another/O way/O to/O inconvenience/O the/O borough/O ./O 
//O This/O story/O has/O been/O updated/O with/O Stonehill/ORGANIZATION 's/O comments/O ./O 
//O unique_identifier/O Paying/O with/O pennies/O */O By/O William/PERSON R./PERSON Toler/PERSON */O A/O Winston-Salem/LOCATION activist/O paid/O his/O vehicle/O tax/O bill/O last/O week/O .../O in/O pennies.pennies/O 300x239/O Paying/O with/O pennies/O Clyde/PERSON Freeman/PERSON walked/O into/O the/O Forsyth/LOCATION County/LOCATION tax/O office/O with/O a/O box/O full/O of/O pennies/O ,/O clad/O in/O a/O t-shirt/O that/O read/O ``/O Taxation/O is/O Theft/O ''/O and/O a/O camera/O in-tow/O .../O manned/O by/O Cop/ORGANIZATION Block/ORGANIZATION founder/O Ademo/PERSON Freeman/PERSON ./O 
Employees/O tried/O to/O tell/O him/O he/O could/O n't/O record/O ,/O but/O he/O insisted/O on/O his/O right/O to/O record/O public/O officals/O in/O a/O public/O building/O ./O 
It/O took/O more/O than/O a/O dozen/O tax/O office/O employees/O 40/O minutes/O to/O count/O the/O $/O 117.22/O .../O that/O 's/O 11/O ,/O 722/O copper/O coins/O ./O 
Freeman/PERSON got/O the/O idea/O from/O Ian/PERSON Freeman/PERSON ,/O a/O fellow/O activist/O in/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION ,/O who/O once/O paid/O a/O property/O tax/O bill/O in/O all/O one/O dollar/O federal/O reserve/O notes/O ./O 
He/O said/O he/O considers/O property/O and/O vehicle/O taxes/O -LRB-/O as/O well/O as/O other/O taxes/O -RRB-/O as/O a/O form/O of/O extortion/O from/O the/O government/O ./O 
Freeman/PERSON is/O the/O founder/O of/O Carolinas/ORGANIZATION Cop/ORGANIZATION Block/ORGANIZATION and/O Never/O Take/O A/O Plea/O ./O 
He/O orignially/O used/O the/O surname/O Voluntaryist/PERSON to/O identify/O himself/O with/O that/O philosophy/O ./O 
``/O Also/O ,/O people/O would/O ask/O me/O what/O it/O meant/O and/O that/O was/O an/O opportunity/O to/O educate/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O recently/O adopted/O Freeman/PERSON ,/O which/O ``/O obviously/O stands/O for/O `/O free/O man/O '/O and/O is/O commonly/O used/O :/O Ian/PERSON Freeman/PERSON ,/O Ademo/LOCATION ,/O etc./O ''/O unique_identifier/O Pennies/O Not/O Accepted/O dek/O Comstock/O Select/O //O Corbis/ORGANIZATION In/O response/O to/O the/O copper/O coin/O 's/O declining/O value/O ,/O some/O stores/O have/O stopped/O accepting/O it/O as/O a/O form/O of/O payment/O ./O 
In/O 2007/O ,/O a/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION City/LOCATION man/O was/O so/O incensed/O when/O a/O Chinese/O restaurant/O refused/O to/O let/O him/O pay/O for/O his/O dinner/O with/O 10/O pennies/O -LRB-/O along/O with/O other/O cash/O -RRB-/O that/O he/O persuaded/O a/O state/O senator/O to/O draft/O a/O bill/O requiring/O pennies/O to/O be/O accepted/O everywhere/O and/O at/O all/O times/O ./O 
-LRB-/O The/O bill/O was/O not/O passed/O ./O -RRB-/O 
And/O in/O 2009/O ,/O a/O number/O of/O Concord/LOCATION ,/O Mass./LOCATION ,/O shopkeepers/O banded/O together/O to/O protest/O pennies/O --/O on/O Lincoln/PERSON 's/O 200th/O birthday/O ,/O no/O less/O ./O 
While/O federal/O law/O states/O that/O coins/O are/O legal/O tender/O ,/O it/O does/O not/O compel/O anyone/O to/O accept/O them/O ./O 
If/O a/O business/O does/O n't/O want/O to/O take/O pennies/O --/O or/O a/O $/O 100/O bill/O ,/O for/O that/O matter/O --/O it/O has/O a/O legal/O right/O to/O refuse/O them/O ./O 
So/O why/O does/O the/O government/O keep/O the/O penny/O around/O ?/O 
The/O answer/O is/O simple/O :/O sales/O tax/O ./O 
Sales/O tax/O raises/O the/O price/O of/O an/O item/O to/O an/O uneven/O amount/O ,/O requiring/O pennies/O to/O be/O given/O in/O change/O ./O 
Retailers/O need/O pennies/O to/O return/O to/O customers/O ,/O banks/O need/O pennies/O to/O give/O to/O the/O retailers/O ,/O and/O the/O Fed/ORGANIZATION needs/O pennies/O to/O give/O to/O the/O bank/O ./O 
All/O so/O you/O can/O drop/O one/O on/O the/O sidewalk/O on/O your/O way/O out/O ./O 
Read/O TIME/O 's/O 1998/O cover/O story/O on/O the/O future/O of/O money/O ./O 
</O http://www.time.com/time/covers/0,16641,19980427,00.html/O >/O unique_identifier/O A/O man/O walks/O into/O a/O bank/O .../O and/O pays/O off/O his/O mortgage/O with/O 62,000/O pennies/O Making/O it/O count/O :/O Thomas/PERSON Daigle/PERSON paid/O off/O the/O last/O installment/O of/O his/O mortgage/O with/O one/O cent/O coins/O Some/O people/O say/O they/O are/O redundant/O coins/O but/O one/O Massachusetts/LOCATION man/O proved/O that/O a/O penny/O can/O still/O go/O a/O long/O way/O -/O if/O you/O have/O enough/O of/O them/O ,/O that/O is/O ./O 
Thomas/PERSON Daigle/PERSON ,/O of/O Milford/LOCATION ,/O paid/O off/O the/O last/O installment/O of/O his/O mortgage/O with/O one/O cent/O coins/O ,/O fulfilling/O a/O promise/O he/O made/O when/O he/O bought/O the/O house/O he/O and/O his/O wife/O Sandra/PERSON bought/O in/O 1977/O ./O 
He/O phoned/O ahead/O to/O warn/O staff/O at/O Milford/ORGANIZATION Federal/ORGANIZATION Savings/ORGANIZATION and/ORGANIZATION Loan/ORGANIZATION Association/ORGANIZATION ,/O telling/O them/O he/O would/O be/O dropping/O off/O about/O 62,000/O pennies/O weighing/O 800/O pounds/O for/O his/O final/O payment/O ./O 
The/O bank/O was/O '/O 100/O per/O cent/O for/O it/O ,/O '/O he/O told/O The/O Milford/ORGANIZATION Daily/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION ,/O adding/O that/O he/O just/O wanted/O to/O make/O his/O last/O payment/O on/O April/O 24/O `/O memorable/O '/O ./O 
`/O It/O was/O something/O I/O wanted/O to/O do/O ,/O '/O he/O said/O ./O '/O 
I/O always/O follow/O through/O ./O 
I/O was/O just/O praying/O I/O did/O n't/O die/O first/O ./O '/O 
Daigle/PERSON started/O saving/O his/O pennies/O when/O he/O moved/O into/O the/O home/O ,/O gathering/O an/O average/O of/O 2.5/O per/O day/O ./O 
On/O bad-weather/O days/O he/O would/O sort/O them/O into/O rolls/O of/O 50/O and/O store/O them/O in/O steel/O military/O rocket/O launcher/O ammo/O boxes/O ./O 
Long/O time/O coming/O :/O The/O penny-payment/O full/O filled/O a/O promise/O Daigle/PERSON made/O when/O he/O bought/O the/O house/O he/O and/O his/O wife/O Sandra/PERSON bought/O in/O 1977/O The/O optician/O says/O his/O wife/O of/O 35/O years/O laughed/O whenever/O he/O would/O pick/O up/O a/O penny/O he/O found/O on/O the/O ground/O and/O say/O it/O was/O going/O to/O the/O mortgage/O ./O 
Daigle/PERSON said/O he/O is/O just/O glad/O to/O have/O the/O coins/O out/O of/O his/O house/O ./O 
He/O still/O picks/O up/O stray/O pennies/O off/O the/O street/O but/O now/O takes/O them/O to/O coin/O sorting/O machines/O instead/O ./O 
`/O I/O 'm/O too/O old/O to/O pick/O up/O those/O boxes/O of/O pennies/O ,/O '/O he/O said/O ,/O adding/O that/O he/O has/O replaced/O his/O hobby/O with/O creating/O a/O garden/O in/O the/O backyard/O ./O 
Moneybags/O :/O On/O bad-weather/O days/O Daigle/PERSON would/O sort/O the/O pennies/O into/O rolls/O of/O 50/O and/O store/O them/O in/O steel/O military/O rocket/O launcher/O ammo/O boxes/O unique_identifier/O A/O Protest/O Over/O Pennies/O Small/O Change/O Leads/O To/O A/O Big/O School/O Ruckus/O In/O this/O small/O town/O near/O Bethlehem/LOCATION ,/O a/O school/O district/O and/O one/O of/O its/O most/O popular/O teachers/O have/O come/O to/O odds/O over/O muffins/O and/O a/O few/O cents/O ./O 
The/O teacher/O ,/O Dale/PERSON Schneck/PERSON ,/O is/O off/O the/O job/O without/O pay/O ,/O and/O 36/O students/O were/O suspended/O for/O three/O days/O last/O week/O for/O protesting/O his/O fate/O ./O 
Posters/O bearing/O pennies/O line/O the/O high/O school/O halls/O ,/O and/O thousands/O of/O flyers/O supporting/O Schneck/PERSON have/O been/O handed/O out/O in/O town/O ./O 
Students/O are/O wearing/O copper-colored/O ribbons/O ,/O even/O to/O their/O prom/O ,/O held/O Friday/O night/O ./O 
The/O controversy/O resembles/O a/O broken/O roll/O of/O coins/O ,/O scattering/O to/O the/O floor/O in/O every/O direction/O ./O 
And/O for/O Schneck/PERSON ,/O 56/O ,/O who/O teaches/O journalism/O at/O Saucon/ORGANIZATION Valley/ORGANIZATION High/ORGANIZATION School/ORGANIZATION ,/O the/O coin/O has/O turned/O into/O a/O symbol/O -/O ``/O A/O penny/O for/O my/O job/O ./O ''/O 
It/O began/O when/O a/O reporter/O for/O the/O student/O newspaper/O ,/O the/O Panther/ORGANIZATION Press/ORGANIZATION ,/O told/O Schneck/PERSON that/O the/O cafeteria/O was/O cheating/O students/O out/O of/O their/O change/O for/O 99-cent/O low-fat/O TastyKake/O muffins/O -/O flavors/O ranging/O from/O blueberry/O to/O chocolate/O chip/O ./O 
When/O students/O paid/O $/O 1/O ,/O they/O would/O not/O receive/O their/O one/O cent/O back/O ./O 
Although/O the/O cafeteria/O was/O only/O selling/O about/O six/O muffins/O a/O week/O ,/O a/O penny/O here/O and/O a/O penny/O there/O added/O up/O to/O a/O bad/O policy/O ,/O Schneck/PERSON and/O students/O said/O ./O 
One/O student/O even/O paid/O pennies/O for/O a/O $/O 1.50/O lunch/O ,/O to/O protest/O ./O 
So/O ,/O one/O day/O last/O month/O ,/O Schneck/PERSON confronted/O a/O cashier/O while/O he/O was/O passing/O through/O the/O lunch/O line/O ./O 
He/O said/O he/O was/O told/O :/O ``/O We/O do/O n't/O do/O pennies/O ./O ''/O 
The/O cafeteria/O workers/O had/O developed/O the/O plan/O in/O reaction/O to/O students/O '/O tossing/O the/O coins/O on/O the/O floor/O or/O simply/O refusing/O to/O take/O them/O as/O change/O ./O 
Schneck/PERSON said/O he/O advised/O the/O cashier/O that/O it/O was/O only/O appropriate/O to/O give/O change/O ,/O no/O matter/O how/O insignificant/O ,/O back/O to/O a/O customer/O ./O 
He/O then/O thought/O the/O story/O was/O over/O ,/O until/O he/O was/O accused/O by/O the/O cashier/O of/O yelling/O at/O her/O ./O 
He/O denies/O having/O raised/O his/O voice/O ./O 
The/O allegation/O forced/O Saucon/ORGANIZATION Valley/ORGANIZATION High/ORGANIZATION School/ORGANIZATION principal/O Curtis/PERSON R./PERSON Dietrich/PERSON to/O arrange/O a/O meeting/O ./O 
Schneck/PERSON gave/O his/O terms/O ,/O which/O included/O having/O two/O student/O reporters/O present/O ./O 
Dietrich/PERSON said/O he/O refused/O to/O comply/O ,/O as/O district/O policy/O is/O to/O not/O give/O students/O information/O on/O employee/O disputes/O ./O 
In/O response/O ,/O Schneck/PERSON walked/O out/O ./O 
More/O meetings/O with/O the/O principal/O and/O Saucon/LOCATION Valley/LOCATION District/O Superintendent/O Ralph/PERSON Tarola/PERSON were/O scheduled/O ./O 
Again/O ,/O Schneck/PERSON wanted/O student/O reporters/O to/O attend/O ./O 
Since/O they/O could/O not/O ,/O he/O did/O not/O ./O 
In/O a/O memo/O sent/O on/O April/O 24/O to/O Schneck/PERSON ,/O Tarola/PERSON warned/O him/O about/O the/O consequences/O of/O refusing/O to/O attend/O a/O meeting/O scheduled/O for/O that/O day/O ./O 
If/O Schneck/PERSON skipped/O out/O ,/O he/O would/O be/O ``/O suspended/O without/O pay/O pending/O a/O hearing/O before/O the/O Saucon/LOCATION Valley/LOCATION school/O board/O ./O ''/O 
And/O that/O 's/O what/O happened/O ./O 
Schneck/PERSON was/O ordered/O not/O to/O show/O up/O for/O school/O ,/O starting/O that/O Monday/O ./O 
The/O school/O board/O has/O yet/O to/O schedule/O a/O hearing/O ,/O said/O the/O district/O solicitor/O ,/O Donald/PERSON F./O Spry/O 2d/O ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O if/O he/O yelled/O at/O anybody/O ./O 
He/O never/O gave/O me/O the/O opportunity/O to/O find/O out/O ,/O ''/O said/O Tarola/PERSON ./O 
Schneck/PERSON ,/O who/O has/O taught/O in/O the/O district/O for/O 11/O years/O ,/O disobeyed/O an/O ``/O official/O directive/O .../O ./O 
In/O the/O private/O sector/O ,/O he/O would/O have/O been/O history/O ,/O ''/O Tarola/PERSON said/O ./O 
About/O 200/O students/O protested/O with/O a/O walkout/O Monday/O morning/O ./O 
Some/O wore/O T-shirts/O with/O ``/O A/O Penny/O for/O Your/O Job/O ''/O and/O ``/O In/O Schneck/O We/O Trust/O ''/O written/O on/O them/O ./O 
One/O used/O a/O bullhorn/O to/O lead/O chants/O supporting/O Schneck/PERSON ./O 
About/O half/O went/O to/O the/O auditorium/O ,/O and/O the/O other/O half/O left/O the/O building/O ./O 
Of/O those/O who/O headed/O out/O ,/O 36/O would/O not/O come/O back/O in/O and/O were/O suspended/O ./O 
Katy/PERSON Baker/PERSON ,/O an/O 18-year-old/O senior/O and/O an/O editor/O of/O the/O Panther/ORGANIZATION Press/ORGANIZATION ,/O organized/O the/O walkout/O ./O 
She/O and/O the/O other/O suspended/O students/O spent/O their/O time/O off/O handing/O out/O 2,500/O flyers/O in/O support/O of/O Schneck/PERSON ./O 
They/O also/O are/O wearing/O the/O copper-colored/O ribbons/O -/O with/O pennies/O attached/O ./O 
``/O I/O understand/O how/O the/O school/O would/O be/O angry/O that/O Schneck/PERSON would/O not/O go/O to/O the/O meeting/O ,/O but/O I/O 'm/O really/O sick/O and/O tired/O how/O they/O give/O us/O a/O false/O feeling/O that/O we/O 're/O heard/O ,/O ''/O Baker/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O We/O want/O the/O public/O to/O know/O that/O we/O might/O be/O losing/O one/O of/O the/O finest/O teachers/O in/O the/O district/O ./O ''/O 
Administrators/O said/O they/O had/O been/O unaware/O of/O the/O cafeteria/O 's/O penny/O policy/O ,/O which/O was/O started/O by/O the/O cashiers/O in/O January/O ./O 
Dietrich/PERSON and/O Tarola/PERSON stopped/O it/O when/O the/O controversy/O began/O ./O 
The/O muffins/O ,/O their/O price/O prestamped/O ,/O are/O the/O only/O items/O on/O sale/O in/O the/O cafeteria/O for/O 99/O cents/O ./O 
Dietrich/PERSON calculated/O that/O with/O about/O six/O muffins/O sold/O each/O week/O ,/O 60/O cents/O in/O extra/O pennies/O had/O been/O collected/O by/O the/O cashiers/O since/O January/O ./O 
The/O money/O had/O stayed/O in/O the/O cafeteria/O fund/O ./O 
Now/O a/O penny/O cup/O sits/O at/O the/O two/O cafeteria/O cash/O registers/O ./O 
Dietrich/PERSON gave/O students/O who/O felt/O they/O had/O been/O unjustly/O cheated/O out/O of/O their/O change/O until/O Thursday/O to/O seek/O restitution/O ./O 
The/O students/O were/O asked/O to/O go/O to/O the/O principal/O 's/O office/O to/O explain/O that/O they/O had/O bought/O a/O muffin/O with/O a/O dollar/O and/O had/O left/O without/O receiving/O a/O penny/O in/O change/O ./O 
No/O one/O took/O Dietrich/PERSON up/O on/O his/O offer/O ./O 
Schneck/PERSON maintains/O that/O the/O controversy/O stands/O for/O student/O rights/O and/O democracy/O ./O 
School/O officials/O do/O n't/O buy/O that/O ./O 
Tarola/PERSON said/O Schneck/PERSON ``/O has/O a/O bigger/O issue/O in/O mind/O .../O to/O meet/O his/O own/O needs/O ,/O ''/O but/O said/O he/O did/O not/O know/O what/O that/O issue/O was/O ./O 
Schneck/PERSON ,/O who/O has/O hired/O an/O attorney/O ,/O acknowledges/O that/O he/O was/O considering/O retirement/O before/O this/O happened/O and/O knows/O now/O that/O it/O may/O come/O sooner/O than/O planned/O ./O 
For/O him/O ,/O the/O beleaguered/O penny/O ,/O the/O target/O of/O federal/O budget-cutters/O who/O recommend/O its/O extinction/O ,/O has/O taken/O on/O new/O meaning/O ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n't/O throw/O pennies/O away/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ,/O ``/O and/O I/O hope/O they/O never/O do/O away/O with/O the/O penny/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Activists/O Raising/O Cash/O To/O Pay/O Protesters/O '/O Fines/O --/O 5/O `/O Qapiks/O '/O At/O A/O Time/ORGANIZATION Activists/ORGANIZATION in/O Azerbaijan/LOCATION have/O launched/O a/O campaign/O aimed/O at/O collecting/O money/O to/O support/O protesters/O who/O have/O been/O fined/O hundreds/O of/O dollars/O under/O a/O new/O law/O on/O mass/O gatherings/O ./O 
The/O Baku-based/O Youth/ORGANIZATION Movement/ORGANIZATION ,/O which/O is/O behind/O the/O initiative/O ,/O plans/O to/O deliver/O the/O money/O to/O the/O authorities/O in/O the/O form/O of/O five-qapik/O coins/O -LRB-/O 100/O qapiks/O equal/O 1/O manat/O -RRB-/O ./O 
Twenty-one/O men/O were/O fined/O on/O January/O 14/O for/O participating/O in/O a/O Baku/LOCATION demonstration/O two/O days/O earlier/O to/O raise/O awareness/O about/O the/O deaths/O of/O army/O conscripts/O ./O 
They/O now/O have/O to/O pay/O fines/O ranging/O from/O $/O 380/O to/O $/O 760/O -LRB-/O 300/O to/O 600/O manats/O -RRB-/O ./O 
The/O average/O salary/O in/O Azerbaijan/LOCATION is/O about/O $/O 400/O per/O month/O ./O 
Their/O lawyer/O ,/O Esabeli/PERSON Mustafayev/PERSON ,/O told/O RFE/RL/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Azerbaijani/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION that/O his/O clients/O are/O not/O able/O to/O pay/O such/O fines/O ./O 
``/O We/O will/O appeal/O the/O court/O 's/O decision/O in/O all/O courts/O ,/O including/O the/O European/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Human/ORGANIZATION Rights/ORGANIZATION ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O These/O people/O are/O not/O able/O to/O pay/O off/O the/O fines/O ./O 
In/O order/O for/O the/O law/O to/O make/O sense/O ,/O these/O fines/O should/O be/O replaced/O by/O public/O works/O or/O administrative/O arrests/O ./O ''/O 
On/O their/O */O Facebook/O page/O ,/O activists/O from/O the/O Youth/O Movement/O are/O giving/O details/O about/O their/O campaign/O dubbed/O ``/O Fines/O in/O Five/O Qapiks/O ./O ''/O 
The/O activists/O plan/O to/O pay/O the/O fines/O --/O which/O total/O $/O 13,400/O --/O with/O five-qapik/O coins/O in/O the/O case/O that/O the/O protesters/O lose/O their/O appeal/O and/O the/O sanctions/O are/O confirmed/O ./O 
Under/O the/O slogan/O ``/O I/O am/O ready/O to/O give/O 5/O qapiks/O ;/O this/O trial/O 's/O price/O is/O 5/O qapiks/O !/O ''/O 
all/O those/O willing/O to/O contribute/O are/O invited/O to/O bring/O coins/O or/O banknotes/O to/O the/O organization/O 's/O Baku/LOCATION office/O ./O 
The/O activists/O said/O they/O had/O collected/O some/O $/O 150/O by/O the/O afternoon/O of/O January/O 15/O ./O 
*/O Death/O Of/O A/O Conscript/O */O The/O 21/O men/O were/O the/O first/O in/O Azerbaijan/LOCATION to/O be/O penalized/O under/O a/O law/O on/O mass/O gatherings/O that/O took/O effect/O on/O January/O 1/O ./O 
The/O new/O legislation/O increased/O fines/O for/O taking/O part/O in/O or/O organizing/O unsanctioned/O rallies/O up/O to/O 30-fold/O ,/O with/O a/O maximum/O penalty/O of/O $/O 3,800/O ./O 
The/O 21/O were/O among/O hundreds/O of/O people/O who/O demonstrated/O on/O Fountains/LOCATION Square/LOCATION in/O the/O center/O of/O Baku/LOCATION on/O January/O 12/O ./O 
The/O crowd/O called/O for/O the/O resignation/O of/O Defense/O Minister/O Safar/PERSON Abiyev/PERSON over/O what/O they/O say/O is/O a/O widespread/O problem/O of/O hazing/O and/O bullying/O within/O the/O country/O 's/O armed/O forces/O ./O 
The/O demonstration/O was/O organized/O online/O by/O Youth/ORGANIZATION Movement/ORGANIZATION members/O and/O other/O activists/O after/O the/O */O sudden/O death/O last/O week/O of/O conscript/O Ceyhun/O Qubadov/O ./O 
The/O army/O initially/O said/O Qubadov/PERSON died/O of/O a/O heart/O attack/O ,/O but/O authorities/O later/O launched/O an/O investigation/O after/O his/O relatives/O published/O photos/O of/O his/O body/O that/O appeared/O to/O show/O evidence/O of/O violence/O ./O 
Activists/O have/O also/O been/O collecting/O signatures/O for/O an/O online/O petition/O addressed/O to/O President/O Ilham/PERSON Aliyev/PERSON ,/O urging/O him/O to/O address/O the/O situation/O faced/O by/O army/O conscripts/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O Pays/O $/O 21,000/O Settlement/O To/O Andres/ORGANIZATION Carrasco/ORGANIZATION In/ORGANIZATION Coins/ORGANIZATION Adriana/ORGANIZATION s/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION ,/O a/O Southern/LOCATION California/LOCATION insurance/O company/O ,/O has/O settled/O a/O lawsuit/O ,/O paying/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 76/O ,/O $/O 21,000/O in/O loose/O coins/O ./O 
Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O Settles/O Lawsuit/O $/O 21,000/O In/O Coins/O Carrasco/PERSON filed/O a/O lawsuit/O against/O Adriana/PERSON s/O Insurance/O in/O 2012/O claiming/O he/O was/O physically/O assaulted/O by/O an/O employee/O ./O 
After/O reaching/O a/O settlement/O in/O June/O ,/O a/O team/O of/O lawyers/O from/O Adriana/ORGANIZATION s/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION reportedly/O dropped/O off/O 16/O buckets/O full/O of/O coins/O to/O Carrasco/PERSON s/O lawyer/O ,/O Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON </O //O name/nm0303004/O //O >/O ./O 
The/O buckets/O were/O full/O of/O quarters/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O pennies/O ,/O and/O Gallo/PERSON estimates/O it/O will/O take/O him/O and/O his/O team/O a/O week/O to/O count/O ./O 
In/O an/O interview/O with/O CBS/ORGANIZATION local/O news/O ,/O Carrasco/PERSON ,/O who/O is/O reportedly/O recovering/O from/O a/O hernia/O operation/O ,/O appears/O at/O a/O complete/O loss/O ,/O saying/O simply/O ,/O It/O s/O too/O heavy/O ./O 
Adriana/PERSON s/O Insurance/O ,/O is/O this/O the/O way/O you/O treat/O everyone/O ?/O 
Why/O don/O t/O you/O like/O your/O clients/O ?/O 
I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON s/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O Pays/O Out/O $/O 21,000/O Settlement/O In/O Coins/O --/O To/O A/O Guy/O Who/O Ca/O n't/O Lift/O Them/O Everyone/O knows/O what/O it/O 's/O like/O for/O an/O insurance/O company/O to/O get/O under/O your/O skin/O ./O 
But/O 73-year-old/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON now/O has/O a/O story/O that/O beats/O them/O all/O :/O After/O agreeing/O to/O a/O settlement/O after/O an/O employee/O allegedly/O physically/O assaulted/O him/O ,/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O paid/O Carrasco/PERSON over/O $/O 20,000/O in/O coins/O ,/O in/O seemingly/O an/O effort/O to/O be/O as/O difficult/O as/O possible/O ./O 
It/O is/O n't/O sitting/O well/O with/O him/O ,/O or/O ,/O for/O that/O matter/O ,/O basically/O anybody/O who/O hears/O about/O the/O story/O --/O I/O mean/O ,/O //O really/O //O ?/O 
Buckets/O and/O buckets/O full/O of/O change/O ?/O 
Carrasco/PERSON filed/O his/O lawsuit/O against/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O back/O in/O 2012/O ./O 
While/O details/O of/O the/O suit/O have/O n't/O been/O widely/O reported/O ,/O and/O likely/O wo/O n't/O be/O known/O due/O to/O the/O settlement/O ,/O this/O much/O seems/O clear/O :/O The/O folks/O at/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O were/O n't/O happy/O about/O it/O ./O 
This/O is/O laid/O especially/O bare/O by/O the/O fact/O that/O they/O did/O n't/O cash/O out/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O entire/O settlement/O in/O coin/O form/O --/O they/O actually/O gave/O him/O a/O check/O at/O the/O same/O time/O ,/O presumably/O making/O up/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O money/O ./O 
The/O $/O 21,000/O sum/O in/O coins/O would/O seem/O ,/O therefore/O ,/O to/O have/O been/O a/O deliberate/O decision/O --/O is/O it/O //O that/O //O hard/O to/O write/O a/O new/O check/O for/O the/O full/O amount/O ?/O 
According/O to/O NBC/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION ,/O this/O harms/O Carrasco/PERSON to/O a/O considerable/O extent/O ./O 
The/O coins/O were/O reportedly/O delivered/O to/O his/O attorney/O 's/O office/O by/O eight/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O employees/O ,/O which/O makes/O sense/O --/O $/O 21,000/O in/O loose/O change/O has/O to/O be/O quite/O a/O heavy/O lift/O ./O 
So/O heavy/O ,/O in/O fact/O ,/O that/O Carrasco/PERSON ca/O n't/O even/O lift/O them/O ,/O having/O recently/O been/O treated/O for/O a/O hernia/O ,/O and/O being/O of/O an/O advanced/O age/O ,/O and/O it/O does/O n't/O even/O make/O sense/O why/O he/O has/O to/O deal/O with/O all/O this/O ,/O //O what/O the/O hell/O ?/O 
//O If/O it/O 's/O becoming/O obvious/O how/O much/O this/O distresses/O me/O ,/O rest/O assured/O ,/O it/O 's/O nothing/O compared/O to/O how/O Carrasco/PERSON must/O be/O feeling/O ./O 
In/O a/O statement/O from/O Tuesday/O ,/O he/O had/O the/O following/O to/O say/O :/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O ,/O is/O this/O the/O way/O you/O treat/O everyone/O ?/O 
Why/O do/O n't/O you/O like/O your/O clients/O ?/O 
I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ./O 
We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ./O 
The/O public/O relations/O nightmare/O for/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O ,/O which/O anyone/O with/O a/O scrap/O of/O common/O sense/O could/O 've/O seen/O coming/O ,/O is/O now/O underway/O ./O 
As/O the/O //O Atlanta/LOCATION Journal-Constitution/O //O observed/O ,/O their/O Yelp/O page/O has/O been/O inundated/O with/O negative/O reviews/O citing/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O story/O ,/O including/O one/O claiming/O to/O be/O from/O his/O nephew/O ./O 
With/O this/O story/O sweeping/O through/O social/O media/O ,/O it/O feels/O like/O a/O foregone/O conclusion/O that/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O will/O have/O to/O apologize/O for/O this/O ,/O or/O at/O least/O address/O the/O situation/O publicly/O ./O 
So/O far/O ,/O though/O ,/O they/O 've/O done/O neither/O ./O 
Maybe/O it/O 's/O time/O to/O get/O some/O damage/O control/O experts/O on/O staff/O ?/O 
unique_identifier/O Adding/O insult/O to/O injury/O :/O Insurance/O company/O delivered/O a/O $/O 21,000/O settlement/O to/O elderly/O man/O who/O claimed/O he/O was/O assaulted/O by/O one/O of/O the/O company/O 's/O employees/O in/O BUCKETS/O of/O loose/O change/O */O Adriana/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION ,/ORGANIZATION Inc./ORGANIZATION gave/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 73/O ,/O over/O $/O 21,000/O in/O coins/O as/O part/O of/O a/O settlement/O */O An/O employee/O assaulted/O Carrasco/PERSON ,/O the/O elderly/O man/O claimed/O in/O a/O 2012/O lawsuit/O */O Carrasco/PERSON is/O not/O strong/O enough/O to/O lift/O the/O buckets/O and/O was/O treated/O for/O a/O hernia/O ,/O his/O lawyer/O said/O */O Since/O the/O story/O broke/O ,/O Yelp/O users/O have/O flooded/O the/O insurance/O company/O 's/O page/O with/O one-star/O reviews/O A/O California/LOCATION insurance/O company/O paid/O a/O senior/O citizen/O in/O coins/O as/O part/O of/O a/O settlement/O ./O 
Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION ,/ORGANIZATION Inc./ORGANIZATION gave/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 73/O ,/O over/O $/O 21,000/O in/O coins/O along/O with/O a/O check/O ,/O NBC/ORGANIZATION Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION reported/O ./O 
An/O employee/O assaulted/O Carrasco/PERSON ,/O the/O elderly/O man/O claimed/O in/O a/O 2012/O lawsuit/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O station/O ./O 
Victim/O :/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 73/O ,/O was/O paid/O over/O $/O 21,000/O in/O coins/O by/O an/O insurance/O company/O in/O a/O settlement/O deal/O `/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O ,/O is/O this/O the/O way/O you/O treat/O everyone/O ?/O '/O 
He/O said/O in/O statement/O to/O the/O station/O ./O 
`/O Why/O do/O n't/O you/O like/O your/O clients/O ?/O '/O 
Carrasco/PERSON also/O said/O '/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ./O 
We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ./O '/O 
Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON ,/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O ,/O told/O NBC/ORGANIZATION Los/ORGANIZATION Angeles/ORGANIZATION that/O company/O employees/O left/O `/O five-gallon/O containers/O '/O at/O his/O office/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON told/O the/O affiliate/O station/O his/O client/O is/O not/O strong/O enough/O to/O lift/O the/O containers/O ./O 
Carrasco/PERSON was/O recently/O treated/O for/O a/O hernia/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
As/O noted/O by/O The/O Atlanta/O Journal-Constitution/O ,/O since/O the/O story/O broke/O online/O users/O have/O flooded/O the/O company/O 's/O Yelp/O page/O with/O one-star/O reviews/O ./O 
A/O request/O for/O comment/O to/O the/O insurance/O company/O from/O MailOnline/ORGANIZATION was/O not/O immediately/O answered/O ./O 
Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O bizarre/O television/O advert/O -/O `/O Gigante/PERSON '/O Strange/O change/O :/O Carresco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O told/O NBC/ORGANIZATION buckets/O of/O change/O were/O left/O by/O the/O insurance/O company/O at/O his/O office/O -LRB-/O file/O photo/O -RRB-/O unique_identifier/O Penny/O for/O your/O thoughts/O ?/O 
Angry/O customer/O takes/O revenge/O after/O he/O 's/O hit/O with/O $/O 6,500/O debt/O .../O by/O paying/O it/O with/O 650,000/O pennies/O Paying/O off/O your/O credit/O card/O bill/O can/O be/O hard/O at/O the/O best/O of/O times/O ./O 
But/O one/O California/LOCATION man/O has/O taken/O clearing/O his/O debts/O to/O a/O new/O level/O after/O he/O tried/O to/O clear/O a/O $/O 6,500/O debt/O with/O 650,000/O pennies/O ./O 
Thirry/PERSON Chahez/PERSON ,/O who/O runs/O a/O cake/O shop/O ,/O loaded/O the/O crates/O of/O coins/O in/O to/O the/O back/O of/O his/O van/O and/O drove/O to/O a/O local/O Chase/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION in/O an/O attempt/O to/O pay/O his/O credit/O card/O bill/O that/O was/O due/O on/O Monday/O ./O 
Thwarted/O :/O Thirry/PERSON Chahez/PERSON tried/O to/O pay/O his/O credit/O card/O debt/O with/O 650,000/O pennies/O Debt/O :/O Initially/O ,/O Mr/O Chahez/PERSON was/O told/O he/O needed/O to/O roll/O the/O coins/O in/O order/O for/O the/O bank/O to/O accept/O them/O But/O despite/O his/O best/O efforts/O ,/O the/O bank/O refused/O to/O accept/O the/O payment/O and/O asked/O Mr/O Chahez/PERSON to/O package/O them/O into/O more/O manageable/O individual/O coin/O rolls/O ./O 
Accepting/O the/O request/O ,/O Mr/O Chahez/PERSON was/O shocked/O when/O the/O bank/O would/O not/O accept/O the/O re-packaged/O payment/O either/O '/O I/O brought/O them/O back/O ,/O and/O now/O they/O 're/O rolled/O and/O they/O still/O do/O n't/O want/O them/O ,/O '/O Mr/O Chahez/PERSON said/O ./O 
Success/O :/O Eventually/O the/O bank/O accepted/O the/O coins/O and/O the/O debt/O was/O settled/O ,/O for/O now/O `/O Do/O my/O pennies/O stink/O ?/O '/O 
He/O said/O ,/O he/O has/O tried/O to/O make/O the/O payment/O for/O days/O at/O several/O different/O branches/O `/O Money/O 's/O money/O is/O n't/O it/O ,/O '/O he/O added/O ./O 
`/O Different/O time/O ,/O different/O branches/O ,/O and/O they/O all/O send/O me/O away/O and/O have/O a/O very/O bad/O attitude/O ./O '/O 
Eventually/O Mr/O Chahez/PERSON managed/O to/O deposit/O the/O money/O and/O pay/O off/O his/O debt/O after/O being/O sent/O to/O a/O branch/O with/O a/O bigger/O vault/O ./O 
Mr/O Chahez/PERSON says/O he/O undertook/O the/O drastic/O measure/O as/O he/O was/O upset/O with/O his/O bank/O over/O a/O refinance/O he/O could/O not/O get/O and/O other/O charges/O and/O fees/O on/O his/O credit/O card/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Appeals/O court/O rules/O for/O ticket/O protestor/O The/O Michigan/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Appeals/ORGANIZATION has/O overturned/O the/O conviction/O of/O a/O western/O Michigan/LOCATION woman/O who/O was/O Tasered/O and/O pepper-sprayed/O after/O protesting/O a/O traffic/O ticket/O in/O Hudsonville/ORGANIZATION District/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION ./O 
The/O Holland/ORGANIZATION Sentinel/ORGANIZATION says/O </O http://bit.ly/10CFw5b/O >/O */O an/O Ottawa/LOCATION County/LOCATION jury/O convicted/O 36-year-old/O Mary/PERSON E./PERSON Vandenberg/PERSON in/O 2012/O of/O resisting/O arrest/O and/O obstructing/O an/O officer/O ./O 
A/O judge/O gave/O her/O $/O 548/O in/O fines/O and/O fees/O ./O 
The/O appeals/O court/O threw/O out/O the/O conviction/O Friday/O ,/O saying/O the/O law/O under/O which/O she/O was/O convicted/O is/O ``/O unconstitutionally/O vague/O and/O overbroad/O ./O ''/O 
Authorities/O say/O Vandenberg/PERSON tried/O to/O pay/O a/O traffic/O fine/O using/O 145/O dollar/O bills/O that/O she/O 'd/O defaced/O with/O red/O and/O black/O markers/O ./O 
They/O say/O employees/O would/O n't/O accept/O the/O money/O ,/O and/O officers/O escorted/O her/O out/O ./O 
Authorities/O say/O officers/O Tasered/O ,/O pepper-sprayed/O and/O handcuffed/O her/O when/O she/O refused/O to/O leave/O the/O building/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Area/O man/O tries/O to/O pay/O old/O traffic/O ticket/O in/O pennies/O Ron/PERSON Seys/PERSON took/O out/O his/O frustration/O over/O having/O to/O pay/O a/O 16-year-old/O traffic/O ticket/O on/O a/O clerk/O at/O the/O Scott/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION this/O week/O ./O 
He/O carried/O a/O sack/O with/O $/O 59.40/O in/O pennies/O into/O the/O courthouse/O in/O Davenport/LOCATION ,/O showed/O the/O clerk/O the/O old/O ticket/O and/O then/O dumped/O the/O load/O on/O her/O counter/O ./O 
``/O Did/O I/O do/O this/O on/O purpose/O ?/O 
Yes/O ,/O I/O did/O ,/O to/O make/O a/O point/O ,/O ''/O Seys/PERSON said/O afterward/O ./O 
The/O rural/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION man/O said/O he/O went/O to/O a/O bank/O Wednesday/O morning/O to/O get/O the/O pennies/O and/O emptied/O each/O roll/O into/O his/O sack/O ./O 
About/O a/O month/O ago/O ,/O Seys/PERSON received/O a/O letter/O from/O the/O Iowa/ORGANIZATION Department/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Transportation/ORGANIZATION demanding/O that/O he/O pay/O an/O outstanding/O 1996/O ticket/O for/O improper/O registration/O ./O 
The/O state/O recently/O entered/O into/O a/O contract/O with/O the/O Kansas/LOCATION City/LOCATION ,/O Mo./LOCATION ,/O law/O firm/O of/O Linebarger/PERSON ,/O Goggan/LOCATION ,/O Blair/PERSON and/O Sampson/ORGANIZATION LLP/ORGANIZATION to/O collect/O court/O fines/O and/O fees/O that/O have/O been/O unpaid/O for/O more/O than/O a/O year/O ./O 
State/O law/O also/O requires/O county/O treasurers/O to/O refuse/O to/O renew/O a/O vehicle/O registration/O when/O the/O vehicle/O owner/O owes/O unpaid/O fines/O and/O court/O fees/O ./O 
State/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION Administrator/O David/PERSON Boyd/PERSON said/O in/O September/O that/O the/O state/O is/O boosting/O collection/O efforts/O to/O recoup/O past-due/O obligations/O in/O the/O face/O of/O shrinking/O revenues/O ./O 
Seys/PERSON does/O n't/O remember/O getting/O the/O ticket/O and/O said/O he/O 's/O been/O able/O to/O renew/O his/O driver/O 's/O license/O in/O the/O years/O since/O ,/O until/O recently/O ./O 
Seys/PERSON also/O said/O he/O did/O n't/O realize/O he/O could/O n't/O use/O pennies/O to/O pay/O off/O the/O ticket/O ,/O although/O signs/O at/O the/O clerk/O 's/O office/O say/O no/O more/O than/O $/O 3/O in/O pennies/O can/O be/O used/O for/O payment/O ./O 
Two/O Scott/LOCATION County/LOCATION sheriff/O 's/O deputies/O showed/O up/O in/O the/O office/O and/O told/O Seys/PERSON he/O was/O harassing/O the/O clerk/O ./O 
They/O asked/O him/O to/O pick/O up/O the/O pennies/O and/O put/O them/O back/O into/O the/O bag/O ./O 
Many/O of/O the/O pennies/O had/O fallen/O onto/O the/O floor/O ./O 
He/O then/O paid/O the/O ticket/O in/O other/O cash/O ,/O slung/O the/O sack/O of/O pennies/O over/O his/O shoulder/O and/O left/O the/O courthouse/O ./O 
Outside/O ,/O he/O said/O he/O did/O n't/O do/O anything/O wrong/O ./O 
``/O Since/O when/O is/O it/O wrong/O to/O use/O legal/O tender/O ?/O ''/O 
he/O said/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Asshole/O pays/O 10,000/O yuan/O assault/O charge/O in/O coins/O It/O took/O bank/O workers/O in/O Kunming/LOCATION ,/O Yunnan/LOCATION province/O over/O eight/O hours/O to/O process/O 5,000/O yuan/O in/O one/O jiao/O -LRB-/O 0.1/O yuan/O -RRB-/O coins/O paid/O to/O a/O woman/O surnamed/O Wu/PERSON as/O compensation/O for/O assault/O ./O 
In/O September/O 2012/O ,/O Wu/PERSON was/O eating/O at/O a/O noodle/O restaurant/O when/O she/O and/O her/O husband/O got/O into/O an/O altercation/O with/O the/O owner/O ./O 
After/O leaving/O a/O restaurant/O worker/O chased/O after/O the/O couple/O and/O attacked/O them/O ,/O leaving/O Wu/PERSON with/O a/O brain/O contusion/O and/O her/O husband/O with/O three/O broken/O ribs/O ./O 
A/O court/O ruled/O in/O June/O 2013/O that/O the/O restaurant/O must/O compensate/O Wu/PERSON 68,000/O yuan/O in/O damages/O ./O 
After/O paying/O a/O portion/O of/O the/O compensation/O through/O his/O lawyer/O ,/O the/O restaurant/O owner/O called/O Wu/PERSON on/O August/O 9th/O to/O pick/O up/O 10,000/O yuan/O of/O the/O remainder/O ./O 
Upon/O arrival/O Wu/PERSON was/O presented/O with/O eight/O bags/O containing/O the/O sum/O in/O one/O jiao/O coins/O ./O 
18/O employees/O at/O a/O Kunming/LOCATION ICBC/LOCATION branch/O spent/O all/O day/O counting/O around/O half/O of/O the/O money/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Attempt/O to/O pay/O property/O taxes/O in/O $/O 1/O bills/O lands/O man/O in/O jail/O A/O Wichita/LOCATION Falls/LOCATION man/O was/O arrested/O by/O a/O Wichita/ORGANIZATION County/ORGANIZATION Sheriff/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Office/ORGANIZATION deputy/O Jan./O 28/O for/O refusing/O to/O leave/O the/O Wichita/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION Annex/LOCATION while/O trying/O to/O pay/O his/O property/O tax/O in/O $/O 1/O bills/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O affidavit/O :/O The/O deputy/O was/O at/O the/O Annex/O ,/O 600/O Scott/LOCATION Street/LOCATION ,/O just/O after/O 2/O p.m./O when/O Wichita/LOCATION County/LOCATION Tax/O Assessor/O Collector/O Tommy/PERSON Smyth/PERSON asked/O Timothy/PERSON Andrew/PERSON Norris/PERSON ,/O 27/O ,/O to/O leave/O the/O tax/O office/O ./O 
Smyth/PERSON accused/O Norris/PERSON of/O disrupting/O the/O operation/O and/O efficiency/O of/O the/O tax/O office/O by/O attempting/O to/O pay/O $/O 600-worth/O of/O property/O taxes/O with/O $/O 1/O bills/O ./O 
The/O bills/O were/O said/O to/O be/O folded/O so/O tightly/O it/O ``/O required/O tax/O office/O personnel/O approximately/O six/O minutes/O to/O unfold/O each/O bill/O ./O ''/O 
When/O Norris/PERSON refused/O ,/O he/O was/O arrested/O and/O charged/O with/O criminal/O trespass/O ./O 
As/O the/O deputy/O grabbed/O Norris/PERSON '/O arm/O to/O place/O him/O in/O handcuffs/O ,/O Norris/PERSON pulled/O away/O ./O 
He/O pulled/O away/O again/O when/O the/O deputy/O went/O to/O grab/O his/O arm/O a/O second/O time/O ,/O causing/O the/O deputy/O and/O Smyth/PERSON to/O wrestle/O Norris/PERSON to/O the/O ground/O to/O detain/O him/O --/O bringing/O an/O additional/O charge/O of/O resisting/O arrest/O ./O 
Norris/PERSON '/O bail/O totaled/O $/O 500/O for/O both/O charges/O ./O 
He/O was/O not/O in/O the/O Wichita/LOCATION County/LOCATION Jail/LOCATION Monday/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Pay/O and/O dismay/O :/O Irate/O driver/O pays/O #/O 35/O parking/O fine/O with/O 1,200/O coins/O An/O irate/O Australian/O driver/O got/O his/O own/O back/O on/O a/O council/O by/O paying/O his/O $/O 60/O -LRB-/O #/O 35/O -RRB-/O parking/O fine/O with/O 1,200/O five/O cent/O coins/O ./O 
After/O going/O to/O the/O bank/O for/O bags/O of/O change/O ,/O the/O motorist/O poured/O sacks/O of/O coins/O on/O to/O the/O counter/O to/O the/O astonishment/O of/O two/O cashiers/O after/O asking/O `/O cash/O alright/O ?/O '/O 
./O 
The/O anonymous/O man/O uploaded/O a/O clip/O of/O the/O moment/O he/O exacted/O revenge/O on/O Adelaide/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION to/O YouTube/ORGANIZATION ,/O where/O it/O has/O already/O been/O viewed/O 150,000/O times/O ./O 
But/O his/O stunt/O backfired/O after/O officials/O told/O him/O they/O could/O not/O accept/O the/O payment/O ./O 
Under/O Australian/O law/O payments/O made/O with/O five/O cent/O coins/O can/O be/O refused/O for/O transactions/O greater/O than/O $/O 5/O -LRB-/O #/O 3/O -RRB-/O --/O presumably/O to/O stop/O shenanigans/O like/O this/O one/O ./O 
Undeterred/O by/O the/O cashier/O 's/O refusal/O to/O take/O payment/O he/O pushed/O the/O coins/O back/O over/O the/O counter/O at/O her/O and/O walked/O out/O saying/O :/O `/O I/O paid/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O out/O ./O 
Bye/O ./O 
I/O gave/O you/O the/O money/O ./O '/O 
A/O council/O spokesman/O told/O Australian/O news/O website/O news.com.au/O that/O the/O fine/O is/O still/O `/O outstanding/O '/O following/O the/O cranky/O motorist/O 's/O stunt/O on/O Friday/O ./O 
The/O man/O 's/O money/O is/O being/O held/O in/O its/O safe/O and/O he/O has/O been/O sent/O a/O letter/O asking/O him/O to/O collect/O it/O ,/O added/O a/O council/O spokesman/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Australian/O driver/O pays/O fine/O in/O coins/O ,/O gets/O rejected/O After/O receiving/O a/O parking/O fine/O of/O $/O 60/O -LRB-/O #/O 35/O -RRB-/O ,/O an/O Australian/O driver/O was/O so/O angry/O that/O he/O decided/O to/O get/O revenge/O by/O paying/O his/O fine/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
The/O motorist/O 's/O moment/O of/O glory/O has/O been/O immortalised/O in/O a/O video/O ,/O which/O he/O published/O on/O YouTube/ORGANIZATION ,/O showing/O him/O pouring/O out/O his/O sack/O of/O coins/O onto/O the/O desk/O of/O a/O council/O cashier/O ,/O saying/O ``/O Cash/O alright/O ?/O ''/O 
The/O man/O 's/O victory/O is/O short-lived/O ,/O however/O ,/O as/O the/O cashier/O is/O quick/O to/O inform/O him/O that/O she/O can/O not/O accept/O the/O payment/O ./O 
But/O the/O motorist/O leaves/O the/O coins/O and/O walks/O out/O of/O Adelaide/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION 's/O offices/O saying/O ,/O ``/O I/O paid/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O out/O ./O 
Bye/O ./O 
I/O gave/O you/O the/O money/O ./O ''/O 
However/O ,/O Adelaide/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION has/O stated/O that/O the/O 5-cent/O coins/O can/O not/O be/O accepted/O as/O payment/O for/O fine/O ./O 
Their/O spokesman/O told/O ABC/ORGANIZATION news/O :/O ``/O We/O will/O be/O sending/O the/O customer/O a/O letter/O to/O communicate/O the/O fine/O remains/O outstanding/O and/O his/O money/O is/O being/O held/O in/O the/O safe/O ./O ''/O 
Under/O Australian/O law/O ,/O as/O with/O UK/LOCATION law/O ,/O there/O is/O a/O restriction/O on/O the/O amount/O you/O can/O pay/O using/O small/O change/O ./O 
In/O Australia/LOCATION ,/O where/O they/O do/O n't/O even/O have/O coppers/O ,/O payment/O in/O 5-cent/O coins/O can/O be/O refused/O for/O amounts/O over/O $/O 5/O ./O 
In/O the/O UK/LOCATION ,/O under/O the/O Coinage/O Act/O 1971/O ,/O 1ps/O and/O 2ps/O are/O legal/O tender/O to/O the/O value/O of/O 20p/O ./O 
However/O ,/O if/O the/O vendor/O accepts/O payment/O in/O coins/O ,/O you/O can/O legally/O use/O them/O for/O larger/O amounts/O ./O 
There/O are/O also/O restrictions/O on/O other/O coins/O :/O 5ps/O and/O 10ps/O can/O be/O used/O to/O pay/O up/O to/O #/O 5/O ,/O 20ps/O and/O 50ps/O for/O amounts/O up/O to/O #/O 10/O ,/O but/O #/O 1/O and/O #/O 2/O coins/O can/O be/O used/O for/O any/O amount/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Australian/O Man/O Pays/O City/O Council/O Parking/O Fine/O In/O 5/O Cent/O Coins/O -LRB-/O VIDEO/O -RRB-/O An/O Australian/O man/O from/O Adelaide/LOCATION was/O fined/O $/O 60/O by/O City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION Parking/ORGANIZATION has/O come/O up/O with/O a/O novel/O way/O of/O paying/O his/O fine/O --/O in/O 5/O cent/O coins/O ./O 
Being/O angry/O at/O City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION ,/O the/O man/O decided/O to/O take/O revenge/O and/O paid/O the/O amount/O in/O 1200/O coins/O of/O 5/O cents/O each/O ./O 
This/O whole/O incident/O was/O shot/O from/O camera/O mounted/O on/O his/O head/O ./O 
However/O ,/O his/O revenge/O plan/O backfired/O when/O the/O cashier/O refused/O to/O take/O his/O money/O ./O 
According/O to/O Australian/O laws/O ,/O cashiers/O can/O refuse/O to/O take/O in/O 5/O cent/O coins/O for/O anything/O over/O $/O 5/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Australian/O Man/O Pays/O Parking/O Ticket/O In/O 5c/O Coins/O But/O The/O Joke/O 's/O On/O Him/O An/O unidentified/O driver/O in/O Adelaide/LOCATION recorded/O himself/O paying/O a/O $/O 60/O parking/O ticket/O in/O five/O cent/O coins/O last/O Friday/O ./O 
Unfortunately/O ,/O it/O appears/O that/O the/O Adelaide/LOCATION city/O council/O has/O the/O upper/O hand/O ./O 
The/O video/O ,/O which/O has/O already/O racked/O up/O 296,065/O views/O on/O YouTube/ORGANIZATION and/O 172,511/O on/O LiveLeak/O ,/O shows/O the/O fined/O driver/O asking/O ``/O Is/O cash/O alright/O ?/O ''/O 
before/O dumping/O 1,200/O coins/O on/O the/O receptionist/O 's/O counter/O ./O 
The/O cashier/O affirmed/O that/O she/O could/O not/O accept/O the/O coins/O ,/O but/O the/O fined/O driver/O disagreed/O ./O 
A/O security/O guard/O showed/O up/O ,/O there/O was/O a/O brief/O argument/O ,/O and/O the/O fined/O man/O left/O with/O the/O words/O ,/O ``/O I/O paid/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O out/O ./O 
Bye/O ./O 
I/O gave/O you/O the/O money/O ./O ''/O 
//O News.com.au/O //O reports/O ,/O however/O ,/O that/O according/O to/O Australian/O law/O ,/O anyone/O can/O legally/O refuse/O payments/O made/O with/O five/O cent/O coins/O for/O transactions/O over/O five/O dollars/O ./O 
//O News.com.au/O //O also/O reports/O that/O the/O man/O 's/O fine/O is/O still/O considered/O outstanding/O and/O his/O change/O is/O being/O held/O in/O a/O safe/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Azerbaijani/O Activists/O Raise/O Funds/O To/O Pay/O Protesters/O '/O Fines/O In/O Small/O Coins/O Azerbaijani/O activists/O say/O they/O have/O raised/O 11,600/O manats/O -LRB-/O $/O 14,770/O -RRB-/O to/O pay/O fines/O for/O protesters/O who/O have/O been/O fined/O hundreds/O of/O dollars/O under/O a/O new/O law/O on/O mass/O gatherings/O ./O 
Representatives/O of/O the/O Positive/O Change/O youth/O movement/O told/O RFE/RL/ORGANIZATION on/O January/O 21/O that/O the/O money/O will/O be/O delivered/O to/O the/O authorities/O in/O the/O form/O of/O five-qapik/O coins/O -LRB-/O 100/O qapiks/O =/O 1/O manat/O -RRB-/O if/O the/O protesters/O lose/O their/O appeal/O and/O the/O fines/O are/O confirmed/O ./O 
The/O campaign/O to/O raise/O the/O money/O was/O launched/O last/O week/O after/O more/O than/O 20/O men/O were/O fined/O for/O participating/O in/O a/O Baku/LOCATION demonstration/O on/O January/O 12/O ./O 
The/O event/O was/O aimed/O at/O raising/O awareness/O about/O the/O deaths/O of/O army/O conscripts/O ./O 
The/O men/O have/O been/O ordered/O to/O pay/O fines/O ranging/O from/O $/O 380/O to/O $/O 760/O -LRB-/O 300/O to/O 600/O manats/O -RRB-/O each/O ,/O adding/O up/O to/O a/O total/O of/O $/O 13,400/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Bad/O business/O :/O Fla./LOCATION car/O dealership/O gives/O woman/O refund/O in/O pennies/O A/O Florida/LOCATION woman/O is/O outraged/O after/O buying/O a/O faulty/O car/O from/O a/O Jacksonville/LOCATION dealership/O and/O receiving/O a/O refund/O in/O thousands/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
Irena/PERSON Mujakovic/PERSON </O //O topics/irena-mujakovic/O //O >/O bought/O a/O 2003/O Saab/ORGANIZATION from/O Holiday/ORGANIZATION Motors/ORGANIZATION </O //O topics/holiday-motors/O //O >/O in/O January/O that/O ended/O up/O needing/O transmission/O repairs/O ./O 
Holiday/O Motors/O </O //O topics/holiday-motors/O //O >/O first/O repaired/O the/O vehicle/O for/O $/O 300/O and/O sold/O her/O a/O warranty/O ,/O First/ORGANIZATION Coast/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION reported/O ./O 
The/O transmission/O went/O out/O a/O second/O time/O ,/O and/O the/O dealer/O charged/O her/O an/O additional/O $/O 400/O ,/O saying/O the/O warranty/O did/O n't/O cover/O costs/O of/O labor/O ./O 
``/O I/O though/O it/O unfair/O because/O nobody/O said/O that/O to/O me/O ,/O ''/O Miss/O Mujakovic/PERSON told/O the/O station/O ./O 
She/O filed/O a/O complaint/O with/O the/O Florida/ORGANIZATION Department/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Motor/ORGANIZATION Vehicles/ORGANIZATION ,/O which/O directed/O the/O dealer/O to/O give/O her/O a/O refund/O ./O 
Irena/PERSON Mujakovic/PERSON is/O outraged/O after/O buying/O a/O faulty/O car/O from/O a/O Jacksonville/LOCATION dealership/O and/O receiving/O a/O refund/O in/O thousands/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
But/O when/O Miss/O Mujakovic/PERSON went/O back/O to/O the/O dealership/O to/O collect/O her/O refund/O ,/O she/O was/O disturbed/O when/O she/O was/O handed/O two/O bags/O full/O of/O pennies/O and/O a/O handful/O of/O dollar/O bills/O ./O 
Not/O knowing/O how/O much/O money/O was/O even/O in/O the/O bags/O ,/O Miss/O Mujakovic/PERSON left/O them/O at/O the/O dealership/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O so/O mad/O with/O them/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
When/O asked/O by/O First/ORGANIZATION Coast/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION if/O the/O pennies/O were/O retaliation/O for/O her/O complaint/O ,/O Holiday/ORGANIZATION Motors/ORGANIZATION owner/O Ed/PERSON Di/PERSON Miranda/PERSON said/O ,/O ``/O I/O am/O doing/O what/O DMV/ORGANIZATION asked/O me/O to/O do/O ./O ''/O 
``/O It/O is/O legal/O tender/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O The/O warranty/O did/O not/O cover/O labor/O and/O I/O failed/O to/O write/O that/O in/O and/O that/O was/O her/O loophole/O ./O ''/O 
Mr./O Di/PERSON Miranda/PERSON said/O he/O emptied/O containers/O where/O he/O collects/O spare/O change/O because/O business/O has/O been/O slow/O lately/O ./O 
The/O money/O is/O reportedly/O still/O waiting/O at/O the/O dealership/O for/O Miss/O Mujakovic/PERSON ./O 
unique_identifier/O Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION woman/O protests/O $/O 570/O water/O bill/O by/O paying/O in/O pennies/O ,/O nickels/O and/O dimes/O Sarah/PERSON LeVasseur/PERSON really/O wanted/O Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION employees/O to/O feel/O the/O impact/O of/O her/O $/O 569.81/O adjusted/O water/O bill/O ./O 
So/O the/O 75-year-old/O woman/O on/O Thursday/O ,/O July/O 31/O ,/O packed/O coolers/O and/O suitcases/O with/O rolls/O of/O pennies/O ,/O nickels/O and/O dimes/O ,/O drove/O to/O City/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION and/O plopped/O the/O total/O amount/O of/O her/O larger-than-normal/O bill/O on/O the/O floor/O of/O the/O Accounts/O Receivable/O office/O ./O 
The/O bill/O ,/O officials/O say/O ,/O included/O her/O monthly/O usage/O ,/O plus/O charges/O for/O past/O water/O use/O that/O did/O n't/O show/O up/O on/O past/O bills/O because/O her/O outdoor/O water/O meter/O was/O n't/O reading/O properly/O ./O 
``/O I/O want/O to/O let/O them/O know/O I/O 'm/O upset/O ,/O ''/O LeVasseur/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O I/O was/O told/O my/O reading/O has/O been/O a/O mistake/O for/O the/O past/O several/O months/O and/O that/O none/O of/O my/O past/O bills/O were/O accurate/O ./O ''/O 
While/O there/O was/O an/O initial/O objection/O to/O accepting/O the/O tender/O of/O rolled/O coins/O ,/O George/PERSON Martini/PERSON ,/O the/O city/O 's/O financial/O services/O director/O ,/O personally/O counted/O and/O accepted/O the/O payment/O ./O 
Five/O years/O ago/O ,/O Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION resident/O Richard/PERSON O'Hara/PERSON attempted/O to/O pay/O his/O water/O and/O electric/O bill/O in/O pennies/O and/O nickels/O ,/O but/O Neil/PERSON Wackerly/PERSON ,/O the/O city/O 's/O attorney/O rendered/O an/O opinion/O that/O paying/O with/O coins/O is/O ``/O dangerous/O and/O inconvenient/O for/O the/O city/O ./O ''/O 
Martini/PERSON said/O he/O was/O made/O aware/O of/O the/O legal/O opinion/O Thursday/O morning/O ,/O but/O decided/O the/O better/O solution/O was/O to/O count/O the/O coins/O and/O bring/O it/O straight/O to/O the/O bank/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O a/O pain/O ,/O but/O it/O 's/O money/O ,/O ''/O Martini/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O She/O was/O obviously/O upset/O about/O the/O bill/O she/O received/O and/O wanted/O to/O make/O her/O protest/O ./O ''/O 
Martini/PERSON said/O he/O needed/O an/O additional/O city/O employee/O to/O help/O him/O carry/O the/O heavy/O coins/O to/O his/O car/O ./O 
LeVasseur/PERSON said/O if/O the/O city/O did/O n't/O accept/O her/O coins/O ,/O she/O planned/O to/O fill/O up/O wheelbarrows/O and/O deliver/O the/O payment/O in/O front/O of/O the/O Bay/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Commission/ORGANIZATION ./O 
While/O the/O act/O of/O paying/O in/O coins/O was/O done/O in/O protest/O ,/O and/O perhaps/O in/O jest/O ,/O it/O exposes/O a/O potential/O problem/O as/O the/O city/O continues/O to/O roll/O out/O its/O $/O 6.8/O million/O smart/O meter/O program/O ./O 
LeVasseur/PERSON had/O her/O smart/O meter/O installed/O earlier/O this/O month/O ./O 
She/O did/O n't/O experience/O any/O plumbing/O issues/O ,/O as/O some/O have/O had/O during/O the/O transition/O ,/O but/O her/O water/O meter/O was/O read/O before/O the/O switch-out/O and/O it/O did/O n't/O match/O her/O outdoor/O water/O meter/O --/O the/O meter/O that/O city/O staff/O have/O read/O for/O the/O past/O two/O years/O and/O reported/O to/O billing/O ./O 
Some/O houses/O have/O touchpads/O that/O are/O connected/O to/O the/O inside/O meter/O ,/O which/O gives/O the/O most/O accurate/O reading/O ,/O while/O others/O have/O an/O inside/O meter/O and/O an/O outside/O meter/O that/O are/O connected/O ,/O but/O are/O n't/O always/O in-sync/O ,/O said/O Martini/PERSON ./O 
``/O For/O various/O reasons/O ,/O the/O outside/O meter/O does/O n't/O always/O lineup/O with/O the/O inside/O meter/O ,/O ''/O Martini/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O It/O could/O be/O as/O simple/O as/O a/O spider/O getting/O into/O the/O meter/O and/O gumming/O things/O up/O --/O it/O could/O be/O a/O number/O of/O things/O that/O might/O slow/O it/O down/O ./O 
That/O 's/O one/O of/O the/O reasons/O why/O we/O spent/O $/O 6/O million/O to/O upgrade/O to/O the/O AMI/O meters/O ./O ''/O 
LeVasseur/PERSON 's/O inside/O meter/O was/O last/O checked/O out/O by/O city/O staff/O in/O August/O 2012/O ./O 
At/O that/O time/O ,/O Martini/PERSON said/O ,/O there/O was/O a/O slight/O discrepancy/O between/O that/O meter/O and/O her/O outside/O meter/O ./O 
The/O problem/O was/O corrected/O ,/O but/O it/O came/O back/O ./O 
Her/O bills/O range/O from/O $/O 140/O to/O $/O 160/O per/O month/O on/O average/O and/O should/O continue/O to/O be/O about/O that/O much/O ,/O pending/O any/O major/O spikes/O in/O usage/O ,/O Martini/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O Really/O ,/O one/O of/O the/O biggest/O problems/O we/O have/O are/O the/O people/O who/O literally/O pay/O their/O bill/O every/O month/O and/O never/O have/O any/O issues/O ,/O ''/O Martini/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O We/O never/O get/O into/O their/O house/O to/O shut/O off/O the/O water/O ,/O look/O at/O their/O meter/O ,/O so/O we/O miss/O these/O things/O ./O 
It/O 's/O the/O squeaky/O wheel/O gets/O the/O grease/O analogy/O ./O ''/O 
Earlier/O this/O summer/O ,/O owners/O of/O Columbus/ORGANIZATION Laundromat/ORGANIZATION ,/O 1000/O Columbus/LOCATION Ave./LOCATION ,/O battled/O with/O the/O city/O for/O three/O months/O after/O receiving/O an/O initial/O bill/O adjustment/O of/O more/O than/O $/O 18,000/O ./O 
The/O city/O made/O errors/O over/O a/O two-year/O period/O with/O the/O laundromat/O ,/O including/O installing/O the/O wrong/O type/O of/O outdoor/O meter/O and/O estimating/O usage/O in/O the/O billing/O department/O ./O 
A/O deal/O was/O eventually/O reached/O with/O the/O city/O that/O included/O a/O 15/O percent/O discount/O and/O an/O opportunity/O to/O pay/O the/O bill/O off/O over/O five/O years/O at/O zero/O percent/O interest/O ./O 
Martini/PERSON said/O the/O city/O offered/O LeVasseur/PERSON several/O opportunities/O to/O pay/O her/O bill/O at/O zero/O percent/O interest/O over/O the/O next/O year/O ./O 
She/O wanted/O to/O just/O take/O care/O of/O it/O ,/O though/O ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O deal/O with/O any/O late/O fees/O or/O my/O service/O being/O shut/O off/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
``/O If/O this/O happens/O again/O though/O ,/O I/O 'm/O not/O going/O to/O pay/O it/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O buys/O Chevy/ORGANIZATION with/O small/O change/O An/O Ohio/LOCATION man/O with/O a/O hatred/O of/O paper/O money/O slapped/O down/O $/O 8,000/O in/O coins/O at/O a/O car/O dealership/O to/O buy/O a/O Chevrolet/ORGANIZATION pick-up/O -/O then/O paid/O the/O rest/O by/O cheque/O ./O 
James/PERSON Jones/PERSON ,/O 70/O ,/O produced/O 16/O coffee/O cans/O full/O of/O coins/O to/O buy/O his/O new/O Chevrolet/ORGANIZATION Silverado/ORGANIZATION in/O Cincinnati/LOCATION and/O staff/O spent/O 90/O minutes/O counting/O it/O ./O 
But/O his/O coin/O hoard/O only/O covered/O half/O of/O the/O $/O 16,000/O -LRB-/O 8,500/O -RRB-/O price/O tag/O ./O 
The/O man/O 's/O son/O said/O the/O most/O amazing/O thing/O for/O him/O was/O his/O father/O deciding/O to/O replace/O his/O 1981/O pick-up/O at/O all/O ./O 
As/O far/O back/O as/O he/O could/O remember/O ,/O Dennis/PERSON Jones/PERSON told/O the/O Cincinnati/ORGANIZATION Enquirer/ORGANIZATION ,/O his/O father/O had/O always/O had/O coins/O ./O 
He/O gave/O me/O lunch/O money/O in/O coins/O and/O each/O time/O he/O ever/O gave/O me/O money/O it/O was/O in/O coins/O ,/O he/O recalled/O ./O 
I/O am/O amazed/O that/O we/O were/O able/O to/O talk/O him/O into/O buying/O a/O new/O truck/O ,/O because/O he/O is/O pretty/O tight/O with/O his/O money/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O paper/O ,/O James/PERSON Jones/PERSON walked/O into/O the/O Jake/PERSON Sweeney/PERSON dealership/O ,/O plunked/O down/O his/O cans/O and/O said/O :/O I/O want/O that/O Chevy/ORGANIZATION truck/O ./O 
``/O In/O my/O 19/O years/O in/O this/O business/O I/O have/O never/O seen/O anything/O like/O this/O ,/O said/O Biff/PERSON Arnold/PERSON ,/O finance/O manager/O for/O Jake/PERSON Sweeney/PERSON ./O 
I/O have/O seen/O many/O buyers/O come/O in/O with/O a/O lot/O of/O cash/O money/O ,/O but/O never/O this/O much/O money/O in/O coins/O ./O 
Salesman/O David/PERSON Crisswell/PERSON said/O the/O coins/O included/O ``/O dimes/O ,/O quarters/O ,/O half-dollars/O ,/O silver/O and/O Susan/PERSON B/PERSON Anthony/PERSON dollars/O ''/O ./O 
The/O new/O owner/O of/O the/O Chevy/ORGANIZATION says/O he/O does/O not/O trust/O banks/O or/O paper/O money/O ./O 
Paper/O money/O will/O burn/O ,/O but/O it/O is/O hard/O to/O damage/O coins/O ,/O ''/O the/O retired/O engineer/O pointed/O out/O ./O 
``/O I/O bought/O four/O or/O five/O rolls/O of/O coins/O each/O month/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O know/O how/O long/O it/O took/O me/O to/O save/O this/O amount/O ,/O probably/O all/O my/O life/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Cornwall/LOCATION demands/O economic/O help/O Hundreds/O of/O campaigners/O demanding/O help/O for/O Cornwall/ORGANIZATION 's/O economy/O have/O staged/O a/O protest/O at/O a/O toll/O bridge/O across/O the/O River/LOCATION Tamar/LOCATION ./O 
Greg/PERSON Woods/PERSON said/O Cornwall/LOCATION can/O not/O afford/O more/O job/O losses/O on/O BBC/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION 24/O -LRB-/O 3/O '/O 35/O '/O -RRB-/O The/O demonstration/O has/O been/O organised/O by/O the/O Cornish/ORGANIZATION Solidarity/ORGANIZATION Action/ORGANIZATION Group/ORGANIZATION ,/O which/O was/O formed/O following/O the/O closure/O of/O Europe/LOCATION 's/O last/O tin/O mine/O ,/O South/LOCATION Crofty/LOCATION ,/O last/O week/O ./O 
The/O convoy/O of/O protesters/O ,/O many/O waving/O black/O and/O white/O Cornish/PERSON flags/O from/O their/O vehicles/O ,/O drove/O to/O the/O Tamar/LOCATION Bridge/LOCATION ,/O and/O used/O pennies/O to/O pay/O the/O 1/O toll/O to/O enter/O Devon/LOCATION at/O Plymouth/LOCATION ./O 
Greg/PERSON Woods/PERSON ,/O Cornish/ORGANIZATION Solidarity/ORGANIZATION chairman/O ,/O who/O was/O active/O in/O the/O community/O campaign/O to/O save/O the/O mine/O ,/O said/O the/O protesters/O were/O paying/O in/O pennies/O ``/O because/O that/O is/O all/O we/O have/O got/O left/O to/O pay/O with/O in/O Cornwall/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
He/O said/O Cornwall/LOCATION was/O currently/O losing/O about/O 50/O jobs/O a/O week/O ,/O and/O young/O people/O were/O having/O to/O leave/O the/O area/O to/O look/O elsewhere/O for/O work/O ./O 
He/O said/O Cornwall/LOCATION was/O experiencing/O a/O ``/O youth/O drain/O ,/O ''/O because/O youngsters/O had/O to/O leave/O the/O county/O to/O get/O a/O university/O degree/O ,/O and/O then/O stayed/O away/O because/O there/O was/O nothing/O to/O go/O back/O to/O ./O 
The/O organisers/O were/O demanding/O special/O status/O for/O Cornwall/ORGANIZATION ,/O which/O would/O give/O the/O county/O the/O same/O benefits/O as/O South/LOCATION Wales/LOCATION and/O Merseyside/LOCATION in/O terms/O of/O development/O grants/O to/O businesses/O ./O 
Last/O month/O ,/O a/O 20/O car/O convoy/O ,/O including/O miners/O ,/O farmers/O ,/O fishermen/O and/O councillors/O ,/O caused/O a/O six/O mile/O traffic/O jam/O when/O they/O drove/O at/O a/O snail/O 's/O pace/O on/O the/O main/O A30/O road/O ,/O half/O the/O length/O of/O the/O county/O to/O the/O Devon/O border/O to/O protest/O about/O the/O Cornish/PERSON economy/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Parcel/O of/O 10p/O coins/O sparks/O scare/O A/O motorist/O who/O paid/O a/O 30/O fixed/O penalty/O charge/O in/O 10p/O pieces/O sparked/O a/O bomb/O scare/O in/O Suffolk/LOCATION when/O the/O parcel/O was/O treated/O as/O a/O suspect/O package/O ./O 
Staff/O at/O a/O ticket/O handling/O office/O in/O the/O centre/O of/O Ipswich/ORGANIZATION called/O police/O after/O noticing/O the/O package/O was/O unusually/O heavy/O ,/O Suffolk/ORGANIZATION Police/ORGANIZATION said/O ./O 
Workers/O were/O evacuated/O ,/O buses/O were/O diverted/O and/O an/O army/O bomb/O disposal/O team/O was/O brought/O in/O to/O X-ray/O the/O package/O ./O 
It/O was/O then/O discovered/O it/O contained/O coins/O sent/O as/O payment/O for/O the/O fine/O ./O 
Staff/O raised/O alarm/O Staff/O at/O the/O Central/ORGANIZATION Ticket/ORGANIZATION Office/ORGANIZATION reported/O the/O package/O felt/O heavy/O and/O rattled/O when/O moved/O ./O 
The/O office/O processes/O payment/O of/O fines/O for/O police/O ,/O magistrates/O '/O courts/O and/O Suffolk/ORGANIZATION SafeCam/ORGANIZATION ,/O which/O operates/O speed/O cameras/O in/O the/O county/O ./O 
The/O sender/O paid/O for/O the/O parcel/O to/O be/O sent/O by/O special/O delivery/O ./O 
A/O Suffolk/ORGANIZATION Police/ORGANIZATION spokeswoman/O said/O after/O police/O received/O the/O report/O of/O the/O suspect/O package/O an/O army/O bomb/O disposal/O team/O from/O Colchester/LOCATION barracks/O in/O Essex/LOCATION was/O called/O in/O ./O 
Michelle/PERSON Finnerty/PERSON ,/O from/O Suffolk/LOCATION SafeCam/LOCATION ,/O said/O :/O ``/O The/O sender/O on/O this/O occasion/O has/O wasted/O police/O time/O ,/O has/O wasted/O the/O bomb/O disposal/O team/O 's/O time/O and/O caused/O unnecessary/O concern/O and/O anxiety/O ./O 
``/O In/O the/O process/O they/O 've/O cost/O themselves/O more/O money/O in/O having/O to/O post/O the/O parcel/O special/O delivery/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Back/O pay/O row/O over/O crate/O of/O coins/O A/O man/O involved/O in/O an/O employment/O dispute/O has/O had/O his/O 1,300/O severance/O pay/O delivered/O to/O him/O in/O a/O crate/O full/O of/O small/O change/O weighing/O 11/O stone/O ./O 
Mr/O Raine/PERSON ,/O from/O Burnhope/LOCATION in/O County/LOCATION Durham/LOCATION ,/O was/O expecting/O a/O cheque/O for/O the/O balance/O of/O his/O cash/O award/O ,/O following/O an/O industrial/O tribunal/O win/O ./O 
But/O the/O acrimonious/O split/O from/O his/O bus/O firm/O boss/O ,/O Malcolm/PERSON Lee/PERSON ,/O ended/O with/O a/O crate/O of/O coins/O dumped/O at/O his/O door/O ./O 
Mr/O Raine/PERSON ,/O 61/O ,/O said/O he/O intended/O to/O seek/O legal/O advice/O to/O resolve/O the/O matter/O ./O 
The/O delivery/O came/O after/O a/O protracted/O wrangle/O between/O Mr/O Raine/PERSON and/O his/O former/O employer/O Malcolm/PERSON Lee/PERSON ,/O who/O runs/O Lee/PERSON 's/O Coaches/O in/O nearby/O Langley/LOCATION Moor/LOCATION ./O 
Mr/O Raine/PERSON said/O he/O quit/O his/O job/O in/O 2005/O on/O medical/O advice/O and/O spent/O his/O last/O days/O at/O work/O on/O sick/O leave/O ./O 
He/O claimed/O he/O had/O been/O under-paid/O and/O was/O awarded/O 2,300/O at/O a/O subsequent/O industrial/O tribunal/O ./O 
Legal/O wrangle/O He/O received/O a/O cheque/O for/O 1,000/O and/O the/O remaining/O amount/O in/O coins/O from/O 1p/O to/O 20p/O ./O 
Mr/O Raine/PERSON ,/O who/O lives/O with/O his/O partner/O Linda/PERSON Walker/PERSON ,/O said/O he/O had/O to/O call/O on/O neighbours/O to/O get/O the/O crate/O into/O his/O house/O after/O it/O was/O delivered/O and/O left/O on/O his/O doorstep/O ./O 
Ms/O Walker/PERSON said/O :/O ``/O A/O gentleman/O just/O knocked/O on/O the/O door/O and/O said/O he/O had/O a/O delivery/O ./O 
``/O Now/O we/O have/O a/O legal/O wrangle/O ,/O because/O we/O are/O not/O accepting/O this/O and/O as/O far/O as/O we/O are/O concerned/O Mr/O Lee/PERSON has/O not/O honoured/O his/O agreement/O ./O ''/O 
Mr/O Raine/PERSON said/O he/O had/O contacted/O his/O solicitor/O to/O try/O to/O resolve/O the/O matter/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O Royal/O Mint/O the/O following/O amounts/O of/O coins/O are/O legal/O tender/O in/O Britain/LOCATION for/O single/O transactions/O :/O 20p/O for/O any/O amount/O not/O exceeding/O 10/O ;/O 10p/O for/O any/O amount/O not/O exceeding/O 5/O ;/O 5p/O for/O any/O amount/O not/O exceeding/O 5/O ;/O 2p/O for/O any/O amount/O not/O exceeding/O 20p/O ;/O and/O 1p/O for/O any/O amount/O not/O exceeding/O 20p/O ./O 
Mr/O Lee/PERSON has/O made/O no/O comment/O on/O the/O matter/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Penny/O payment/O settles/O the/O pounds/O A/O restaurant/O owner/O -/O who/O was/O served/O up/O 18,000/O pennies/O in/O payment/O of/O a/O disputed/O bill/O -/O has/O said/O he/O will/O give/O the/O money/O to/O charity/O ./O 
Vincenzo/PERSON Arceri/PERSON ,/O who/O runs/O Emilio/PERSON 's/O Restaurant/O in/O Durham/LOCATION ,/O said/O he/O was/O forced/O to/O call/O the/O police/O after/O waiting/O two/O months/O for/O the/O party/O of/O eight/O diners/O to/O pay/O their/O 180/O bill/O ./O 
When/O they/O eventually/O agreed/O to/O pay/O ,/O he/O was/O escorted/O to/O their/O place/O of/O work/O to/O be/O confronted/O with/O a/O large/O bucket/O filled/O with/O 1p/O pieces/O ./O 
Mr/O Arceri/PERSON said/O he/O did/O not/O want/O to/O give/O them/O the/O satisfaction/O of/O not/O taking/O the/O money/O -/O despite/O not/O being/O legally/O obliged/O to/O do/O so/O ./O 
He/O said/O he/O planned/O to/O give/O the/O money/O away/O ./O 
I/O could/O see/O the/O snigger/O on/O their/O faces/O and/O I/O decided/O they/O were/O n't/O going/O to/O get/O the/O best/O of/O me/O Vincenzo/PERSON Arceri/PERSON Mr/PERSON Arceri/PERSON said/O :/O ``/O We/O went/O to/O the/O offices/O ,/O up/O two/O flights/O of/O stairs/O ,/O they/O sat/O us/O down/O and/O said/O `/O there/O you/O go/O ,/O there/O is/O your/O money/O '/O ./O ''/O 
``/O It/O was/O 180/O he/O owed/O us/O ,/O and/O gave/O it/O to/O us/O in/O pennies/O in/O a/O bucket/O ./O 
``/O The/O bucket/O must/O have/O weighed/O 80-90/O kilos/O ./O 
There/O was/O no/O way/O I/O could/O pick/O it/O up/O ./O 
``/O I/O could/O see/O the/O snigger/O on/O their/O faces/O and/O I/O decided/O they/O were/O n't/O going/O to/O get/O the/O best/O of/O me/O ./O 
``/O We/O accepted/O the/O money/O and/O we/O are/O going/O to/O donate/O it/O to/O a/O local/O children/O 's/O charity/O ./O 
``/O It/O was/O n't/O so/O much/O the/O 180/O itself/O ,/O it/O was/O the/O principle/O of/O it/O ./O ''/O 
`/O Largest/O sum/O '/O Brian/PERSON Capon/PERSON ,/O from/O the/O British/ORGANIZATION Bankers/ORGANIZATION Association/ORGANIZATION ,/O said/O Mr/O Arceri/PERSON could/O have/O refused/O to/O accept/O the/O coppers/O ./O 
He/O said/O :/O ``/O If/O both/O parties/O agree/O to/O accept/O payment/O in/O that/O way/O there/O is/O nothing/O stopping/O them/O ,/O but/O the/O maximum/O amount/O of/O bronze/O that/O should/O n't/O be/O refused/O by/O a/O creditor/O in/O payment/O of/O a/O debt/O is/O actually/O only/O 20p/O ./O 
``/O A/O person/O only/O has/O to/O accept/O that/O amount/O .../O they/O could/O turn/O around/O and/O refuse/O to/O accept/O more/O than/O 20p/O in/O coppers/O ./O 
``/O It/O is/O the/O largest/O sum/O -LSB-/O paid/O in/O pennies/O -RSB-/O I/O have/O heard/O of/O ,/O but/O I/O 'm/O sure/O I/O will/O have/O telephone/O calls/O to/O tell/O me/O otherwise/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Council/ORGANIZATION rejects/O pennies/O '/O payment/O A/O wheel/O clamper/O who/O tried/O to/O pay/O a/O 1,300/O fine/O using/O pennies/O in/O a/O shopping/O trolley/O has/O had/O his/O payment/O refused/O ./O 
Gary/PERSON Southall/PERSON ,/O 48/O ,/O of/O Digbeth/LOCATION ,/O had/O the/O trolley/O containing/O 461kg/O -LRB-/O 0.508/O tons/O -RRB-/O of/O pennies/O delivered/O to/O trading/O standards/O at/O Birmingham/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION ./O 
He/O was/O ordered/O to/O pay/O the/O court/O fine/O after/O clamping/O vehicles/O without/O providing/O his/O business/O contact/O details/O on/O receipts/O to/O motorists/O ./O 
The/O council/O said/O rules/O meant/O pennies/O could/O only/O settle/O debts/O up/O to/O 20p/O ./O 
`/O Bank/O charges/O '/O Chris/PERSON Neville/PERSON ,/O the/O city/O 's/O head/O of/O trading/O standards/O ,/O said/O :/O ``/O I/O can/O see/O a/O humorous/O side/O to/O it/O in/O a/O sense/O ,/O but/O it/O also/O illustrates/O to/O me/O the/O contempt/O he/O has/O got/O for/O authority/O ./O 
``/O He/O 's/O cocking/O a/O snook/O at/O authority/O -/O if/O he/O had/O any/O respect/O he/O would/O just/O pay/O in/O the/O conventional/O way/O ./O ''/O 
Mr/O Southall/PERSON ,/O who/O has/O traded/O under/O the/O names/O National/ORGANIZATION Parking/ORGANIZATION Control/ORGANIZATION and/ORGANIZATION Nationwide/ORGANIZATION Parking/ORGANIZATION Control/ORGANIZATION ,/O was/O ordered/O to/O pay/O the/O council/O 1,300/O after/O action/O was/O taken/O under/O the/O Enterprise/O Act/O ./O 
Mr/O Neville/PERSON said/O rules/O governing/O the/O payment/O of/O debts/O stipulated/O pennies/O were/O only/O legal/O tender/O up/O to/O the/O value/O of/O 20p/O ./O 
He/O added/O :/O ``/O It/O would/O be/O a/O considerable/O inconvenience/O if/O we/O had/O to/O count/O 130,000/O pennies/O and/O the/O bank/O would/O charge/O us/O as/O well/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Court/O refuses/O man/O 's/O 4,000/O pennies/O A/O man/O who/O wants/O to/O pay/O ``/O every/O penny/O ''/O of/O his/O fine/O for/O careless/O driving/O in/O one/O penny/O pieces/O has/O been/O banned/O from/O paying/O the/O 40/O instalments/O in/O copper/O ./O 
Michael/PERSON Rees/PERSON ,/O 41/O ,/O of/O Tonteg/LOCATION ,/O south/O Wales/LOCATION ,/O was/O told/O the/O court/O did/O not/O have/O to/O accept/O the/O 4,000/O coins/O ./O 
He/O said/O his/O 2003/O conviction/O was/O a/O ``/O raw/O deal/O ''/O and/O that/O he/O was/O prepared/O to/O go/O to/O jail/O if/O he/O could/O not/O pay/O in/O coins/O ./O 
Rhondda/O magistrates/O said/O the/O Coinage/O Act/O of/O 1971/O meant/O the/O court/O did/O not/O have/O to/O take/O more/O than/O 20p/O in/O copper/O ./O 
Mr/O Rees/O ,/O was/O convicted/O of/O careless/O driving/O by/O Rhondda/O magistrates/O in/O 2003/O and/O was/O told/O to/O pay/O a/O 250/O fine/O ./O 
An/O unsuccessful/O appeal/O added/O 400/O costs/O ./O 
He/O has/O so/O far/O paid/O 540/O ,/O but/O only/O by/O going/O to/O a/O bank/O and/O changing/O his/O 40/O instalments/O into/O 4,000/O one/O penny/O pieces/O ./O 
It/O means/O staff/O have/O to/O spend/O two/O or/O three/O hours/O counting/O out/O pennies/O and/O bagging/O them/O Court/O clerk/O Steve/PERSON Miller/PERSON He/PERSON said/O :/O ``/O This/O is/O the/O way/O I/O feel/O ./O 
I/O could/O not/O prove/O my/O innocence/O ./O 
``/O I/O take/O all/O the/O pennies/O out/O of/O each/O individual/O bag/O ./O 
I/O rip/O the/O bags/O open/O and/O I/O empty/O them/O in/O a/O big/O sack/O so/O it/O gives/O them/O a/O job/O to/O count/O them/O ./O 
It/O 's/O funny/O to/O watch/O ./O 
``/O They/O are/O refusing/O to/O accept/O any/O more/O of/O my/O money/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
There/O is/O no/O such/O thing/O as/O the/O Coinage/O Act/O ./O 
It/O is/O legal/O tender/O ,/O it/O belongs/O to/O the/O Queen/O ./O 
``/O If/O I/O am/O not/O allowed/O to/O pay/O the/O pennies/O then/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O be/O in/O contempt/O of/O court/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O willing/O to/O go/O to/O prison/O for/O it/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O pay/O it/O the/O way/O I/O feel/O I/O should/O pay/O it/O ./O 
I/O 've/O been/O dealt/O a/O raw/O deal/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O unemployed/O and/O I/O 'm/O struggling/O to/O pay/O ./O ''/O 
`/O Aggrieved/O '/O The/O clerk/O to/O the/O Miskin/PERSON ,/O Cynon/LOCATION Valley/LOCATION and/O Merthyr/O Tydfil/O magistrates/O '/O courts/O ,/O Steve/PERSON Miller/PERSON ,/O defended/O the/O right/O not/O to/O accept/O the/O coppers/O as/O legal/O tender/O ./O 
He/O said/O :/O ``/O Mr/O Rees/PERSON is/O not/O unique/O ./O 
I/O have/O had/O a/O number/O of/O people/O who/O feel/O aggrieved/O about/O a/O financial/O penalty/O and/O try/O to/O pay/O the/O fines/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O It/O does/O happen/O every/O now/O and/O again/O ./O 
If/O someone/O is/O trying/O to/O make/O a/O point/O ,/O really/O I/O will/O always/O say/O no/O ./O 
``/O The/O reason/O we/O have/O always/O said/O no/O is/O it/O means/O staff/O have/O to/O spend/O two/O or/O three/O hours/O counting/O out/O pennies/O and/O bagging/O them/O ./O 
``/O Staff/O are/O employed/O to/O be/O doing/O different/O things/O from/O that/O ./O ''/O 
Mr/O Miller/PERSON said/O exceptions/O were/O made/O for/O ``/O genuine/O cases/O ''/O ./O 
A/O spokesman/O for/O HM/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION said/O :/O ``/O Anything/O over/O 20p/O in/O bronze/O is/O not/O legal/O tender/O ./O 
You/O do/O n't/O have/O to/O accept/O it/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Tesco/ORGANIZATION petrol/O station/O row/O over/O coin/O payment/O A/O man/O has/O criticised/O a/O petrol/O station/O in/O Devon/LOCATION for/O refusing/O to/O accept/O his/O payment/O in/O coins/O ./O 
Brett/PERSON Chamberlain/PERSON ,/O from/O Tiverton/LOCATION ,/O tried/O to/O pay/O at/O the/O town/O 's/O store/O with/O money/O he/O had/O found/O with/O his/O metal/O detector/O ./O 
Tesco/ORGANIZATION refused/O to/O accept/O the/O #/O 100/O worth/O of/O coins/O and/O said/O some/O were/O discoloured/O and/O foreign/O and/O it/O would/O have/O taken/O too/O long/O to/O search/O through/O the/O money/O ./O 
Staff/O called/O the/O police/O when/O Mr/O Chamberlain/PERSON declined/O to/O give/O them/O his/O name/O and/O address/O ./O 
No/O action/O was/O taken/O ./O 
Tarnished/O coins/O Mr/O Chamberlain/PERSON told/O BBC/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION :/O ``/O Police/O threatened/O to/O arrest/O me/O for/O trying/O to/O obtain/O goods/O by/O deception/O ,/O which/O is/O ridiculous/O ./O ''/O 
Devon/PERSON and/O Cornwall/ORGANIZATION Police/ORGANIZATION said/O no/O criminal/O offences/O were/O disclosed/O as/O it/O was/O purely/O a/O civil/O matter/O ./O 
``/O Start/O Quote/O It/O would/O have/O taken/O staff/O a/O long/O time/O to/O sort/O through/O the/O coins/O ''/O End/O Quote/O Tesco/ORGANIZATION statement/O Mr/O Chamberlain/PERSON said/O he/O repeatedly/O returned/O to/O the/O store/O to/O pay/O for/O the/O fuel/O ,/O but/O staff/O would/O not/O accept/O the/O coins/O ./O 
After/O multiple/O visits/O he/O said/O the/O supermarket/O chain/O accepted/O his/O payment/O with/O alternative/O coins/O ./O 
Since/O the/O incident/O he/O said/O the/O tarnished/O coins/O has/O been/O accepted/O by/O a/O self-service/O checkout/O at/O a/O Tesco/ORGANIZATION store/O ./O 
The/O fuel/O cost/O #/O 95/O ,/O and/O Mr/O Chamberlain/PERSON tried/O to/O pay/O for/O it/O with/O #/O 85/O in/O one/O pound/O coins/O ,/O and/O the/O remainder/O with/O other/O coins/O ./O 
In/O a/O statement/O ,/O the/O supermarket/O chain/O said/O :/O ``/O We/O do/O everything/O we/O can/O to/O help/O our/O customers/O ./O 
In/O this/O instance/O ,/O the/O customer/O attempted/O to/O pay/O with/O over/O #/O 100/O of/O coins/O ./O ''/O 
Tesco/ORGANIZATION added/O :/O ``/O It/O would/O have/O taken/O staff/O a/O long/O time/O to/O sort/O through/O the/O coins/O and/O it/O would/O have/O been/O unfair/O and/O inconvenient/O for/O other/O customers/O ./O ''/O 
Mr/O Chamberlain/PERSON said/O :/O ``/O I/O 'm/O not/O a/O thief/O ,/O I/O just/O wanted/O to/O pay/O for/O my/O diesel/O with/O my/O legal/O tender/O coins/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Bitter/O Boss/O Whose/O Nurse/O Left/O Over/O Long/O Hours/O Gives/O Her/O Final/O Wages/O In/O Mountain/O Of/O 2p/O Coins/O Genji/O Hsing/PERSON left/O her/O job/O at/O a/O clinic/O in/O Taiwan/LOCATION ,/O only/O to/O get/O her/O final/O wages/O in/O several/O huge/O plastic/O bags/O containing/O near-worthless/O currency/O ./O 
A/O bitter/O hospital/O boss/O whose/O nurse/O quit/O over/O her/O long/O hours/O paid/O her/O final/O month/O 's/O salary/O in/O coins/O worth/O 2p/O ./O 
Genji/PERSON Hsing/PERSON left/O her/O job/O at/O a/O clinic/O ,/O only/O to/O get/O her/O final/O wages/O in/O several/O huge/O plastic/O bags/O containing/O near-worthless/O currency/O ./O 
Hsing/PERSON ,/O 34/O ,/O was/O even/O told/O to/O count/O out/O the/O mountain/O of/O coins/O before/O she/O was/O allowed/O to/O take/O it/O home/O in/O Taiwan/LOCATION 's/O Taichung/LOCATION City/LOCATION ./O 
She/O said/O :/O '/O I/O had/O decided/O I/O wanted/O to/O leave/O because/O I/O was/O doing/O really/O long/O hours/O that/O I/O was/O n't/O rewarded/O for/O ,/O but/O I/O was/O really/O surprised/O by/O the/O hostile/O reaction/O I/O got/O and/O even/O more/O surprised/O at/O the/O way/O he/O decided/O to/O publicly/O humiliate/O me/O ./O '/O 
Bitter/O :/O The/O mountain/O of/O coins/O presented/O to/O Genji/O Hsing/O ./O 
-LRB-/O CEN/O -RRB-/O Bitter/O :/O The/O mountain/O of/O coins/O presented/O to/O Genji/O Hsing/O ./O 
-LRB-/O CEN/O -RRB-/O She/O said/O on/O her/O last/O day/O ,/O her/O boss/O turned/O up/O with/O sacks/O of/O coins/O under/O her/O desk/O in/O front/O of/O patients/O and/O other/O staff/O members/O at/O the/O clinic/O in/O western/O Taiwan/LOCATION 's/O Taichung/LOCATION City/LOCATION ./O 
Hsing/PERSON added/O :/O '/O I/O had/O to/O work/O out/O my/O notice/O and/O on/O my/O last/O day/O the/O boss/O at/O the/O clinic/O brought/O me/O my/O wages/O of/O 21,000/O NTD/O -LRB-/O #/O 454/O -RRB-/O in/O plastic/O bags/O filled/O with/O coins/O and/O dumped/O them/O on/O the/O table/O and/O floor/O ./O 
`/O He/O said/O I/O had/O to/O count/O the/O money/O right/O here/O and/O added/O he/O would/O sue/O me/O if/O I/O took/O even/O a/O penny/O more/O than/O I/O was/O entitled/O to/O ./O '/O 
The/O nurse/O began/O counting/O the/O scattered/O money/O in/O front/O of/O other/O nurses/O and/O patients/O and/O said/O she/O spent/O a/O total/O of/O four/O hours/O counting/O the/O money/O ./O 
Genji/PERSON Hsing/PERSON is/O considering/O demanding/O compensation/O for/O humiliation/O ./O 
-LRB-/O CEN/O -RRB-/O Genji/PERSON Hsing/PERSON is/O considering/O demanding/O compensation/O for/O humiliation/O ./O 
-LRB-/O CEN/O -RRB-/O She/O said/O she/O was/O even/O forced/O to/O continue/O counting/O it/O on/O the/O street/O in/O front/O of/O her/O boss/O after/O the/O clinic/O had/O closed/O ./O 
She/O added/O :/O '/O I/O felt/O humiliated/O and/O degraded/O in/O public/O and/O I/O 'm/O now/O taking/O legal/O advice/O to/O get/O compensation/O for/O the/O embarrassment/O I/O had/O to/O endure/O ./O '/O 
