By/O Gracie/PERSON Lee/PERSON ,/O Christian/ORGANIZATION Post/ORGANIZATION Contributor/O August/O 3/O ,/O 2013/O |/O 12:59/O am/O A/O man/O has/O paid/O a/O court/O ordered/O settlement/O in/O quarters/O --/O 600,000/O of/O them/O ./O 
A/O man/O has/O paid/O 0,000/O in/O quarters/O in/O protest/O of/O a/O court/O order/O ./O 
-LRB-/O Photo/O :/O CNN/ORGANIZATION Screen/ORGANIZATION Shot/ORGANIZATION -RRB-/O A/O man/O has/O paid/O 0,000/O in/O quarters/O in/O protest/O of/O a/O court/O order/O ./O 
Roger/PERSON Herrin/PERSON ,/O a/O retired/O foot/O surgeon/O ,/O nursing/O home/O owner/O and/O Southern/ORGANIZATION Illinois/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION trustee/O ,/O was/O ordered/O by/O an/O Illinois/LOCATION appeals/O court/O to/O share/O $/O 500,000/O from/O insurance/O with/O passengers/O who/O survived/O a/O car/O crash/O that/O killed/O his/O teenage/O son/O ./O 
Angered/O by/O the/O order/O ,/O Herrin/PERSON protested/O the/O settlement/O by/O paying/O $/O 150,000/O in/O quarters/O ./O 
The/O payment/O was/O made/O via/O 150/O bags/O filled/O with/O quarters/O that/O were/O said/O to/O have/O weighed/O 4/O tons/O ,/O according/O to/O The/O Southern/O newspaper/O ./O 
Herrin/PERSON ,/O of/O Harrisburg/LOCATION ,/O Ill./LOCATION ,/O told/O the/O paper/O ,/O ``/O It/O 's/O vehemently/O wrong/O in/O my/O view/O and/O nearly/O everybody/O else/O in/O the/O world/O ./O 
If/O and/O when/O someone/O loses/O a/O child/O ,/O it/O leaves/O a/O hole/O in/O your/O heart/O that/O is/O never/O repairable/O ./O ''/O 
The/O businessman/O 's/O 15/O year/O old/O son/O ,/O Michael/PERSON ,/O died/O in/O 2001/O when/O a/O farm/O truck/O failed/O to/O halt/O at/O a/O stop/O sign/O in/O southern/O Illinois/LOCATION ;/O it/O went/O on/O to/O broadside/O the/O Jeep/O Cherokee/O he/O was/O in/O ./O 
The/O crash/O killed/O Michael/PERSON ,/O and/O injured/O two/O friends/O and/O the/O driver/O ,/O who/O was/O the/O mother/O of/O one/O of/O the/O friends/O ./O 
The/O teens/O family/O was/O given/O $/O 1.65/O million/O in/O a/O settlement/O for/O a/O wrongful-death/O lawsuit/O with/O two/O insurance/O companies/O representing/O the/O truck/O driver/O ./O 
A/O court/O also/O awarded/O the/O Herrin/PERSON family/O $/O 500,000/O of/O an/O $/O 800,000/O pool/O for/O underinsured/O motorists/O for/O all/O passengers/O ./O 
However/O ,/O in/O January/O 2012/O ,/O an/O appeals/O court/O ruled/O that/O the/O original/O court/O had/O erred/O in/O awarding/O the/O family/O the/O money/O ,/O and/O gave/O a/O new/O order/O that/O the/O money/O should/O be/O redistributed/O to/O the/O injured/O passengers/O ./O 
Herrin/PERSON was/O given/O until/O Wednesday/O to/O comply/O with/O the/O court/O order/O or/O be/O held/O in/O contempt/O ./O 
However/O ,/O he/O did/O eventually/O deliver/O when/O an/O armored/O truck/O transported/O the/O huge/O batch/O of/O quarters/O from/O the/O Federal/ORGANIZATION Reserve/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION St./ORGANIZATION Louis/ORGANIZATION to/O a/O bank/O in/O Marion/LOCATION ,/O Ill./LOCATION ./O 
The/O bags/O of/O quarters/O were/O then/O transferred/O to/O other/O vehicles/O that/O took/O the/O money/O to/O the/O two/O law/O firms/O '/O offices/O that/O had/O represented/O the/O other/O injured/O clients/O in/O the/O case/O ./O 
The/O bags/O were/O dumped/O in/O the/O lobbies/O of/O their/O buildings/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Forbes/O Forbes/O </O //O >/O Taxes/O 9/05/2013/O @/O 2:31/O PM/O 12,942/O views/O Man/O Pays/O Tax/O Bill/O With/O Thousands/O Of/O Single/O Dollar/O Bills/O To/O Protest/O `/O Stolen/O '/O Money/O Nobody/O likes/O to/O pay/O taxes/O ./O 
Robert/PERSON Fernandes/PERSON ,/O of/O Forks/LOCATION Township/LOCATION ,/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION ,/O wants/O people/O to/O know/O exactly/O //O how/O much/O //O he/O does/O n't/O like/O paying/O his/O taxes/O ./O 
Last/O week/O ,/O the/O father/O of/O three/O took/O his/O wife/O and/O children/O --/O and/O $/O 7,143.54/O in/O cash/O --/O to/O the/O tax/O collector/O ./O 
He/O paid/O the/O township/O tax/O bill/O in/O single/O dollar/O bills/O ./O 
And/O ,/O just/O to/O make/O sure/O that/O he/O made/O his/O point/O ,/O he/O posted/O the/O whole/O thing/O on/O YouTube/ORGANIZATION :/O Fernandes/PERSON made/O his/O public/O statement/O to/O protest/O money/O that/O he/O claims/O is/O being/O ``/O stolen/O ''/O since/O he/O does/O not/O wish/O to/O ``/O voluntarily/O ''/O pay/O for/O services/O that/O he/O does/O n't/O believe/O he/O benefits/O his/O family/O ./O 
Specifically/O ,/O Fernandes/PERSON '/O young/O children/O -LRB-/O ages/O 1/O ,/O 4/O and/O 7/O -RRB-/O are/O not/O enrolled/O in/O a/O brick/O and/O mortar/O school/O in/O the/O school/O district/O :/O Fernandes/PERSON '/O wife/O is/O currently/O homeschooling/O the/O children/O ./O 
He/O said/O about/O the/O tax/O ,/O ``/O We/O do/O n't/O even/O use/O the/O public/O system/O ,/O yet/O I/O am/O being/O forced/O to/O pay/O all/O this/O money/O into/O a/O public/O school/O system/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O think/O that/O 's/O really/O either/O fair/O or/O just/O or/O even/O ethical/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O the/O equivalent/O if/O McDonald/LOCATION 's/LOCATION McDonald/LOCATION 's/LOCATION were/O to/O force/O vegetarians/O to/O pay/O for/O their/O cheeseburgers/O ./O ''/O 
Well/O ,/O er/O ,/O McDonald/ORGANIZATION 's/O //O would/O //O force/O vegetarians/O to/O pay/O for/O cheeseburgers/O if/O they/O opted/O to/O show/O up/O at/O the/O restaurant/O and/O order/O them/O --/O even/O if/O they/O did/O n't/O eat/O them/O ./O 
And/O that/O 's/O kind/O of/O what/O Fernandes/PERSON did/O ./O 
These/O property/O taxes/O did/O n't/O sneak/O up/O on/O him/O :/O he/O moved/O to/O the/O district/O last/O year/O in/O search/O of/O lower/O property/O taxes/O ./O 
That/O should/O mean/O that/O he/O did/O a/O little/O bit/O of/O research/O before/O putting/O in/O the/O offer/O for/O his/O home/O --/O at/O least/O enough/O to/O know/O the/O tax/O rates/O ./O 
And/O he/O did/O n't/O accidentally/O land/O in/O Forks/LOCATION Township/LOCATION :/O he/O voluntarily/O moved/O his/O entire/O family/O to/O the/O township/O after/O snatching/O up/O a/O house/O at/O a/O short/O sale/O ./O 
But/O that/O notwithstanding/O ,/O Fernandes/PERSON '/O claims/O that/O he/O does/O n't/O benefit/O from/O the/O school/O district/O ring/O a/O bit/O hollow/O ./O 
Under/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION law/O ,/O families/O who/O homeschool/O are/O still/O considered/O part/O of/O the/O school/O district/O where/O they/O live/O --/O in/O some/O districts/O ,/O home/O schooled/O children/O are/O allowed/O access/O to/O the/O schools/O for/O extracurricular/O programs/O like/O art/O ,/O music/O and/O sports/O ./O 
Even/O if/O students/O do/O n't/O take/O advantage/O of/O school-related/O activities/O ,/O they/O are/O still/O tied/O to/O the/O district/O :/O as/O part/O of/O Act/O 169/O -LRB-/O PA/ORGANIZATION 's/O homeschooling/O law/O parents/O must/O file/O an/O affidavit/O with/O the/O superintendent/O of/O the/O school/O district/O of/O residence/O at/O the/O beginning/O of/O the/O homeschooling/O period/O for/O evaluation/O purposes/O ./O 
Each/O year/O ,/O parents/O must/O submit/O each/O student/O 's/O portfolio/O of/O records/O and/O materials/O including/O log/O of/O instructional/O time/O ,/O standardized/O test/O results/O ,/O and/O annual/O written/O evaluation/O of/O educational/O progress/O -LRB-/O 24/O P.S./O 1-102/O -RRB-/O ;/O this/O is/O to/O ensure/O compliance/O with/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION 's/O compulsory/O attendance/O laws/O ./O 
In/O other/O words/O ,/O even/O if/O Fernandes/PERSON '/O children/O are/O n't/O physically/O present/O at/O a/O district/O school/O building/O ,/O they/O are/O still/O under/O the/O administrative/O oversight/O of/O the/O district/O --/O and/O that/O means/O there/O is/O work/O to/O be/O done/O on/O their/O behalf/O ./O 
Even/O if/O you/O do/O n't/O buy/O the/O argument/O that/O Fernandes/PERSON is/O benefiting/O from/O the/O direct/O services/O of/O the/O district/O ,/O it/O 's/O a/O tough/O argument/O to/O make/O that/O public/O education/O does/O n't/O benefit/O society/O ./O 
In/O fact/O ,/O one/O of/O our/O Founding/O Fathers/O ,/O Thomas/PERSON Jefferson/PERSON ,/O loudly/O championed/O the/O idea/O of/O a/O public/O school/O system/O paid/O for/O by/O tax/O dollars/O ./O 
Jefferson/PERSON felt/O that/O a/O well-educated/O population/O was/O the/O key/O to/O a/O successful/O democracy/O ,/O saying/O :/O -LSB-/O W/O -RSB-/O herever/O the/O people/O are/O well/O informed/O they/O can/O be/O trusted/O with/O their/O own/O government/O ;/O that/O whenever/O things/O get/O so/O far/O wrong/O as/O to/O attract/O their/O notice/O ,/O they/O may/O be/O relied/O on/O to/O set/O them/O to/O rights/O ./O 
And/O sure/O ,/O it/O costs/O money/O to/O provide/O public/O education/O ./O 
But/O what/O is/O the/O greater/O cost/O in/O not/O providing/O an/O education/O ?/O 
According/O to/O a/O study/O published/O in/O //O The/O New/ORGANIZATION York/ORGANIZATION Times/ORGANIZATION //O about/O one/O in/O every/O 10/O young/O male/O high/O school/O dropouts/O is/O in/O jail/O or/O juvenile/O detention/O ./O 
Factoring/O in/O lost/O tax/O revenues/O -LRB-/O since/O dropouts/O earn/O less/O than/O high/O school/O graduates/O -RRB-/O ,/O welfare/O payments/O -LRB-/O since/O dropouts/O are/O more/O likely/O to/O depend/O on/O public/O benefits/O -RRB-/O and/O other/O associated/O costs/O ,/O the/O estimated/O collective/O cost/O to/O taxpayers/O --/O those/O of/O us/O who/O have/O to/O make/O up/O the/O difference/O --/O is/O $/O 292,000/O over/O the/O working/O life/O of/O //O each/O //O high/O school/O dropout/O ./O 
By/O the/O numbers/O ,/O it/O costs/O more/O to/O have/O an/O uneducated/O population/O than/O an/O educated/O one/O ./O 
That/O said/O ,/O if/O ,/O like/O Fernandes/PERSON ,/O you/O believe/O that/O there/O is/O no/O benefit/O to/O you/O as/O a/O taxpayer/O from/O a/O public/O education/O system/O ,/O Fernandes/PERSON still/O got/O it/O wrong/O :/O protesting/O at/O the/O township/O level/O did/O n't/O make/O the/O right/O statement/O since/O the/O township/O does/O n't/O make/O the/O rules/O or/O set/O the/O school/O budget/O ./O 
Their/O job/O is/O simply/O to/O collect/O the/O tax/O ,/O as/O Forks/LOCATION Township/LOCATION tax/O collector/O ,/O Anne/PERSON Bennett-Morse/PERSON ,/O reminded/O him/O ./O 
Clearly/O ,/O however/O ,/O Fernandes/PERSON was/O in/O the/O mood/O to/O make/O Bennett-Morse/O do/O her/O job/O :/O when/O she/O asked/O Fernandes/PERSON if/O they/O could/O have/O the/O money/O counted/O at/O a/O bank/O ,/O Fernandes/PERSON balked/O ,/O saying/O ,/O ``/O They/O expect/O me/O to/O work/O hard/O for/O it/O and/O other/O people/O to/O work/O hard/O for/O their/O money/O ,/O but/O they/O ca/O n't/O even/O count/O it/O in/O the/O place/O that/O they/O collect/O it/O ./O ''/O 
Bennett-Morse/PERSON defended/O her/O question/O ,/O noting/O that/O she/O did/O not/O have/O a/O problem/O counting/O the/O bills/O but/O that/O she/O did/O not/O want/O to/O inconvenience/O other/O taxpayers/O ./O 
To/O put/O her/O burden/O into/O perspective/O ,/O if/O she/O counted/O $/O 1/O per/O second/O ,/O it/O would/O take/O her/O nearly/O two/O hours/O to/O count/O $/O 7,143/O in/O single/O bills/O --/O and/O that/O 's/O without/O a/O break/O ./O 
As/O for/O that/O ``/O visual/O ''/O that/O Fernandes/PERSON so/O desperately/O wants/O people/O to/O have/O ,/O here/O 's/O a/O quick/O summary/O of/O what/O Bennett-Morse/PERSON faced/O :/O according/O to/O the/O U.S./ORGANIZATION Treasury/ORGANIZATION a/O dollar/O bill/O is/O .0043/O inches/O thick/O and/O there/O are/O 490/O notes/O to/O a/O pound/O ,/O meaning/O that/O a/O stack/O of/O 7,143/O one/O dollar/O bills/O would/O be/O 30.7/O inches/O thick/O and/O weigh/O 14.6/O pounds/O ./O 
Fernandes/PERSON figures/O that/O if/O folks/O understood/O how/O much/O they/O were/O actually/O paying/O in/O taxes/O ,/O they/O would/O protest/O ,/O too/O ./O 
He/O believes/O that/O most/O taxpayers/O do/O n't/O know/O how/O much/O tax/O they/O 're/O actually/O paying/O since/O homeowners/O with/O mortgages/O tend/O to/O escrow/O their/O real/O estate/O and/O school/O taxes/O and/O pay/O monthly/O ;/O that/O sounds/O terribly/O patronizing/O ./O 
I/O would/O venture/O to/O say/O that/O most/O homeowners/O know/O more/O about/O the/O totals/O of/O their/O real/O estate/O and/O school/O taxes/O than/O they/O do/O about/O other/O hidden/O -LRB-/O or/O nearly/O hidden/O -RRB-/O taxes/O like/O sales/O taxes/O and/O excise/O taxes/O on/O utilities/O ,/O gas/O and/O alcohol/O ./O 
So/O what/O does/O Fernandes/PERSON hope/O to/O accomplish/O with/O his/O statement/O ?/O 
``/O I/O 'm/O hoping/O people/O see/O this/O video/O and/O do/O the/O same/O thing/O :/O stop/O paying/O in/O their/O escrow/O and/O mortgage/O and/O start/O paying/O taxes/O the/O way/O I/O did/O ./O ''/O 
I/O suspect/O ,/O however/O ,/O that/O tax/O collectors/O everywhere/O wish/O you/O would/O n't/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Monday/O ,/O September/O 09/O ,/O 2013/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION school/O tax/O protester/O pays/O $/O 7,143/O bill/O with/O $/O 1/O bills/O Somebody/O remind/O Robert/PERSON Fernandes/PERSON of/O Oliver/PERSON Wendell/PERSON Holmes/PERSON ,/O Jr./PERSON 's/O approach/O to/O taxes/O ./O 
The/O esteemed/O Supreme/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION Justice/ORGANIZATION famously/O said/O ,/O ``/O I/O like/O to/O pay/O taxes/O ./O 
With/O them/O I/O buy/O civilization/O ./O ''/O 
Fernandes/PERSON ,/O however/O ,/O wants/O to/O pick/O and/O choose/O which/O part/O of/O civilized/O society/O he/O wants/O to/O fund/O in/O his/O Forks/LOCATION Township/LOCATION ,/O Pa./LOCATION ,/O community/O ./O 
In/O this/O case/O ,/O the/O father/O of/O three/O is/O unhappy/O about/O having/O to/O financially/O support/O public/O schools/O ./O 
Fernandes/PERSON '/O kids/O are/O home/O schooled/O ,/O so/O he/O thinks/O he/O should/O n't/O have/O to/O pony/O up/O for/O educating/O other/O children/O whose/O parents/O depend/O on/O such/O educational/O opportunities/O ./O 
``/O We/O do/O n't/O even/O use/O the/O public/O system/O ,/O yet/O I/O am/O being/O forced/O to/O pay/O all/O this/O money/O into/O a/O public/O school/O system/O ,/O ''/O Fernandes/PERSON told/O LehighValleyLive.com/ORGANIZATION ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n't/O think/O that/O 's/O really/O either/O fair/O or/O just/O or/O even/O ethical/O ./O 
It/O would/O be/O the/O equivalent/O if/O McDonald/ORGANIZATION 's/O were/O to/O force/O vegetarians/O to/O pay/O for/O their/O cheeseburgers/O ./O ''/O 
To/O make/O sure/O his/O message/O got/O out/O ,/O Fernandes/PERSON had/O his/O property/O tax/O payment/O filmed/O and/O then/O posted/O it/O to/O YouTube/ORGANIZATION ./O 
He/O also/O made/O sure/O he/O was/O taped/O offering/O the/O shocked/O tax/O office/O staff/O donuts/O -LRB-/O not/O burgers/O -RRB-/O to/O underscore/O his/O assertion/O that/O he/O was/O n't/O there/O to/O make/O anyone/O 's/O life/O more/O difficult/O ./O 
*/O Taxes/O as/O societal/O insurance/O :/O */O Guess/O what/O ,/O Mr./O Fernandes/PERSON ,/O life/O is/O not/O fair/O ,/O tax/O or/O otherwise/O ./O 
And/O you/O are/O not/O the/O first/O to/O complain/O about/O what/O you/O perceive/O as/O unfair/O payments/O to/O a/O government/O ./O 
Get/O at/O the/O end/O of/O a/O very/O ,/O very/O long/O line/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O not/O saying/O you/O do/O n't/O have/O the/O right/O to/O complain/O ./O 
You/O definitely/O do/O ,/O even/O if/O it/O 's/O in/O a/O calculated/O ,/O over-the-top/O manner/O ./O 
But/O taxes/O ,/O like/O insurance/O policies/O ,/O are/O payments/O for/O things/O down/O the/O road/O ./O 
We/O want/O some/O of/O those/O services/O for/O which/O we/O pay/O ;/O some/O we/O pay/O for/O and/O hope/O to/O never/O need/O ./O 
Whatever/O happens/O ,/O we/O --/O and/O I/O 'm/O talking/O about/O the/O collective/O we/O of/O us/O who/O live/O and/O work/O side-by-side/O --/O need/O to/O pay/O for/O now/O ,/O just/O in/O case/O ./O 
When/O it/O comes/O to/O education/O ,/O the/O bulk/O of/O which/O is/O paid/O by/O real/O property/O owners/O in/O most/O states/O ,/O lots/O of/O folks/O feel/O like/O they/O 're/O getting/O the/O short/O end/O of/O the/O deal/O ./O 
Retirees/O who/O no/O longer/O have/O kids/O in/O public/O schools/O and/O folks/O ,/O like/O me/O ,/O who/O do/O n't/O have/O kids/O also/O are/O paying/O for/O services/O that/O we/O no/O longer/O or/O never/O used/O ./O 
But/O it/O 's/O called/O //O public/O //O education/O ./O 
It/O does/O in/O some/O way/O benefit/O us/O all/O ./O 
It/O 's/O part/O of/O the/O social/O compact/O ,/O the/O civilized/O society/O in/O which/O we/O all/O live/O ,/O where/O we/O pay/O for/O things/O that/O might/O not/O directly/O affect/O us/O ,/O but/O which/O definitely/O have/O an/O impact/O on/O our/O lives/O and/O their/O quality/O ./O 
*/O Paying/O it/O forward/O :/O */O Or/O as/O John/PERSON Green/PERSON explains/O in/O the/O photo/O that/O 's/O made/O the/O rounds/O on/O the/O Internet/O ,/O he/O happily/O pays/O his/O public/O school/O taxes/O because/O he/O does/O n't/O want/O to/O live/O in/O country/O with/O a/O bunch/O of/O stupid/O people/O ./O 
Our/O collective/O taxes/O pay/O for/O a/O lot/O of/O services/O we/O might/O not/O have/O used/O a/O lot/O .../O so/O far/O ./O 
But/O I/O 'm/O happy/O to/O have/O tax-supported/O police/O and/O fire/O departments/O even/O though/O I/O hope/O to/O never/O have/O to/O take/O advantage/O of/O what/O I/O 've/O paid/O for/O over/O the/O years/O ./O 
As/O for/O public/O school/O taxes/O ,/O I/O 'm/O counting/O on/O my/O money/O to/O ensure/O that/O today/O 's/O kids/O will/O turn/O out/O to/O be/O future/O doctors/O ,/O high/O tech/O experts/O ,/O cops/O ,/O firemen/O ,/O scientists/O ,/O business/O owners/O ,/O employees/O of/O those/O small/O and/O large/O companies/O and/O yes/O ,/O teachers/O ./O 
Quick/O question/O ,/O Mr./O Fernandes/PERSON ./O 
Did/O you/O and/or/O your/O wife/O go/O to/O public/O schools/O ?/O 
If/O so/O ,/O I/O 'm/O presuming/O that/O since/O you/O are/O making/O enough/O money/O to/O buy/O a/O house/O and/O show/O up/O with/O the/O cash/O to/O pay/O your/O tax/O bill/O that/O the/O system/O worked/O OK/O for/O you/O ./O 
One/O more/O query/O ./O 
Do/O your/O kids/O ever/O get/O out/O of/O the/O home/O for/O which/O you/O feel/O you/O are/O paying/O too/O much/O property/O tax/O and/O play/O with/O other/O youngsters/O who/O are/O going/O to/O public/O school/O ?/O 
I/O 'm/O sure/O ,/O to/O paraphrase/O John/PERSON Green/PERSON ,/O you/O do/O n't/O want/O your/O kids/O associating/O with/O and/O picking/O up/O bad/O habits/O from/O a/O bunch/O of/O stupid/O children/O ./O 
So/O in/O that/O regard/O ,/O you/O are/O getting/O something/O out/O of/O the/O public/O school/O system/O in/O the/O wider/O socialization/O of/O your/O youngsters/O ./O 
*/O Safeguarding/O and/O guiding/O our/O tax/O investments/O :/O */O All/O of/O us/O should/O demand/O that/O we/O get/O a/O good/O return/O on/O our/O tax/O dollars/O ./O 
That/O money/O ,/O whether/O it/O goes/O to/O schools/O or/O road/O repair/O and/O construction/O or/O public/O safety/O or/O myriad/O other/O local/O ,/O state/O and/O national/O programs/O ,/O is/O an/O investment/O ./O 
At/O least/O Fernandes/PERSON paid/O his/O taxes/O ,/O albeit/O with/O an/O ulterior/O ,/O attention/O seeking/O motive/O ./O 
If/O you/O 're/O really/O upset/O about/O your/O property/O tax/O amount/O ,/O appeal/O it/O It/O could/O be/O wrong/O ./O 
I/O also/O encourage/O Fernandes/PERSON and/O those/O who/O feel/O the/O same/O to/O do/O more/O than/O grouse/O and/O showboat/O ./O 
Vote/O ./O 
Run/O for/O the/O school/O board/O or/O city/O council/O ./O 
Show/O up/O for/O state/O and/O local/O sessions/O where/O taxes/O are/O being/O proposed/O and/O discussed/O ./O 
Be/O an/O engaged/O participant/O in/O our/O civilized/O society/O ./O 
That/O 's/O a/O life/O lesson/O we/O all/O need/O to/O heed/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O uses/O common/O cents/O to/O pay/O fine/O 10:15/O PM/O ,/O Sep./O 15/O ,/O 2013/O `/O Sovereign/O citizen/O '/O pays/O fines/O with/O 70,000/O pennies/O `/O Sovereign/O citizen/O '/O pays/O fines/O with/O 70,000/O pennies/O :/O Sovereign/O citizen/O James/PERSON Sanders/PERSON explains/O why/O is/O paying/O his/O $/O 702/O fine/O in/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION with/O all/O coins/O ./O 
Justin/PERSON L./PERSON Mack/PERSON Fourteen/PERSON months/O and/O about/O 70,000/O pennies/O later/O ,/O James/PERSON Sanders/PERSON has/O finally/O paid/O off/O a/O pair/O of/O citations/O he/O received/O last/O summer/O in/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION ./O 
After/O more/O than/O a/O year/O of/O unsuccessfully/O fighting/O the/O charges/O filed/O against/O him/O on/O Aug./O 10/O ,/O 2012/O ,/O for/O speeding/O and/O refusing/O to/O identify/O himself/O to/O police/O ,/O Sanders/PERSON made/O the/O trip/O from/O his/O Mulberry/O home/O to/O the/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION to/O pay/O his/O $/O 702/O fine/O ./O 
But/O the/O most/O difficult/O part/O of/O paying/O the/O fine/O was/O n't/O coping/O with/O the/O impact/O it/O might/O have/O on/O his/O budget/O ./O 
It/O was/O figuring/O out/O how/O to/O carry/O it/O from/O the/O car/O to/O the/O courthouse/O ./O 
.../O Man/O uses/O common/O cents/O to/O pay/O fine/O Fourteen/O months/O and/O about/O 70,000/O pennies/O later/O ,/O James/PERSON Sanders/PERSON has/O finally/O paid/O off/O a/O pair/O of/O citations/O he/O received/O last/O summer/O in/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION ./O 
unique_identifier/O `/O Sovereign/O citizen/O '/O pays/O fines/O with/O 70,000/O pennies/O Fourteen/O months/O and/O about/O 70,000/O pennies/O later/O ,/O James/PERSON Sanders/PERSON has/O finally/O paid/O off/O a/O pair/O of/O citations/O he/O received/O last/O summer/O in/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION ./O 
After/O more/O than/O a/O year/O of/O unsuccessfully/O fighting/O the/O charges/O filed/O against/O him/O on/O Aug./O 10/O ,/O 2012/O ,/O for/O speeding/O and/O refusing/O to/O identify/O himself/O to/O police/O ,/O Sanders/PERSON made/O the/O trip/O from/O his/O Mulberry/O home/O to/O the/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION to/O pay/O his/O $/O 702/O fine/O ./O 
But/O the/O most/O difficult/O part/O of/O paying/O the/O fine/O was/O n't/O coping/O with/O the/O impact/O it/O might/O have/O on/O his/O budget/O ./O 
It/O was/O figuring/O out/O how/O to/O carry/O it/O from/O the/O car/O to/O the/O courthouse/O ./O 
``/O As/O far/O as/O I/O 'm/O concerned/O ,/O they/O are/O stealing/O this/O money/O from/O me/O ,/O ''/O Sanders/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O If/O they/O want/O it/O ,/O this/O is/O how/O they/O are/O going/O to/O get/O it/O ./O ''/O 
Using/O only/O change/O -/O primarily/O pennies/O with/O a/O few/O quarters/O and/O nickels/O thrown/O in/O for/O good/O measure/O -/O Sanders/PERSON paid/O his/O fine/O with/O the/O goal/O of/O making/O the/O county/O officials/O ``/O work/O for/O it/O ./O ''/O 
This/O is/O n't/O the/O first/O time/O this/O year/O Sanders/PERSON has/O used/O change/O to/O pay/O off/O a/O ticket/O ./O 
On/O Feb./O 28/O ,/O he/O used/O a/O box/O full/O of/O dollar/O coins/O ,/O pennies/O and/O dimes/O to/O settle/O a/O $/O 153/O ticket/O in/O Tippecanoe/LOCATION County/LOCATION ./O 
He/O did/O the/O same/O thing/O a/O few/O months/O later/O in/O Jackson/LOCATION County/LOCATION ,/O paying/O off/O a/O ticket/O of/O about/O $/O 150/O ./O 
But/O last/O week/O 's/O payment/O was/O Sanders/PERSON '/O largest/O coin-only/O transaction/O to/O date/O ./O 
Using/O two/O large/O buckets/O and/O a/O utility/O dolly/O usually/O used/O for/O moving/O furniture/O ,/O Sanders/PERSON and/O a/O neighbor/O loaded/O up/O the/O coins/O and/O carted/O them/O into/O the/O courthouse/O ./O 
Sanders/PERSON '/O unusual/O way/O of/O handling/O tickets/O stems/O from/O the/O fact/O that/O he/O considers/O himself/O a/O ``/O sovereign/O man/O ''/O or/O a/O ``/O freeman/O ''/O -/O an/O ideology/O that/O asserts/O that/O American-born/O citizens/O answer/O only/O to/O independent/O authority/O and/O not/O the/O government/O ./O 
He/O began/O considering/O the/O way/O of/O life/O a/O few/O years/O back/O after/O his/O son/O received/O a/O speeding/O ticket/O ./O 
Common/O law/O is/O typically/O used/O to/O justify/O why/O sovereign/O citizens/O believe/O they/O are/O exempt/O from/O certain/O rules/O and/O regulations/O ./O 
Sanders/PERSON adds/O that/O he/O is/O not/O part/O of/O any/O larger/O sovereign/O citizen/O movement/O or/O group/O and/O does/O not/O support/O acts/O of/O violence/O ./O 
``/O I/O believe/O in/O obeying/O the/O law/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O make/O up/O my/O own/O laws/O ./O 
I/O read/O the/O law/O and/O I/O follow/O it/O ./O 
That/O 's/O it/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n't/O believe/O the/O code/O was/O written/O for/O me/O ,/O though/O ./O 
My/O main/O law/O is/O God/O 's/O law/O and/O I/O will/O always/O obey/O God/O 's/O law/O ./O 
And/O the/O only/O movement/O I/O belong/O to/O is/O the/O republic/O for/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION of/LOCATION America/LOCATION ./O 
That/O 's/O what/O I/O belong/O to/O ./O ''/O 
Clinton/ORGANIZATION County/ORGANIZATION Clerk/ORGANIZATION Sherri/ORGANIZATION Crews/ORGANIZATION declined/O to/O comment/O on/O the/O incident/O because/O she/O was/O away/O at/O a/O conference/O when/O Sanders/PERSON came/O in/O ./O 
Plus/O ,/O despite/O the/O manner/O of/O payment/O ,/O Sanders/PERSON '/O fine/O was/O like/O any/O other/O ./O 
In/O fact/O ,/O staff/O members/O in/O the/O courthouse/O Wednesday/O hardly/O flinched/O and/O remained/O professional/O when/O Sanders/PERSON stepped/O off/O the/O elevator/O and/O rolled/O his/O coins/O into/O the/O clerk/O 's/O office/O just/O 10/O minutes/O before/O they/O closed/O for/O the/O day/O ./O 
Once/O he/O was/O inside/O ,/O staff/O members/O explained/O that/O because/O they/O do/O not/O have/O the/O manpower/O to/O count/O the/O thousands/O of/O pennies/O ,/O they/O would/O accompany/O Sanders/PERSON to/O a/O nearby/O bank/O to/O have/O the/O coins/O counted/O and/O converted/O ./O 
That/O afternoon/O ,/O they/O went/O to/O Regions/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION and/O Farmers/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION ,/O but/O because/O of/O how/O late/O in/O the/O business/O day/O it/O was/O ,/O it/O was/O decided/O that/O Sanders/PERSON would/O return/O to/O the/O courthouse/O the/O next/O morning/O to/O handle/O the/O conversion/O ./O 
After/O a/O lot/O of/O talking/O ,/O counting/O and/O sorting/O early/O Thursday/O ,/O the/O coins/O became/O cash/O and/O Sanders/PERSON '/O fine/O was/O logged/O as/O paid/O in/O full/O ./O 
Sanders/PERSON said/O he/O had/O about/O $/O 690/O converted/O into/O dollar/O bills/O at/O his/O bank/O ,/O and/O the/O clerk/O 's/O office/O only/O took/O about/O $/O 10/O worth/O of/O loose/O change/O ./O 
In/O the/O end/O ,/O Sanders/PERSON may/O not/O have/O gotten/O the/O reaction/O he/O was/O looking/O for/O ,/O but/O he/O vows/O to/O continue/O to/O defend/O his/O way/O of/O life/O ./O 
``/O The/O last/O time/O in/O Jackson/LOCATION County/LOCATION I/O had/O five/O police/O officers/O show/O up/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O know/O why/O they/O showed/O up/O ./O 
And/O when/O I/O told/O them/O they/O had/O to/O accept/O it/O ,/O the/O clerk/O drove/O 30/O miles/O to/O pick/O it/O up/O ,/O ''/O Sanders/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O They/O 've/O caught/O on/O to/O it/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Posted/O :/O */O 16/O September/O ,/O 2013/O by/O Scoopla/ORGANIZATION Team/ORGANIZATION Man/ORGANIZATION Pays/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION Fines/ORGANIZATION Using/ORGANIZATION Coins/ORGANIZATION An/ORGANIZATION Adelaide/ORGANIZATION man/O has/O paid/O his/O council/O fine/O by/O going/O to/O the/O bank/O ,/O getting/O a/O bag/O of/O change/O and/O then/O handing/O it/O over/O to/O the/O city/O council/O worker/O ./O 
It/O happened/O on/O Friday/O when/O a/O man/O decided/O to/O get/O his/O revenge/O on/O the/O local/O council/O and/O pay/O his/O $/O 60/O parking/O fine/O -/O with/O 1200/O five/O cent/O coins/O !/O 
The/O council/O 's/O receptionist/O would/O n't/O have/O any/O of/O it/O ,/O and/O told/O the/O man/O that/O she/O could/O n't/O process/O the/O payment/O ./O 
And/O she/O 's/O quite/O right/O too/O ./O 
According/O to/O Australian/O law/O ,/O payments/O that/O are/O made/O with/O five/O cent/O coins/O can/O be/O refused/O for/O transactions/O greater/O than/O $/O 5/O ./O 
A/O spokesperson/O for/O the/O council/O told/O News/ORGANIZATION Limited/ORGANIZATION that/O the/O man/O still/O has/O to/O pay/O his/O outstanding/O bill/O ./O 
``/O We/O will/O be/O sending/O the/O customer/O a/O letter/O to/O communicate/O the/O fine/O remains/O outstanding/O and/O his/O money/O is/O being/O held/O in/O the/O safe/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O pays/O parking/O fine/O in/O 5/O cent/O coins/O Yahoo!/O 7/O September/O 16/O ,/O 2013/O ,/O 3:50/O pm/O Man/O pays/O parking/O fine/O in/O 5/O cent/O coins/O -/O Yahoo!/O 7/O A/O fed-up/O Adelaide/LOCATION man/O has/O attempted/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 60/O parking/O fine/O entirely/O in/O 5/O cent/O coins/O ./O 
The/O unidentified/O man/O used/O a/O hidden/O camera/O to/O film/O as/O he/O first/O visited/O a/O bank/O to/O withdraw/O the/O coins/O --/O all/O 1200/O of/O them/O --/O before/O visiting/O his/O local/O council/O to/O pay/O the/O fine/O ./O 
``/O Can/O I/O pay/O cash/O ?/O ''/O 
he/O asks/O the/O worker/O behind/O the/O desk/O ./O 
When/O she/O replied/O in/O the/O affirmative/O ,/O the/O dumped/O hundreds/O of/O coins/O on/O the/O desk/O and/O pushes/O them/O towards/O her/O ,/O before/O asking/O for/O a/O receipt/O ./O 
After/O some/O back/O and/O forth/O ,/O the/O woman/O informs/O the/O disgruntled/O ratepayer/O she/O ca/O n't/O possibly/O process/O a/O transaction/O using/O that/O many/O coins/O --/O and/O the/O law/O is/O on/O her/O side/O ./O 
The/O Reserve/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Australia/ORGANIZATION confirms/O there/O are/O limits/O to/O how/O much/O one/O person/O can/O pay/O for/O with/O coins/O ./O 
From/O the/O RBA/ORGANIZATION website/O :/O //O The/O RBA/ORGANIZATION states/O ``/O coins/O are/O legal/O tender/O for/O payment/O of/O amounts/O which/O are/O limited/O as/O follows/O :/O //O */O //O not/O exceeding/O 20c/O if/O 1c/O and/or/O 2c/O coins/O are/O offered/O -LRB-/O these/O coins/O have/O been/O withdrawn/O from/O circulation/O ,/O but/O are/O still/O legal/O tender/O -RRB-/O ;/O //O */O //O not/O exceeding/O $/O 5/O if/O any/O combination/O of/O 5c/O ,/O 10c/O ,/O 20c/O and/O 50c/O coins/O are/O offered/O ;/O and/O //O */O //O not/O exceeding/O 10/O times/O the/O face/O value/O of/O the/O coin/O if/O $/O 1/O or/O $/O 2/O coins/O are/O offered/O ./O 
//O ''/O //O For/O example/O ,/O if/O someone/O wants/O to/O pay/O a/O merchant/O with/O five/O cent/O coins/O ,/O they/O can/O only/O pay/O up/O to/O $/O 5/O worth/O of/O five/O cent/O coins/O and/O any/O more/O than/O that/O will/O not/O be/O considered/O legal/O tender/O ./O 
//O The/O man/O ,/O however/O ,/O was/O n't/O taking/O no/O for/O an/O answer/O ./O 
``/O You/O 're/O part/O of/O a/O corporation/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O deal/O with/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O as/O he/O left/O the/O building/O ./O 
``/O I/O paid/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O out/O ./O 
Bye/O ./O 
I/O gave/O you/O the/O money/O ./O ''/O 
An/O Adelaide/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION spokesperson/O today/O said/O the/O man/O will/O still/O need/O to/O pay/O his/O fine/O ,/O //ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION Corp/ORGANIZATION Australia/LOCATION //O reports/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Payback/O Time/O in/O Nickels/O and/O Dimes/O for/O Aussie/O Cited/O with/O a/O Parking/O Ticket/O Armed/O with/O a/O backpack/O filled/O with/O several/O hundred/O five/O and/O ten/O cent/O coins/O that/O he/O had/O just/O made/O at/O the/O bank/O along/O with/O a/O head-mounted/O camera/O filming/O his/O every/O move/O ,/O an/O Australian/O man/O set/O out/O to/O //O troll/O //O the/O Adelaide/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION for/O a/O parking/O fine/O he/O had/O previously/O received/O ./O 
The/O parking/O ticket/O was/O $/O 60/O ,/O which/O means/O the/O man/O had/O well/O over/O 600/O coins/O in/O his/O bag/O ,/O which/O he/O then/O laid/O out/O over/O the/O counter/O of/O a/O city/O council/O employee/O right/O after/O asking/O her/O if/O she/O accepts/O cash/O ,/O to/O which/O she/O had/O answered/O ``/O yes/O ''/O ./O 
However/O ,/O after/O seeing/O the/O number/O of/O coins/O ,/O the/O young/O woman/O was/O in/O no/O mood/O to/O count/O them/O and/O sent/O the/O man/O on/O his/O way/O .../O Take/O a/O look/O at/O the/O video/O and/O voice/O your/O thoughts/O on/O the/O incident/O below/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O This/O Is/O What/O Happens/O When/O You/O Try/O To/O Pay/O A/O Parking/O Fine/O In/O Loose/O Change/O -LSB-/O Video/O -RSB-/O Chris/PERSON Jager/PERSON 16/O September/O 2013/O 4:30/O PM/O Most/O of/O us/O have/O copped/O a/O parking/O fine/O at/O one/O point/O or/O another/O --/O whether/O guilty/O or/O innocent/O ,/O it/O usually/O leaves/O you/O simmering/O with/O impotent/O rage/O ./O 
One/O disgruntled/O Adelaide/LOCATION man/O has/O attempted/O to/O exact/O some/O petty/O revenge/O on/O his/O council/O by/O paying/O a/O parking/O fine/O in/O five/O and/O 10/O cent/O coins/O ./O 
He/O also/O recorded/O the/O entire/O incident/O on/O video/O .../O As/O you/O can/O see/O from/O the/O above/O footage/O ,/O things/O did/O n't/O really/O go/O according/O to/O plan/O for/O the/O shrapnel/O crusader/O ./O 
His/O payment/O was/O staunchly/O refused/O and/O no/O receipt/O was/O given/O --/O he/O basically/O threw/O away/O $/O 60/O and/O still/O has/O an/O unpaid/O fine/O on/O his/O record/O ./O 
A/O lot/O of/O the/O comments/O on/O the/O YouTube/O page/O claim/O that/O the/O council/O is/O being/O unlawful/O and/O that/O any/O Australian/O currency/O must/O be/O accepted/O ./O 
This/O is/O actually/O untrue/O ,/O however/O ./O 
In/O fact/O ,/O businesses/O are/O n't/O even/O obliged/O to/O accept/O Australian/O banknotes/O ,/O let/O alone/O loose/O change/O ./O 
Simply/O put/O ,/O refusing/O to/O accept/O a/O payment/O using/O legal/O tender/O status/O is/O not/O against/O the/O law/O ./O 
Here/O 's/O what/O the/O Reserve/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Australia/ORGANIZATION 's/O website/O has/O to/O say/O on/O the/O topic/O of/O using/O coins/O as/O legal/O tender/O :/O A/O payment/O of/O coins/O is/O a/O legal/O tender/O throughout/O Australia/LOCATION if/O it/O is/O made/O in/O Australian/O coins/O ,/O but/O this/O is/O subject/O to/O some/O restrictions/O about/O how/O much/O can/O be/O paid/O in/O coin/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O Currency/O Act/O 1965/O -LRB-/O section/O 16/O -RRB-/O coins/O are/O legal/O tender/O for/O payment/O of/O amounts/O which/O are/O limited/O as/O follows/O :/O */O not/O exceeding/O 20c/O if/O 1c/O and/or/O 2c/O coins/O are/O offered/O -LRB-/O these/O coins/O have/O been/O withdrawn/O from/O circulation/O ,/O but/O are/O still/O legal/O tender/O -RRB-/O ;/O */O not/O exceeding/O $/O 5/O if/O any/O combination/O of/O 5c/O ,/O 10c/O ,/O 20c/O and/O 50c/O coins/O are/O offered/O ;/O and/O */O not/O exceeding/O 10/O times/O the/O face/O value/O of/O the/O coin/O if/O $/O 1/O or/O $/O 2/O coins/O are/O offered/O ./O 
For/O example/O ,/O if/O someone/O wants/O to/O pay/O a/O merchant/O with/O five/O cent/O coins/O ,/O they/O can/O only/O pay/O up/O to/O $/O 5/O worth/O of/O five/O cent/O coins/O and/O any/O more/O than/O that/O will/O not/O be/O considered/O legal/O tender/O ./O 
On/O the/O other/O hand/O ,/O the/O RBA/ORGANIZATION notes/O that/O refusing/O to/O accept/O legal/O tender/O to/O pay/O off/O an/O existing/O debt/O can/O cause/O consequences/O in/O legal/O proceedings/O --/O especially/O if/O no/O other/O means/O of/O payment/settlement/O was/O specified/O in/O advance/O ./O 
The/O guy/O in/O the/O video/O could/O conceivably/O find/O a/O loophole/O here/O ,/O depending/O on/O how/O rigorous/O the/O council/O was/O in/O explaining/O his/O payment/O options/O ./O 
That/O said/O ,/O it/O 's/O extremely/O unlikely/O that/O a/O judge/O would/O rule/O in/O his/O favour/O given/O his/O obviously/O spiteful/O intentions/O ./O 
Plus/O ,/O if/O the/O video/O was/O secretly/O recorded/O -LRB-/O as/O appears/O to/O be/O the/O case/O -RRB-/O he/O could/O find/O himself/O in/O additional/O hot/O water/O due/O to/O Australian/O privacy/O laws/O The/O reality/O is/O that/O businesses/O and/O councils/O can/O set/O themselves/O up/O to/O accept/O whatever/O payment/O methods/O they/O desire/O ./O 
If/O you/O want/O to/O launch/O a/O hollow/O protest/O against/O your/O parking/O fine/O ,/O paying/O in/O silver/O coins/O is/O n't/O the/O way/O to/O go/O ./O 
------------------------------------------------------------------------/O unique_identifier/O Australian/O driver/O tries/O to/O pay/O parking/O ticket/O in/O small/O change/O Footage/O uploaded/O to/O YouTube/ORGANIZATION by/O an/O irate/O motorist/O from/O Adelaide/LOCATION shows/O the/O man/O enterting/O a/O council/O office/O and/O attempt/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 60/O fine/O in/O 1,200/O five/O cent/O coins/O ./O 
10:19/O AM/O BST/O 16/O Sep/O 2013/O An/O */O Australian/O */O driver/O hit/O with/O a/O $/O 60/O parking/O ticket/O tried/O to/O exact/O revenge/O against/O Adelaide/LOCATION council/O by/O paying/O for/O the/O fine/O with/O over/O 1,000/O five/O cent/O pieces/O ./O 
To/O the/O astonishment/O of/O two/O employees/O at/O the/O cashier/O 's/O desk/O ,/O the/O irate/O man/O pours/O a/O sack/O of/O coins/O onto/O the/O counter/O after/O asking/O ``/O cash/O alright/O ?/O ''/O 
The/O unidentifed/O man/O ,/O who/O filmed/O his/O escapade/O and/O */O uploaded/O it/O to/O YouTube/ORGANIZATION */O ,/O was/O told/O that/O the/O coins/O could/O not/O be/O accepted/O ,/O but/O left/O them/O on/O the/O counter/O and/O walked/O out/O saying/O ``/O I/O 'm/O paid/O ,/O I/O 'm/O out/O ./O ''/O 
A/O council/O spokesperson/O confirmed/O to/O Australian/O news/O website/O *news.com/O ./O 
au/O */O that/O the/O money/O could/O not/O be/O used/O to/O pay/O the/O fine/O and/O was/O being/O held/O in/O their/O safe/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Penny/O for/O them/O !/O 
`/O Sovereign/O citizen/O '/O pays/O fines/O with/O 70,000/O pennies/O Nobody/O likes/O getting/O fined/O -/O particularly/O when/O they/O feel/O they/O have/O done/O nothing/O wrong/O ./O 
And/O one/O man/O decided/O that/O if/O he/O was/O going/O to/O be/O punished/O with/O citations/O ,/O everyone/O else/O would/O suffer/O -/O by/O paying/O his/O tickets/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
James/PERSON Sanders/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O handed/O a/O pair/O of/O citations/O amounting/O to/O $/O 720/O for/O speeding/O and/O refusing/O to/O identify/O himself/O to/O police/O ,/O has/O paid/O off/O his/O two/O tickets/O -/O in/O 70,000/O pennies/O ./O 
The/O defiant/O man/O took/O his/O haul/O of/O pennies/O to/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION in/O Indiana/LOCATION The/O defiant/O man/O took/O his/O haul/O of/O pennies/O to/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION in/O Indiana/LOCATION The/O defiant/O motorist/O ,/O who/O claims/O to/O be/O a/O `/O sovereign/O citizen/O '/O -/O a/O movement/O which/O recognises/O common/O law/O and/O do/O not/O accept/O federal/O ,/O state/O or/O municipal/O law/O -/O had/O protested/O the/O charges/O since/O being/O handed/O them/O in/O August/O last/O year/O ./O 
`/O As/O far/O as/O I/O 'm/O concerned/O ,/O they/O are/O stealing/O this/O money/O from/O me/O ,/O ''/O Sanders/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O If/O they/O want/O it/O ,/O this/O is/O how/O they/O are/O going/O to/O get/O it/O ,/O '/O he/O told/O JC/O Online/O He/O used/O pennies/O ,/O quarters/O and/O nickels/O ,/O Sanders/PERSON hauled/O his/O fine/O in/O to/O Clinton/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION ,/O Indiana/LOCATION ,/O using/O buckets/O and/O a/O hand/O cart/O ./O 
His/O fine/O was/O taken/O to/O a/O nearby/O bank/O ,/O where/O it/O was/O counted/O and/O converted/O into/O cash/O ,10/O News/O reported/O ./O 
He/O said/O he/O did/O not/O believe/O he/O had/O committed/O a/O crime/O ,/O and/O wanted/O to/O make/O those/O who/O had/O fined/O him/O earn/O the/O financial/O penalty/O they/O had/O imposed/O on/O him/O ./O '/O 
I/O believe/O in/O obeying/O the/O law/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O make/O up/O my/O own/O laws/O ./O 
I/O read/O the/O law/O and/O I/O follow/O it/O ./O 
That/O 's/O it/O ,/O '/O he/O told/O 10/O News/O ./O 
Mr/O Sanders/PERSON is/O not/O the/O only/O citizen/O who/O has/O decided/O to/O seek/O revenge/O through/O unusual/O methods/O of/O paying/O ./O 
In/O 2011/O a/O Californian/O man/O took/O clearing/O his/O debts/O to/O a/O new/O level/O after/O he/O tried/O to/O clear/O a/O $/O 6,500/O debt/O with/O 650,000/O pennies/O ./O 
Thirry/PERSON Chahez/PERSON ,/O who/O runs/O a/O cake/O shop/O ,/O loaded/O the/O crates/O of/O coins/O in/O to/O the/O back/O of/O his/O van/O and/O drove/O to/O a/O local/O Chase/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION in/O an/O attempt/O to/O pay/O his/O credit/O card/O bill/O that/O was/O due/O on/O Monday/O ./O 
But/O despite/O his/O best/O efforts/O ,/O the/O bank/O refused/O to/O accept/O the/O payment/O and/O asked/O Mr/O Chahez/PERSON to/O package/O them/O into/O more/O manageable/O individual/O coin/O rolls/O ./O 
Accepting/O the/O request/O ,/O Mr/O Chahez/PERSON was/O shocked/O when/O the/O bank/O would/O not/O accept/O the/O re-packaged/O payment/O either/O ./O 
Eventually/O Mr/O Chahez/PERSON managed/O to/O deposit/O the/O money/O and/O pay/O off/O his/O debt/O after/O being/O sent/O to/O a/O branch/O with/O a/O bigger/O vault/O ./O 
Mr/O Chahez/PERSON says/O he/O undertook/O the/O drastic/O measure/O as/O he/O was/O upset/O with/O his/O bank/O over/O a/O refinance/O he/O could/O not/O get/O and/O other/O charges/O and/O fees/O on/O his/O credit/O card/O ./O 
And/O when/O one/O woman/O was/O faced/O with/O a/O court/O order/O to/O pay/O her/O ex-husband/O $/O 50.12/O as/O part/O of/O a/O divorce/O settlement/O ,/O she/O decided/O to/O settle/O her/O debts/O and/O punish/O her/O ex/O ./O 
The/O aggrieved/O spouse/O ,/O believed/O to/O be/O Nebraska/LOCATION ,/O paid/O up/O the/O money/O in/O pennies/O delivered/O in/O Tupperware/ORGANIZATION filled/O with/O rice/O and/O beans/O last/O month/O ./O 
She/O handed/O over/O forty/O seven/O dollars/O and/O twelve/O cents/O in/O pennies/O ,/O and/O the/O other/O three/O dollars/O paid/O for/O the/O containers/O that/O she/O used/O ,/O she/O wrote/O in/O an/O angry/O note/O to/O him/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Streets/O of/O Basel/LOCATION paved/O with/O gold/O :/O 15/O TONS/O of/O five/O cent/O coins/O are/O dumped/O on/O city/O 's/O streets/O as/O protesters/O demand/O a/O basic/O minimum/O income/O for/O every/O Swiss/O household/O By/O Anna/PERSON Edwards/PERSON Published/O :/O 08:32/O EST/O ,/O 4/O October/O 2013/O |/O Updated/O :/O 09:13/O EST/O ,/O 4/O October/O 2013/O For/O years/O it/O 's/O long/O been/O regarded/O as/O one/O of/O Europe/LOCATION 's/O richest/O countries/O ./O 
And/O judging/O by/O these/O photos/O ,/O they/O really/O have/O got/O money/O to/O throw/O about/O -/O and/O can/O even/O pave/O the/O streets/O with/O gold/O ./O 
But/O the/O cash/O so/O freely/O splashed/O was/O with/O five-centime/O pieces/O -/O and/O the/O reason/O behind/O the/O move/O was/O to/O demand/O a/O minimum/O income/O for/O Swiss/O households/O ./O 
Activists/O pile/O 8/O Mio/O five-centime/O pieces/O ,/O one/O for/O each/O citizen/O in/O Switzerland/LOCATION ,/O into/O a/O bank/O vault/O Activists/O pile/O 8/O Mio/O five-centime/O pieces/O ,/O one/O for/O each/O citizen/O in/O Switzerland/LOCATION ,/O into/O a/O bank/O vault/O Money/O to/O throw/O around/O :/O The/O controversial/O scheme/O was/O presented/O to/O parliament/O today/O Money/O to/O throw/O around/O :/O The/O controversial/O scheme/O was/O presented/O to/O parliament/O today/O As/O Europe/LOCATION continues/O to/O struggle/O with/O financial/O turbulence/O and/O unemployment/O ,/O activists/O in/O Switzerland/LOCATION have/O decided/O to/O take/O a/O stand/O and/O demand/O a/O basic/O income/O to/O each/O citizen/O on/O a/O monthly/O basis/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Denver/LOCATION and/O the/O West/O Man/O who/O protests/O with/O coins/O gets/O booted/O from/O courthouse/O */O By/O John/PERSON Fryar/PERSON */O //O Longmont/LOCATION Times-Call/O //O Posted/O :/O 12/26/2013/O 12:01:00/O AM/O MST/O A/O Boulder/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION security/O officer/O escorted/O Fairview/ORGANIZATION Estates/ORGANIZATION homeowner/O Todd/PERSON Hunter/PERSON out/O of/O the/O county/O treasurer/O 's/O office/O Monday/O afternoon/O after/O Hunter/PERSON tried/O to/O pay/O his/O $/O 8,190/O subdivision/O paving/O district/O assessment/O with/O a/O $/O 7,958.58/O check/O and/O $/O 231.42/O in/O assorted/O coins/O ./O 
On/O Tuesday/O ,/O Hunter/PERSON said/O he/O had/O deliberately/O decided/O to/O pay/O part/O of/O the/O total/O charge/O with/O ``/O a/O random/O selection/O of/O coins/O ''/O to/O protest/O the/O assessment/O Boulder/LOCATION County/LOCATION imposed/O on/O his/O property/O on/O Brockway/LOCATION Drive/LOCATION --/O and/O the/O lien/O the/O county/O had/O attached/O to/O that/O property/O until/O the/O assessment/O was/O paid/O in/O full/O ./O 
Hunter/PERSON said/O he/O did/O n't/O want/O to/O make/O a/O scene/O when/O he/O showed/O up/O at/O the/O treasurer/O 's/O office/O ,/O ``/O but/O I/O wanted/O to/O make/O a/O statement/O ''/O about/O his/O objections/O to/O Boulder/LOCATION County/LOCATION commissioners/O '/O new/O Subdivision/ORGANIZATION Paving/ORGANIZATION Local/ORGANIZATION Improvement/ORGANIZATION District/ORGANIZATION ./O 
County/O Treasurer/O Bob/PERSON Hullinghorst/PERSON ,/O however/O ,/O said/O Tuesday/O that/O Hunter/PERSON ``/O was/O obviously/O trying/O to/O make/O a/O disturbance/O in/O our/O office/O ''/O by/O showing/O up/O with/O ``/O a/O large/O number/O of/O coins/O that/O were/O unsorted/O ,/O in/O various/O denominations/O ,/O ''/O which/O the/O treasurer/O said/O he/O and/O his/O staff/O did/O n't/O have/O time/O to/O count/O themselves/O Monday/O in/O order/O to/O verify/O that/O they/O totaled/O $/O 231.42/O ./O 
``/O I/O did/O n't/O want/O to/O create/O a/O huge/O burden/O for/O the/O people/O who/O work/O there/O ,/O ''/O Hunter/PERSON said/O ./O 
Hunter/PERSON said/O he/O had/O called/O ahead/O of/O his/O visit/O and/O was/O told/O by/O a/O member/O of/O Hullinghorst/PERSON 's/O staff/O that/O the/O office/O would/O accept/O a/O cash/O payment/O ./O 
He/O said/O his/O bank/O had/O counted/O and/O sealed/O the/O $/O 231.42/O in/O coins/O in/O the/O bag/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O What/O a/O tightwad/O !/O 
Texas/LOCATION man/O JAILED/O after/O attempt/O to/O pay/O $/O 600/O tax/O bill/O with/O tightly/O folded/O dollar/O bills/O By/O Snejana/PERSON Farberov/PERSON For/O Dailymail.com/O Published/O :/O 12:35/O EST/O ,/O 4/O February/O 2015/O |/O Updated/O :/O 16:13/O EST/O ,/O 4/O February/O 2015/O A/O Texas/LOCATION man/O landed/O in/O jail/O after/O trying/O to/O pull/O a/O prank/O on/O tax/O collectors/O involving/O a/O stack/O of/O tightly/O folded/O dollar/O bills/O ./O 
Timothy/PERSON Norris/PERSON ,/O 27/O ,/O from/O Wichita/LOCATION Falls/LOCATION ,/O was/O arrested/O January/O 28/O after/O refusing/O to/O leave/O the/O county/O tax/O office/O while/O attempting/O to/O pay/O his/O property/O tax/O using/O several/O hundred/O extremely/O creased/O banknotes/O ./O 
An/O arrest/O affidavit/O indicates/O the/O smart-aleck/O debtor/O was/O asked/O by/O tax/O collector/O Tommy/PERSON Smyth/PERSON to/O leave/O the/O Wichita/LOCATION County/LOCATION building/O for/O disrupting/O the/O operations/O of/O the/O office/O ./O 
Tightfisted/O :/O Timothy/PERSON Norris/PERSON ,/O 27/O ,/O was/O arrested/O and/O charged/O with/O criminal/O trespass/O and/O resisting/O arrest/O after/O he/O brought/O 600/O tightly/O folded/O $/O 1/O banknotes/O to/O pay/O his/O property/O tax/O bill/O Tightfisted/O :/O Timothy/PERSON Norris/PERSON ,/O 27/O ,/O was/O arrested/O and/O charged/O with/O criminal/O trespass/O and/O resisting/O arrest/O after/O he/O brought/O 600/O tightly/O folded/O $/O 1/O banknotes/O to/O pay/O his/O property/O tax/O bill/O The/O incident/O took/O place/O at/O around/O 2pm/O at/O the/O Wichita/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION Annex/LOCATION on/O Scott/LOCATION Street/LOCATION ./O 
Norris/PERSON was/O attempting/O to/O pay/O his/O $/O 600/O tax/O bill/O using/O $/O 1/O bills/O folded/O so/O tightly/O it/O took/O personnel/O about/O six/O minutes/O to/O unfold/O each/O banknote/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O affidavit/O obtained/O by/O Times/ORGANIZATION Record/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION ./O 
The/O document/O states/O the/O situation/O turned/O physical/O when/O Norris/PERSON pulled/O away/O twice/O from/O a/O deputy/O who/O was/O attempting/O to/O place/O him/O in/O handcuffs/O ./O 
Money/O pit/O :/O The/O incident/O took/O place/O at/O around/O 2pm/O at/O the/O Wichita/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION Annex/LOCATION on/O Scott/LOCATION Street/LOCATION in/O Wichita/LOCATION Falls/LOCATION ,/O Texas/LOCATION Money/O pit/O :/O The/O incident/O took/O place/O at/O around/O 2pm/O at/O the/O Wichita/LOCATION County/LOCATION Courthouse/LOCATION Annex/LOCATION on/O Scott/LOCATION Street/LOCATION in/O Wichita/LOCATION Falls/LOCATION ,/O Texas/LOCATION He/O eventually/O was/O wrestled/O to/O the/O ground/O ,/O placed/O in/O custody/O and/O charged/O with/O criminal/O trespass/O and/O resisting/O arrest/O ./O 
Norris/PERSON was/O hauled/O of/O the/O jail/O and/O ordered/O held/O on/O $/O 500/O bail/O ./O 
As/O of/O Monday/O he/O was/O no/O longer/O being/O detained/O at/O the/O Wichita/LOCATION County/LOCATION jail/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Rangers/ORGANIZATION manager/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON paid/O a/O $/O 200/O fine/O with/O 20,000/O pennies/O By/O Mike/PERSON //O Axisa/O //O |/O Baseball/O Writer/O March/O 11/O ,/O 2014/O 3:41/O PM/O ET/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON had/O some/O fun/O with/O MLB/ORGANIZATION two/O years/O ago.Ron/O Washington/LOCATION had/O some/O fun/O with/O MLB/ORGANIZATION two/O years/O ago/O ./O 
-LRB-/O USATSI/ORGANIZATION -RRB-/O This/O is/O great/O ./O 
Two/O years/O ago/O ,/O Rangers/ORGANIZATION manager/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON was/O ejected/O from/O a/O spring/O training/O </O //O mlb/spring-training/O >/O game/O and/O fined/O $/O 200/O by/O MLB/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Third/O baseman/O Adrian/PERSON Beltre/PERSON got/O tossed/O and/O then/O Washington/LOCATION got/O run/O by/O the/O umpire/O after/O leaving/O the/O dugout/O to/O stand/O up/O for/O his/O player/O ./O 
How/O did/O Washington/LOCATION pay/O that/O relatively/O small/O fine/O ?/O 
He/O shipped/O a/O box/O of/O 20,000/O pennies/O to/O MLB/ORGANIZATION 's/O office/O in/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION ./O 
From/O Stefan/PERSON Stevenson/PERSON of/O the/O //O Fort/LOCATION Worth/LOCATION Star-Telegram/LOCATION //O I/O lost/O my/O mind/O ,/O Washington/LOCATION recalled/O ./O 
Beltre/PERSON was/O yelling/O from/O the/O dugout/O ,/O It/O was/O outside/O !/O '/O 
And/O the/O umpire/O threw/O him/O out/O of/O the/O game/O because/O he/O told/O Beltre/PERSON to/O stop/O and/O Beltre/PERSON did/O n't/O stop/O ./O 
And/O then/O I/O went/O out/O there/O and/O argued/O with/O him/O and/O I/O said/O something/O I/O should/O n't/O have/O said/O ./O 
.../O Washington/LOCATION responded/O by/O filling/O a/O box/O with/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O and/O mailing/O it/O to/O Bob/PERSON Watson/PERSON ,/O MLB/ORGANIZATION vice/O president/O in/O charge/O of/O discipline/O ./O 
Cost/O to/O mail/O it/O to/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION :/O About/O $/O 45/O ./O 
Watson/PERSON called/O after/O receiving/O the/O box/O ./O 
Watson/PERSON :/O And/O you/O just/O had/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O hanging/O around/O ?/O 
Washington/LOCATION :/O Yes/O ./O 
Bob/PERSON ,/O I/O did/O n't/O have/O my/O checkbook/O ./O 
I/O was/O n't/O trying/O to/O be/O funny/O ./O 
Now/O go/O to/O the/O bank/O and/O put/O that/O in/O the/O -LSB-/O change/O -RSB-/O machine/O and/O get/O your/O $/O 200/O ./O 
One/O penny/O weighs/O 2.5/O grams/O ,/O so/O 20,000/O pennies/O weigh/O about/O 110/O pounds/O ./O 
That/O was/O a/O pretty/O heavy/O box/O ./O 
Hopefully/O Washington/LOCATION tipped/O his/O mailman/O well/O ./O 
Believe/O it/O or/O not/O ,/O you/O can/O be/O fined/O for/O paying/O bills/O with/O a/O large/O quantity/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
Where/O 's/O the/O fun/O in/O that/O ?/O 
unique_identifier/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON once/O paid/O a/O $/O 200/O MLB/ORGANIZATION fine/O with/O 20,000/O pennies/O By/O :/O Ted/PERSON Berg/PERSON March/O 11/O ,/O 2014/O 3:36/O pm/O ET/O So/O here/O 's/O something/O awesome/O :/O Texas/ORGANIZATION Rangers/ORGANIZATION manager/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON once/O paid/O a/O $/O 200/O fine/O from/O MLB/ORGANIZATION in/O 20,000/O pennies/O ./O 
The/O //O Fort-Worth/O Star/O Telegram/O //O has/O the/O details/O of/O how/O Washington/LOCATION paid/O the/O penalty/O levied/O for/O his/O arguing/O with/O an/O umpire/O in/O 2011/O spring-training/O game/O :/O Washington/LOCATION responded/O by/O filling/O a/O box/O with/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O and/O mailing/O it/O to/O Bob/PERSON Watson/PERSON ,/O MLB/ORGANIZATION vice/O president/O in/O charge/O of/O discipline/O ./O 
Cost/O to/O mail/O it/O to/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION :/O About/O $/O 45/O ./O 
Watson/PERSON called/O after/O receiving/O the/O box/O ./O 
Watson/PERSON :/O ``/O And/O you/O just/O had/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O hanging/O around/O ?/O 
Washington/LOCATION :/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
Bob/PERSON ,/O I/O did/O n't/O have/O my/O checkbook/O ./O 
I/O was/O n't/O trying/O to/O be/O funny/O ./O 
Now/O go/O to/O the/O bank/O and/O put/O that/O in/O the/O -LSB-/O change/O -RSB-/O machine/O and/O get/O your/O $/O 200/O ./O ''/O 
It/O 's/O a/O good/O way/O to/O express/O silent/O disapproval/O over/O a/O fine/O ,/O and/O a/O great/O way/O to/O make/O sure/O the/O league/O thinks/O twice/O before/O it/O fines/O you/O again/O ./O 
Who/O wants/O to/O deal/O with/O pennies/O ?/O 
unique_identifier/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON paid/O a/O fine/O from/O MLB/ORGANIZATION with/O 20,000/O pennies/O Aaron/PERSON Gleeman/PERSON Mar/O 11/O ,/O 2014/O ,/O 3:15/O PM/O EST/O I/O love/O when/O old/O stories/O like/O this/O surface/O ./O 
A/O few/O years/O ago/O Rangers/ORGANIZATION third/O baseman/O Adrian/PERSON Beltre/PERSON and/O manager/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON were/O tossed/O out/O of/O a/O spring/O training/O game/O by/O an/O umpire/O and/O then/O .../O well/O ,/O I/O 'll/O let/O Stefan/PERSON Stevenson/PERSON of/O the/O //O Forth/ORGANIZATION Worth/ORGANIZATION Star/ORGANIZATION Telegram/ORGANIZATION //O take/O it/O from/O here/O :/O However/O ,/O after/O the/O ejection/O Washington/LOCATION never/O left/O the/O dugout/O as/O required/O because/O the/O ballpark/O at/O Peoria/ORGANIZATION Sports/ORGANIZATION Complex/ORGANIZATION is/O n't/O exactly/O flush/O with/O great/O places/O for/O a/O manager/O to/O hang/O out/O if/O ejected/O ./O 
MLB/ORGANIZATION fined/O him/O double/O --/O $/O 200/O --/O for/O not/O leaving/O the/O dugout/O ./O 
Washington/LOCATION responded/O by/O filling/O a/O box/O with/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O and/O mailing/O it/O to/O Bob/PERSON Watson/PERSON ,/O MLB/ORGANIZATION vice/O president/O in/O charge/O of/O discipline/O ./O 
Cost/O to/O mail/O it/O to/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION :/O About/O $/O 45/O ./O 
Watson/PERSON called/O after/O receiving/O the/O box/O ./O 
Watson/PERSON :/O ``/O And/O you/O just/O had/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O hanging/O around/O ?/O 
Washington/LOCATION :/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
Bob/PERSON ,/O I/O did/O n't/O have/O my/O checkbook/O ./O 
I/O was/O n't/O trying/O to/O be/O funny/O ./O 
Now/O go/O to/O the/O bank/O and/O put/O that/O in/O the/O -LSB-/O change/O -RSB-/O machine/O and/O get/O your/O $/O 200/O ./O ''/O 
There/O 's/O actually/O a/O website/O called/O PayWithPennies.com/O that/O 's/O devoted/O to/O ``/O culture/O jamming/O involving/O large/O payments/O in/O pennies/O to/O organizations/O that/O are/O difficult/O to/O deal/O with/O ./O ''/O 
Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON :/O Culture/O Jammer/PERSON ./O 
Also/O ,/O apparently/O you/O can/O be/O arrested/O for/O trying/O to/O pay/O for/O something/O with/O a/O huge/O amount/O of/O pennies/O ,/O although/O it/O 's/O mostly/O about/O dumping/O them/O on/O a/O counter/O or/O otherwise/O making/O things/O annoying/O for/O the/O person/O being/O paid/O ./O 
Washington/LOCATION sent/O them/O in/O a/O nice/O box/O and/O even/O paid/O $/O 45/O extra/O to/O get/O it/O to/O MLB/ORGANIZATION ,/O so/O he/O 's/O probably/O in/O the/O clear/O there/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Rangers/O spring/O break/O :/O 20,000/O pennies/O for/O your/O thoughts/O By/O Stefan/PERSON Stevenson/PERSON -/O sstevenson@star-telegram.com/O 03/09/2014/O 12:49/O PM/O 11/12/2014/O 4:11/O PM/O Ron/ORGANIZATION Washington/ORGANIZATION Ron/ORGANIZATION Washington/ORGANIZATION Rangers/ORGANIZATION manager/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON argues/O with/O home/O plate/O umpire/O Todd/PERSON Tichenor/PERSON during/O a/O game/O last/O June/O ./O 
Washington/LOCATION sent/O the/O league/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O after/O being/O ejected/O in/O a/O spring/O training/O game/O in/O 2011/O ./O 
-LRB-/O AP/ORGANIZATION Photo/LM/ORGANIZATION Otero/ORGANIZATION -RRB-/ORGANIZATION Rangers/ORGANIZATION manager/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON argues/O with/O home/O plate/O umpire/O Todd/PERSON Tichenor/PERSON during/O a/O game/O last/O June/O ./O 
Washington/LOCATION sent/O the/O league/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O after/O being/O ejected/O in/O a/O spring/O training/O game/O in/O 2011/O ./O 
Texas/ORGANIZATION Rangers/ORGANIZATION manager/O Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON had/O a/O few/O words/O with/O the/O home/O plate/O umpire/O Saturday/O when/O Prince/O Fielder/O struck/O out/O looking/O ./O 
Washington/LOCATION was/O n't/O tossed/O ,/O but/O the/O moment/O recalled/O the/O time/O he/O was/O ejected/O during/O a/O spring/O game/O and/O he/O protested/O the/O fine/O by/O sending/O MLB/ORGANIZATION 20,000/O pennies/O ./O 
During/O a/O game/O in/O March/O 2011/O ,/O Adrian/PERSON Beltre/PERSON had/O been/O thrown/O out/O and/O Washington/LOCATION quickly/O followed/O ./O 
``/O I/O lost/O my/O mind/O ,/O ''/O Washington/LOCATION recalled/O ./O 
``/O Beltre/PERSON was/O yelling/O from/O the/O dugout/O ,/O `/O It/O was/O outside/O !/O '/O 
And/O the/O umpire/O threw/O him/O out/O of/O the/O game/O because/O he/O told/O Beltre/PERSON to/O stop/O and/O Beltre/PERSON did/O n't/O stop/O ./O 
And/O then/O I/O went/O out/O there/O and/O argued/O with/O him/O and/O I/O said/O something/O I/O should/O n't/O have/O said/O ./O ''/O 
No/O big/O deal/O ,/O Washington/LOCATION said/O ./O 
However/O ,/O after/O the/O ejection/O Washington/LOCATION never/O left/O the/O dugout/O as/O required/O because/O the/O ballpark/O at/O Peoria/ORGANIZATION Sports/ORGANIZATION Complex/ORGANIZATION is/O n't/O exactly/O flush/O with/O great/O places/O for/O a/O manager/O to/O hang/O out/O if/O ejected/O ./O 
MLB/ORGANIZATION fined/O him/O double/O --/O $/O 200/O --/O for/O not/O leaving/O the/O dugout/O ./O 
Washington/LOCATION responded/O by/O filling/O a/O box/O with/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O and/O mailing/O it/O to/O Bob/PERSON Watson/PERSON ,/O MLB/ORGANIZATION vice/O president/O in/O charge/O of/O discipline/O ./O 
Cost/O to/O mail/O it/O to/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION :/O About/O $/O 45/O ./O 
Watson/PERSON called/O after/O receiving/O the/O box/O ./O 
Watson/PERSON :/O ``/O And/O you/O just/O had/O $/O 200/O in/O pennies/O hanging/O around/O ?/O 
Washington/LOCATION :/O ``/O Yes/O ./O 
Bob/PERSON ,/O I/O did/O n't/O have/O my/O checkbook/O ./O 
I/O was/O n't/O trying/O to/O be/O funny/O ./O 
Now/O go/O to/O the/O bank/O and/O put/O that/O in/O the/O -LSB-/O change/O -RSB-/O machine/O and/O get/O your/O $/O 200/O ./O ''/O 
Word/O from/O Wash/PERSON ``/O If/O he/O wants/O to/O throw/O Prince/O breaking/O balls/O because/O he/O 's/O sitting/O in/O the/O third/O hole/O ,/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O hang/O a/O lot/O of/O them/O and/O he/O 's/O going/O to/O bang/O a/O lot/O of/O them/O ./O 
So/O go/O ahead/O ./O 
You/O want/O to/O throw/O him/O changeups/O ?/O 
Go/O right/O ahead/O ./O 
Because/O he/O 's/O not/O going/O to/O chase/O them/O ./O 
Then/O what/O are/O you/O going/O to/O do/O ?/O ''/O 
--/PERSON Ron/PERSON Washington/PERSON on/O whether/O pitchers/O will/O challenge/O No./O 3/O hitter/O Prince/PERSON Fielder/PERSON with/O fastballs/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Town/O `/O changes/O '/O policy/O after/O woman/O pays/O bill/O with/O coins/O Officials/O came/O up/O with/O the/O policy/O after/O a/O woman/O showed/O up/O March/O 20/O with/O a/O shoe/O box/O full/O of/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O quarters/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 200/O sewer/O bill/O Loading/O .../O Post/O to/O Facebook/ORGANIZATION Town/ORGANIZATION `/O changes/O '/O policy/O after/O woman/O pays/O bill/O with/O coins/O Officials/O came/O up/O with/O the/O policy/O after/O a/O woman/O showed/O up/O March/O 20/O with/O a/O shoe/O box/O full/O of/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O quarters/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 200/O sewer/O bill/O Check/O out/O this/O story/O on/O WKYC.com/O :/O Town/O `/O changes/O '/O policy/O after/O woman/O pays/O bill/O with/O coins/O Kim/PERSON Wendel/PERSON ,/O WKYC/O 4:21/O p.m./O EDT/O April/O 2/O ,/O 2014/O Officials/O came/O up/O with/O the/O policy/O after/O a/O woman/O showed/O up/O March/O 20/O with/O a/O shoe/O box/O full/O of/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O quarters/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 200/O sewer/O bill/O Money/O is/O money/O ,/O right/O ?/O 
Do/O n't/O a/O lot/O of/O you/O have/O jars/O or/O containers/O at/O home/O that/O you/O toss/O your/O coins/O into/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O day/O ?/O 
Well/O ,/O an/O Erie/LOCATION County/LOCATION township/O ``/O coined/O ''/O a/O new/O policy/O that/O wo/O n't/O let/O residents/O pay/O their/O sewer/O and/O water/O bills/O with/O all/O coins/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O //O Associated/ORGANIZATION Press/ORGANIZATION //O ,/O the/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION township/O is/O asking/O residents/O to/O keep/O the/O change/O ,/O to/O coin/O a/O phrase/O ./O 
Officials/O in/O Millcreek/LOCATION Township/LOCATION ,/O along/O with/O its/O water/O and/O sewer/O authorities/O ,/O have/O adopted/O a/O policy/O limiting/O how/O much/O change/O they/O 'll/O accept/O from/O residents/O paying/O sewer/O bills/O and/O other/O fees/O ./O 
The/O township/O 's/O slogan/O is/O ``/O Gateway/O to/O Presque/LOCATION Isle/LOCATION ''/O and/O it/O is/O just/O under/O 30/O square/O miles/O in/O size/O ./O 
This/O is/O not/O a/O four-employee/O type/O of/O small/O operation/O ./O 
Officials/O came/O up/O with/O the/O policy/O after/O a/O woman/O showed/O up/O March/O 20/O with/O a/O shoe/O box/O full/O of/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O quarters/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 200/O sewer/O bill/O ,/O according/O to/O AP/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Officials/O say/O she/O used/O a/O few/O bills/O but/O most/O of/O the/O payment/O was/O in/O change/O and/O it/O took/O four/O employees/O an/O hour/O to/O count/O ,/O sort/O and/O put/O the/O money/O into/O paper/O sleeves/O ./O 
The/O new/O policy/O limits/O residents/O to/O using/O $/O 10/O in/O unrolled/O coins/O or/O $/O 20/O in/O rolled/O coins/O when/O paying/O bills/O ./O 
And/O if/O any/O rolled/O coins/O are/O used/O ,/O the/O customer/O must/O be/O responsible/O for/O the/O rolls/O by/O placing/O his/O or/O her/O name/O and/O telephone/O number/O on/O each/O roll/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O you/O 've/O heard/O of/O people/O paying/O in/O pennies/O to/O protest/O a/O bill/O but/O such/O was/O not/O the/O case/O here/O ./O 
Really/O ?/O 
I/O know/O small/O townships/O do/O n't/O always/O have/O a/O large/O government/O structure/O but/O this/O particular/O township/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O U.S./ORGANIZATION Census/ORGANIZATION Bureau/ORGANIZATION ,/O has/O 53/O ,/O 796/O people/O and/O is/O the/O largest/O suburb/O of/O Erie/LOCATION ,/O Pa./LOCATION ./O 
It/O is/O is/O the/O ninth/O largest/O municipality/O in/O the/O state/O ,/O larger/O than/O Harrisburg/LOCATION and/O Altoona/LOCATION ./O 
So/O ,/O you/O would/O think/O that/O it/O had/O ample/O employees/O to/O handle/O the/O needs/O of/O its/O residents/O ,/O right/O ?/O 
So/O they/O had/O to/O count/O coins/O for/O an/O hour/O ./O 
Is/O that/O such/O a/O hardship/O ?/O 
The/O old/O mantra/O for/O struggling/O communities/O and/O businesses/O was/O ``/O do/O more/O with/O less/O ./O ''/O 
Apparently/O ,/O that/O does/O not/O hold/O true/O there/O ./O 
And/O if/O you/O look/O at/O it/O ,/O unless/O someone/O is/O protesting/O paying/O the/O bill/O and/O chooses/O to/O pay/O with/O all/O pennies/O or/O all/O coins/O ,/O how/O many/O people/O really/O would/O do/O this/O ?/O 
And/O another/O question/O --/O how/O many/O of/O us/O still/O keep/O shoe/O boxes/O lying/O around/O ?/O 
The/O township/O is/O run/O by/O three/O supervisors/O who/O serve/O six-year/O terms/O ./O 
Their/O names/O are/O Brian/PERSON McGrath/PERSON ,/O John/PERSON Groh/PERSON and/O Rick/PERSON Figaski/PERSON ,/O just/O in/O case/O you/O want/O to/O contact/O them/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Town/O Institutes/O Limits/O On/O Coin/O Payments/O After/O Woman/O Pays/O $/O 200/O Sewer/O Bill/O With/O Change/O By/O Mary/PERSON Beth/PERSON Quirk/PERSON April/PERSON 4/O ,/O 2014/O Shh/O ,/O you/O 're/O safe/O now/O ,/O pig/O ./O 
Shh/O ,/O you/O 're/O safe/O now/O ,/O pig/O ./O 
-LRB-/O yoshiffles/O -RRB-/O There/O is/O only/O one/O thing/O that/O happens/O when/O someone/O gets/O an/O affirmative/O reply/O to/O the/O question/O ,/O ``/O Do/O you/O accept/O change/O for/O payments/O ?/O ''/O 
You/O can/O be/O pretty/O darn/O sure/O the/O answer/O will/O be/O met/O with/O a/O whole/O lot/O of/O coins/O getting/O dumped/O on/O the/O counter/O ,/O something/O one/O town/O was/O n't/O ready/O to/O deal/O with/O when/O a/O resident/O paid/O her/O $/O 200/O sewer/O bill/O almost/O entirely/O in/O loose/O coins/O ./O 
The/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION town/O 's/O officials/O passed/O two/O separate/O measures/O recently/O in/O response/O to/O the/O woman/O 's/O nickel/O and/O dime/O extravaganza/O ,/O with/O both/O the/O water/O and/O sewer/O authorities/O limiting/O the/O amount/O of/O coins/O residents/O can/O use/O in/O the/O future/O to/O pay/O their/O bills/O ,/O reports/O the/O //O Erie-Times/O News/O //O Both/O boards/O '/O resolutions/O say/O they/O wo/O n't/O accept/O more/O than/O $/O 10/O in/O unrolled/O coins/O as/O payment/O ,/O and/O no/O more/O than/O $/O 20/O in/O rolled/O coins/O in/O sleeves/O per/O bill/O ./O 
Customers/O will/O also/O have/O to/O write/O their/O names/O and/O phone/O numbers/O on/O each/O roll/O as/O way/O of/O taking/O responsibility/O for/O them/O ./O 
It/O took/O four/O employees/O an/O hour/O to/O count/O up/O the/O woman/O 's/O loose/O change/O ,/O sort/O it/O and/O put/O it/O into/O sleeves/O to/O take/O to/O the/O bank/O ,/O the/O town/O 's/O executive/O director/O of/O the/O sewer/O and/O water/O authorities/O said/O ./O 
She/O used/O a/O few/O bills/O ,/O but/O mostly/O coins/O from/O a/O full/O shoebox/O she/O hoisted/O onto/O the/O counter/O ./O 
``/O They/O had/O never/O encountered/O a/O similar/O situation/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O asked/O the/O town/O 's/O supervisors/O to/O adopt/O similar/O rules/O so/O the/O entire/O town/O can/O be/O consistent/O and/O they/O did/O ,/O writing/O up/O a/O measure/O for/O paying/O various/O other/O fees/O ./O 
All/O over/O town/O ,/O piggy/O banks/O are/O sleeping/O a/O bit/O more/O soundly/O at/O night/O ./O 
Keep/O the/O change/O when/O paying/O Millcreek/LOCATION bills/O unique_identifier/O Oklahoma/LOCATION university/O senior/O makes/O final/O tuition/O payment/O in/O pennies/O A/O Southwestern/ORGANIZATION Christian/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION student/O paid/O for/O school/O once/O cent/O at/O a/O time/O ./O 
Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON rolled/O onto/O campus/O with/O 500/O pounds/O in/O copper/O coins/O ./O 
BY/O Deborah/PERSON Hastings/PERSON NEW/LOCATION YORK/LOCATION DAILY/O NEWS/O Friday/O ,/O April/O 18/O ,/O 2014/O ,/O 5:49/O PM/O Oklahoma/LOCATION university/O student/O Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON make/O his/O last/O tuition/O payment/O completely/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
KOCO/PERSON Oklahoma/PERSON university/O student/O Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON make/O his/O last/O tuition/O payment/O completely/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
</O #/O >/O It/O was/O a/O heavy/O load/O ,/O but/O Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON wanted/O tomake/O a/O point/O ./O 
To/O show/O how/O important/O it/O is/O to/O live/O debt-free/O ,/O the/O senior/O at/O Southwestern/ORGANIZATION Christian/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION in/O Oklahoma/LOCATION paid/O his/O final/O school/O bill/O in/O rolled/O up/O pennies/O ./O 
He/O wheeled/O nearly/O 100,000/O coins/O onto/O campus/O in/O neatly/O stacked/O boxes/O ,/O all/O to/O prove/O that/O saving/O every/O cent/O can/O really/O pay/O off/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O paying/O my/O last/O school/O payment/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
It/O kind/O of/O reminds/O me/O and/O will/O remind/O me/O in/O the/O future/O that/O every/O little/O penny/O counts/O ,/O ''/O he/O told/O KOTV/ORGANIZATION in/O Tulsa/LOCATION ./O 
Southwestern/ORGANIZATION Christian/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION senior/O Andrew/PERSON Magbe/PERSON rolled/O his/O last/O tuition/O payment/O into/O pennies/O ./O 
KOCO/ORGANIZATION Southwestern/ORGANIZATION Christian/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION senior/O Andrew/PERSON Magbe/PERSON rolled/O his/O last/O tuition/O payment/O into/O pennies/O ./O 
Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON delivered/O his/O final/O tuition/O payment/O in/O cardboard/O boxes/O full/O of/O rolled/O pennies/O ./O 
They/O weighed/O more/O than/O 500/O pounds/O ./O 
KOCO/PERSON Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON delivered/O his/O final/O tuition/O payment/O in/O cardboard/O boxes/O full/O of/O rolled/O pennies/O ./O 
They/O weighed/O more/O than/O 500/O pounds/O ./O 
Oklahoma/LOCATION collebe/O student/O Andrew/PERSON Magbe/PERSON made/O his/O last/O tuition/O payment/O completely/O in/O pennies/O to/O show/O the/O value/O of/O saving/O all/O of/O one/O 's/O pennies/O KOCO/ORGANIZATION Oklahoma/ORGANIZATION collebe/O student/O Andrew/PERSON Magbe/PERSON made/O his/O last/O tuition/O payment/O completely/O in/O pennies/O to/O show/O the/O value/O of/O saving/O all/O of/O one/O 's/O pennies/O */O Southwestern/ORGANIZATION Christian/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION senior/O rolled/O his/O last/O tuition/O payment/O into/O pennies/O ./O 
*/O Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON delivered/O his/O final/O tuition/O payment/O in/O cardboard/O boxes/O full/O of/O rolled/O pennies/O ./O 
They/O weighed/O more/O than/O 500/O pounds/O ./O 
*/O Oklahoma/LOCATION student/O made/O his/O last/O tuition/O payment/O completely/O in/O pennies/O ,/O to/O show/O the/O value/O of/O saving/O all/O one/O 's/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O very/O freeing/O ,/O knowing/O that/O you/O 've/O graduated/O without/O debt/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
He/O paid/O every/O dime/O of/O his/O entire/O college/O bill/O ,/O about/O $/O 25,000/O ,/O by/O working/O ./O 
Whether/O it/O was/O running/O errands/O ,/O mowing/O lawns/O or/O fixing/O window/O screens/O ,/O Magbee/PERSON said/O he/O saved/O every/O cent/O he/O could/O to/O pay/O for/O his/O education/O ./O 
He/O even/O saved/O enough/O to/O buy/O his/O own/O business/O ,/O a/O deli/O where/O ``/O I/O try/O to/O make/O the/O best/O sandwich/O I/O can/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Oklahoma/ORGANIZATION College/ORGANIZATION Student/O Pays/O Tuition/O In/O Pennies/O By/O Lisa/PERSON Monahan/PERSON ,/O News/O 9/O Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON said/O he/O collected/O 100,000/O pennies/O to/O deliver/O just/O before/O graduation/O ./O 
Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON said/O he/O collected/O 100,000/O pennies/O to/O deliver/O just/O before/O graduation/O ./O 
BETHANY/LOCATION ,/O Oklahoma/LOCATION -/O Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON is/O a/O senior/O at/O Southwestern/ORGANIZATION Christian/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION ./O 
His/O education/O is/O costing/O him/O about/O $/O 25,000/O but/O Magbee/PERSON is/O not/O only/O paying/O for/O the/O tuition/O himself/O ,/O he/O 's/O found/O a/O way/O to/O do/O it/O without/O racking/O up/O one/O penny/O in/O debt/O ./O 
``/O You/O can/O do/O anything/O you/O set/O your/O mind/O to/O ,/O that/O 's/O the/O exciting/O part/O ,/O ''/O said/O Magbee/PERSON ./O 
As/O a/O business/O major/O ,/O he/O has/O learned/O not/O to/O pass/O up/O a/O good/O opportunity/O ,/O especially/O when/O its/O right/O in/O front/O of/O him/O ./O 
``/O I/O 've/O always/O kept/O that/O in/O mind/O and/O I/O 've/O always/O been/O willing/O to/O do/O the/O dirtiest/O job/O out/O there/O ,/O to/O turn/O a/O dime/O ,/O ''/O Magbee/PERSON said/O he/O has/O turned/O a/O lot/O of/O dimes/O but/O he/O began/O pinching/O pennies/O long/O before/O college/O ./O 
In/O high/O school/O ,/O he/O collected/O loose/O change/O found/O on/O the/O ground/O ./O 
The/O coin/O jar/O is/O now/O worth/O approximately/O $/O 50/O ./O 
That/O savings/O inspired/O Magbee/PERSON to/O set/O an/O impressive/O and/O increasingly/O uncommon/O goal/O --/O get/O through/O college/O without/O incurring/O any/O debt/O ./O 
``/O I/O 've/O done/O just/O odds/O and/O ends/O jobs/O ,/O ''/O Magbee/PERSON said/O he/O 's/O already/O paid/O off/O half/O of/O his/O schooling/O through/O good/O old-fashioned/O hard/O work/O ./O 
He/O rescreened/O windows/O ,/O painted/O houses/O ,/O just/O anything/O and/O everything/O ./O 
On/O Thursday/O ,/O he/O was/O mowing/O ./O 
The/O mower/O has/O ,/O in/O a/O way/O ,/O pushed/O him/O ahead/O of/O most/O college/O students/O ./O 
At/O the/O age/O of/O 24/O ,/O Magbee/PERSON also/O owns/O his/O own/O business/O ,/O the/O First/ORGANIZATION Floor/ORGANIZATION Caf/ORGANIZATION near/O N.W./O 50th/O and/O Grand/O ./O 
``/O I/O try/O to/O make/O the/O best/O sandwich/O I/O can/O ,/O ''/O said/O Magbee/PERSON ./O 
Each/O sandwich/O ,/O each/O tip/O in/O the/O tip/O jar/O puts/O him/O a/O step/O closer/O to/O his/O goal/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O one/O thing/O at/O a/O time/O --/O its/O focusing/O on/O small/O goals/O to/O accomplish/O the/O big/O goal/O ,/O ''/O said/O Magbee/PERSON ./O 
The/O experience/O also/O motivated/O him/O to/O hand/O out/O some/O tips/O of/O his/O own/O ,/O to/O high/O school/O students/O overwhelmed/O by/O the/O thought/O of/O having/O to/O pay/O for/O college/O ./O 
``/O It/O can/O be/O done/O --/O you/O can/O pay/O your/O way/O through/O school/O ,/O if/O you/O work/O really/O hard/O ,/O ''/O Magbee/PERSON said/O to/O show/O how/O it/O can/O all/O add/O up/O he/O is/O toting/O 500/O pounds/O of/O pennies/O .../O carefully/O rolled/O .../O stacked/O .../O and/O ready/O for/O payment/O to/O the/O university/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O paying/O my/O last/O school/O payment/O with/O pennies/O ,/O it/O kind/O of/O reminds/O me/O and/O will/O remind/O me/O in/O the/O future/O that/O every/O little/O penny/O counts/O ,/O ''/O Magbee/PERSON said/O he/O collected/O 100,000/O pennies/O to/O deliver/O just/O before/O graduation/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O heavy/O load/O to/O carry/O --/O but/O a/O heavy/O burden/O lifted/O because/O Magbee/O know/O he/O wo/O n't/O be/O weighed/O down/O with/O debt/O in/O the/O future/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O very/O freeing/O ,/O knowing/O that/O you/O 've/O graduated/O without/O debt/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
Before/O getting/O his/O diploma/O debt-free/O in/O May/O ,/O he/O plans/O to/O help/O the/O university/O transport/O the/O pennies/O to/O a/O local/O bank/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Posted/O :/O 2:04/O p.m./O Monday/O ,/O April/O 21/O ,/O 2014/O Student/O pays/O tuition/O bill/O with/O pennies/O By/O Cox/ORGANIZATION Media/ORGANIZATION Group/ORGANIZATION Web/ORGANIZATION Staff/ORGANIZATION BETHANY/LOCATION ,/O Okla./LOCATION --/O A/O soon-to-be/O graduate/O from/O Oklahoma/LOCATION has/O not/O only/O pinched/O his/O pennies/O to/O get/O though/O college/O ,/O but/O is/O also/O paying/O his/O tuition/O with/O those/O same/O pennies/O ./O 
According/O to/O KVOA/ORGANIZATION ,/O Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON wheeled/O in/O 500/O pounds/O of/O pennies/O --/O 97,400/O of/O them/O --/O to/O pay/O his/O final/O tuition/O payment/O of/O $/O 974/O ./O 
Magbee/PERSON said/O he/O collected/O aluminum/O cans/O ,/O started/O a/O sandwich/O shop/O ,/O mowed/O lawns/O and/O painted/O houses/O ,/O WDAY/O New/ORGANIZATION York/ORGANIZATION Daily/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION reported/O the/O Southwestern/ORGANIZATION Christian/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION senior/O did/O it/O to/O prove/O that/O every/O penny/O counts/O ./O 
He/O paid/O his/O entire/O $/O 25,000/O tuition/O by/O working/O ,/O and/O graduated/O without/O debt/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Student/O pays/O tuition/O bill/O with/O pennies/O Posted/O ,/O 2014-04-21/O Palm/ORGANIZATION Beach/ORGANIZATION Post/ORGANIZATION A/O soon-to-be/O graduate/O from/O Oklahoma/LOCATION has/O not/O only/O pinched/O his/O pennies/O to/O get/O though/O college/O ,/O but/O is/O also/O paying/O his/O tuition/O with/O those/O same/O pennies/O ./O 
According/O to/O KVOA/ORGANIZATION ,/O Andrew/PERSON Magbee/PERSON wheeled/O in/O 500/O pounds/O of/O .../O unique_identifier/O UGA/ORGANIZATION student/O trying/O to/O pay/O fine/O with/O pennies/O arrested/O updated/O Wednesday/O ,/O April/O 30/O ,/O 2014/O -/O 8:57/O pm/O A/O University/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Georgia/ORGANIZATION student/O was/O arrested/O Tuesday/O afternoon/O after/O he/O argued/O with/O county/O downtown/O parking/O employees/O over/O using/O pennies/O to/O pay/O for/O a/O parking/O fine/O ,/O Athens-Clarke/LOCATION County/LOCATION police/O said/O ./O 
Jeremy/PERSON Ian/PERSON Sheftel/PERSON ,/O 23/O ,/O tried/O to/O pay/O the/O fine/O with/O unrolled/O pennies/O ,/O but/O the/O employees/O told/O him/O they/O had/O to/O be/O wrapped/O with/O his/O name/O and/O phone/O number/O on/O it/O in/O case/O the/O bank/O had/O problems/O with/O the/O count/O ,/O according/O to/O police/O ./O 
After/O the/O student/O demanded/O to/O be/O shown/O the/O policy/O of/O accepting/O only/O rolled/O coins/O ,/O the/O officer/O explained/O to/O him/O he/O would/O have/O to/O either/O wrap/O the/O pennies/O or/O find/O another/O method/O of/O payment/O ,/O police/O said/O ./O 
``/O I/O told/O him/O that/O the/O argument/O was/O over/O ,/O he/O knew/O his/O options/O ,/O ''/O the/O officer/O wrote/O in/O a/O police/O incident/O report/O ./O 
Sheftel/PERSON continued/O to/O make/O a/O scene/O and/O as/O he/O was/O leaving/O the/O office/O he/O left/O the/O pennies/O on/O a/O counter/O ,/O telling/O the/O county/O employees/O that/O ``/O they/O would/O be/O accepting/O his/O payment/O because/O he/O was/O n't/O taking/O it/O with/O him/O ,/O ''/O according/O to/O the/O report/O ./O 
The/O officer/O told/O the/O student/O several/O times/O to/O take/O his/O pennies/O ./O 
After/O he/O refused/O the/O officer/O demanded/O to/O see/O his/O identification/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O report/O ./O 
Sheftel/PERSON was/O arrested/O and/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O after/O his/O third/O refusal/O to/O show/O the/O officer/O ID/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O report/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O pays/O car/O in/O full/O with/O 5/O tons-worth/O of/O coins/O By/O -LRB-/O NBC/CCTV/O VIA/O APTN/O -RRB-/O Published/O :/O May/O 16/O ,/O 2014/O ,/O 9:01/O am/O Updated/O :/O May/O 16/O ,/O 2014/O ,/O 3:50/O pm/O LIAOCHENG/LOCATION ,/O China/LOCATION -LRB-/O NBC/ORGANIZATION //O CCTV/O VIA/O APTN/O -RRB-/O --/O A/O car/O salesman/O was/O astonished/O when/O a/O customer/O bought/O a/O car/O for/O $/O 16,000/O --/O and/O paid/O all/O in/O coins/O ./O 
The/O salesman/O in/O a/O car/O dealership/O in/O Shangdong/LOCATION Province/LOCATION said/O after/O he/O made/O the/O deal/O ,/O he/O asked/O the/O unidentified/O customer/O how/O he/O 'd/O like/O to/O pay/O ./O 
The/O customer/O said/O ,/O ``/O Cash/O ,/O ''/O and/O the/O salesman/O expected/O to/O receive/O 100,000/O Yuan/O in/O bills/O ,/O but/O the/O amount/O was/O paid/O in/O Yuan/LOCATION coins/O ./O 
He/O said/O the/O customer/O took/O a/O nap/O while/O the/O dealership/O staff/O counted/O the/O money/O ;/O he/O also/O watched/O a/O movie/O ./O 
Then/O ,/O the/O bank/O could/O only/O accept/O 2,000/O coins/O at/O a/O time/O ./O 
The/O total/O weight/O of/O the/O payment/O :/O 5/O tons/O ./O 
Eventually/O ,/O the/O dealer/O took/O half/O the/O amount/O in/O coins/O ,/O and/O the/O customer/O paid/O the/O rest/O by/O credit/O card/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Trevor/PERSON Vernon/PERSON presses/O on/O with/O court/O case/O Trevor/PERSON Vernon/PERSON presses/O on/O with/O court/O case/O Court/O ordered/O fine/O -LRB-/O Paid/O in/O coins/O -RRB-/O Tuesday/O ,/O May/O 27/O ,/O 2014/O ./O 
*/O AARON/PERSON HUMES/PERSON Reporting/O :/O */O Have/O you/O ever/O seen/O $/O 2,500/O --/O in/O ``/O shillings/O ?/O ''/O 
We/O did/O today/O ,/O as/O former/O litigant/O Trevor/PERSON Vernon/PERSON went/O to/O pay/O his/O court/O costs/O to/O his/O opponent/O Edmond/PERSON Castro/PERSON 's/O attorney/O ,/O Senior/O Counsel/O Denys/PERSON Barrow/PERSON ./O 
Vernon/PERSON and/O assistant/O Peter/PERSON Carter/PERSON logged/O in/O two/O large/O knapsacks/O containing/O 5,000/O 25-cent/O pieces/O amounting/O to/O $/O 1,250/O each/O for/O a/O total/O of/O $/O 2,500/O ,/O half/O the/O court/O costs/O owed/O ,/O which/O is/O $/O 5,000/O ./O 
Last/O week/O we/O reported/O on/O the/O striking/O out/O of/O an/O application/O by/O Vernon/PERSON against/O his/O area/O representative/O whom/O he/O wants/O to/O answer/O for/O the/O thousands/O collected/O on/O behalf/O of/O him/O and/O others/O from/O the/O Belize/ORGANIZATION Airports/ORGANIZATION Authority/ORGANIZATION and/O tried/O to/O bring/O a/O suit/O through/O the/O Supreme/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION alleging/O violations/O of/O the/O Code/O of/O Conduct/O in/O the/O Constitution/O ./O 
But/O Chief/O Justice/O Kenneth/PERSON Benjamin/PERSON said/O the/O wrong/O section/O of/O the/O Civil/O Procedure/O Rules/O was/O used/O ./O 
We/O asked/O Vernon/PERSON about/O the/O unusual/O method/O of/O payment/O ./O 
He/O says/O the/O money/O came/O from/O contributions/O from/O residents/O in/O Belize/LOCATION Rural/LOCATION North/LOCATION and/O a/O few/O outside/O ,/O even/O as/O far/O away/O as/O the/O U.S./LOCATION ./O 
They/O came/O in/O old/O coins/O ,/O new/O coins/O ,/O British/O pounds/O ,/O American/O dollars/O --/O and/O were/O all/O converted/O to/O the/O humble/O Belizean/O shilling/O ./O 
According/O to/O Vernon/PERSON ,/O he/O plans/O to/O pay/O the/O remainder/O next/O week/O ,/O though/O in/O paper/O money/O rather/O than/O coins/O ./O 
The/O bags/O were/O taken/O to/O the/O Central/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION to/O be/O counted/O ./O 
But/O that/O is/O not/O the/O end/O of/O it/O as/O Vernon/PERSON says/O he/O will/O be/O filing/O a/O new/O application/O ,/O using/O what/O he/O has/O learned/O from/O the/O first/O ./O 
Vernon/PERSON will/O keep/O Philip/PERSON Palacio/PERSON as/O his/O attorney/O ;/O no/O word/O ,/O however/O ,/O on/O how/O he/O 's/O paying/O him/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Workers/O get/O coins/O in/O wages/O dispute/O //O 2014-06-02/O 11:37/O //O //O //O chinadaily.com.cn/O //O //O //O //O Web/O Editor/O :/O Gu/PERSON Liping/PERSON //O //O Workers/O have/O been/O paid/O their/O salaries/O in/O over/O 50,000/O coins/O one/O month/O after/O they/O finished/O their/O project/O in/O Nanning/LOCATION city/LOCATION ,/O Guangxi/LOCATION Zhuang/LOCATION autonomous/O region/O ,/O Xinhua/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION Agency/ORGANIZATION reported/O on/O Sunday/O ./O 
A/O worker/O named/O Peng/PERSON and/O his/O fellow/O workers/O took/O on/O a/O decoration/O project/O for/O a/O shop/O in/O March/O and/O agreed/O they/O would/O not/O get/O their/O wages/O of/O roughly/O 52,000/O yuan/O until/O after/O they/O had/O finished/O ./O 
In/O the/O end/O ,/O they/O had/O to/O resort/O to/O local/O labor/O department/O for/O help/O ./O 
They/O finally/O received/O what/O they/O were/O owed/O on/O May/O 29/O ,/O but/O were/O given/O more/O than/O 50,000/O coins/O with/O a/O total/O weight/O of/O over/O 300/O kilograms/O ./O 
The/O employers/O admitted/O they/O were/O angry/O because/O the/O workers/O '/O behavior/O left/O a/O bad/O effect/O on/O the/O company/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Workers/O Get/O Paid/O 300KG/O of/O Coins/O after/O Wage/O Dispute/O //O Jun/O 03/O ,/O 2014/O //O */O By/O eChinacities.com/O */O Worker/O Fills/O Bosses/O Apartment/O with/O Over/O 1000/O Ducklings/O as/O `/O Revenge/O '/O Over/O Pay/O Dispute/O A/O passive/O aggressive/O employer/O decided/O to/O get/O the/O last/O laugh/O in/O a/O wage/O dispute/O with/O his/O employees/O ,/O by/O paying/O them/O their/O wages/O entirely/O in/O coins/O ./O 
Disgruntled/O workers/O in/O Nanning/LOCATION City/LOCATION ,/O Guangxi/LOCATION ,/O were/O told/O that/O they/O could/O n't/O receive/O their/O wages/O until/O the/O project/O was/O finished/O ./O 
They/O appealed/O to/O the/O local/O labor/O board/O ,/O and/O their/O employer/O was/O forced/O to/O pay/O up/O ./O 
However/O ,/O he/O was/O n't/O going/O to/O let/O it/O go/O that/O easily/O ,/O so/O he/O decided/O to/O pay/O them/O in/O the/O most/O annoying/O way/O possible/O :/O by/O paying/O them/O entirely/O in/O coins/O ./O 
The/O workers/O received/O more/O than/O 50,000/O coins/O ,/O totaling/O roughly/O 52,000/O RMB/O and/O weighing/O over/O 300/O kilograms/O ./O 
The/O employer/O admitted/O that/O they/O did/O it/O because/O they/O were/O `/O angry/O '/O at/O the/O workers/O '/O `/O bad/O attitudes/O '/O ./O 
*/O Keywords/O :/O */O Workers/O get/O paid/O in/O coins/O unique_identifier/O Sarah/PERSON LeVasseur/PERSON pays/O utility/O bill/O in/O coins/O as/O a/O protest/O Thursday/O ,/O July/O 31/O ,/O 2014/O 11:58/O AM/O Susan/PERSON LeVasseur/PERSON and/O Sarah/PERSON LeVasseur/PERSON rolls/O suitcases/O with/O coins/O to/O pay/O for/O a/O utility/O bill/O Thursday/O ,/O July/O 31/O ,/O at/O Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ,/O 301/O Washington/LOCATION Ave/LOCATION ,/O in/O Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION ./O 
Sarah/PERSON LeVasseur/PERSON is/O paying/O in/O this/O manner/O in/O protest/O of/O unusually/O high/O bill/O ./O 
-LRB-/O Yfat/PERSON Yossifor/PERSON |/O The/O Bay/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Times/ORGANIZATION -RRB-/O unique_identifier/O Insurance/O company/O pays/O elderly/O man/O 's/O settlement/O with/O $/O 21,000/O in/O change/O Southern/ORGANIZATION California-based/ORGANIZATION Adriana/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION paid/O a/O man/O with/O several/O buckets/O of/O loose/O change/O after/O he/O claimed/O in/O a/O lawsuit/O that/O one/O of/O their/O agents/O roughed/O him/O up/O ./O 
BY/O Philip/PERSON Caulfield/PERSON NEW/LOCATION YORK/LOCATION DAILY/O NEWS/O Wednesday/O ,/O August/O 6/O ,/O 2014/O ,/O 8:45/O AM/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 73/O ,/O received/O $/O 21,000/O in/O coins/O along/O with/O a/O check/O from/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O company/O ,/O which/O he/O sued/O after/O one/O of/O its/O agents/O allegedly/O assaulted/O him/O ./O 
knbc/O tv/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 73/O ,/O received/O $/O 21,000/O in/O coins/O along/O with/O a/O check/O from/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O company/O ,/O which/O he/O sued/O after/O one/O of/O its/O agents/O allegedly/O assaulted/O him/O ./O 
</O #/O >/O Goons/O from/O a/O crooked/O California/LOCATION insurance/O company/O allegedly/O assaulted/O an/O older/O man/O and/O ,/O after/O he/O successfully/O sued/O them/O ,/O paid/O the/O settlement/O with/O buckets/O of/O loose/O change/O ./O 
NBC/ORGANIZATION California/ORGANIZATION reports/O agents/O from/O Los/O Angeles-based/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O paid/O 73-year-old/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON the/O settlement/O with/O a/O check/O but/O also/O several/O five-gallon/O buckets/O brimming/O with/O $/O 21,000/O in/O coins/O ./O 
Carrasco/PERSON sued/O the/O company/O in/O 2012/O ,/O claiming/O one/O of/O the/O company/O 's/O agents/O assaulted/O him/O ./O 
The/O company/O agreed/O to/O settle/O in/O June/O ,/O and/O when/O it/O came/O time/O to/O pay/O up/O ,/O eight/O of/O the/O company/O 's/O workers/O visited/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O lawyer/O 's/O office/O in/O a/O van/O ,/O lugged/O the/O jugs/O of/O chump/O change/O into/O the/O waiting/O room/O and/O then/O split/O ,/O NBC/ORGANIZATION said/O ./O 
Carrasco/PERSON ,/O who/O recently/O had/O a/O hernia/O operation/O ,/O said/O the/O stunt/O left/O him/O feeling/O punked/O ./O 
``/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O ,/O is/O this/O the/O way/O you/O treat/O everyone/O ?/O ''/O 
he/O said/O in/O a/O statement/O ./O 
``/O Why/O do/O n't/O you/O like/O your/O clients/O ?/O ''/O 
``/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ,/O ''/O he/O added/O ./O 
The/O company/O has/O n't/O commented/O on/O the/O move/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Plaintiff/O paid/O in/O coins/O has/O serious/O need/O for/O wrappers/O Posted/O :/O August/O 6/O ,/O 2014/O Plaintiff/O paid/O in/O coins/O has/O serious/O need/O for/O wrappers/O An/O insurance/O company/O 's/O begrudging/O lawsuit/O payoff/O leaves/O an/O elderly/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION man/O with/O up/O to/O 17/O buckets/O of/O change/O ./O 
By/O ROBERT/PERSON JABLON/PERSON The/O Associated/ORGANIZATION Press/ORGANIZATION LOS/ORGANIZATION ANGELES/ORGANIZATION --/O An/O insurance/O company/O settled/O a/O lawsuit/O with/O a/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION man/O by/O dropping/O off/O buckets/O full/O of/O thousands/O of/O quarters/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O pennies/O ,/O his/O attorney/O said/O Wednesday/O ./O 
Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 76/O ,/O filed/O a/O lawsuit/O in/O 2012/O against/O Adriana/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Services/ORGANIZATION ,/O based/O in/O Rancho/LOCATION Cucamonga/LOCATION ./O 
Carrasco/PERSON alleged/O that/O during/O an/O argument/O over/O why/O the/O company/O had/O canceled/O his/O auto/O insurance/O ,/O an/O agent/O assaulted/O him/O by/O physically/O removing/O him/O from/O the/O office/O ./O 
Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON sits/O in/O his/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION office/O with/O buckets/O of/O change/O totaling/O more/O than/O $/O 20,000/O that/O he/O received/O as/O a/O partial/O settlement/O in/O his/O suit/O against/O an/O insurance/O company/O ./O 
Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON sits/O in/O his/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION office/O with/O buckets/O of/O change/O totaling/O more/O than/O $/O 20,000/O that/O he/O received/O as/O a/O partial/O settlement/O in/O his/O suit/O against/O an/O insurance/O company/O ./O 
The/O Associated/ORGANIZATION Press/ORGANIZATION The/O company/O reached/O a/O settlement/O in/O June/O and/O last/O week/O delivered/O partial/O payment/O in/O the/O form/O of/O a/O check/O ,/O but/O also/O tried/O to/O leave/O buckets/O of/O loose/O change/O in/O his/O lawyer/O 's/O East/LOCATION Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION office/O ,/O attorney/O Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON said/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON said/O he/O refused/O to/O accept/O the/O delivery/O because/O he/O could/O n't/O verify/O the/O amount/O in/O the/O buckets/O ./O 
But/O ,/O he/O said/O ,/O the/O cash/O was/O left/O the/O next/O day/O when/O he/O was/O at/O court/O ./O 
His/O assistant/O said/O eight/O people/O came/O in/O ``/O and/O just/O dropped/O it/O off/O in/O the/O lobby/O ,/O ''/O Gallo/PERSON said/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON ,/O who/O would/O n't/O disclose/O the/O settlement/O figure/O ,/O estimated/O there/O may/O be/O $/O 20,000/O or/O more/O in/O coins/O ./O 
``/O There/O 's/O maybe/O 17/O buckets/O of/O coins/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O They/O probably/O -LRB-/O each/O -RRB-/O weigh/O anywhere/O between/O 70/O to/O 100/O pounds/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O assuming/O ,/O because/O I/O ca/O n't/O lift/O them/O ./O ''/O 
One/O bucket/O is/O entirely/O full/O of/O pennies/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON said/O he/O did/O n't/O think/O the/O payment/O was/O illegal/O in/O California/LOCATION ,/O but/O it/O is/O rare/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O insulting/O to/O my/O client/O ./O 
He/O 's/O 76/O years/O old/O ,/O he/O just/O had/O a/O hernia/O operation/O ./O 
Come/O on/O ,/O ''/O Gallo/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O He/O feels/O that/O he/O was/O n't/O treated/O as/O a/O human/O being/O ./O ''/O 
``/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ,/O ''/O Carrasco/PERSON told/O KNBC-TV/ORGANIZATION ./O 
``/O We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ./O ''/O 
A/O call/O to/O the/O insurer/O 's/O attorney/O ,/O Edvin/PERSON Flores/PERSON ,/O was/O n't/O immediately/O returned/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON said/O he/O has/O been/O in/O contact/O with/O the/O company/O 's/O attorney/O and/O would/O like/O to/O see/O the/O insurer/O issue/O a/O check/O for/O the/O rest/O of/O the/O settlement/O and/O take/O away/O the/O coins/O by/O Friday/O ./O 
Otherwise/O ,/O he/O will/O have/O to/O hire/O someone/O to/O count/O the/O stash/O ./O 
``/O If/O the/O money/O 's/O short/O ,/O then/O we/O 'll/O probably/O go/O back/O into/O court/O ''/O to/O ask/O for/O the/O full/O amount/O ,/O along/O with/O the/O cost/O of/O counting/O the/O coins/O ``/O and/O hopefully/O some/O sanctions/O ,/O ''/O Gallo/PERSON said/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Vengeful/O insurance/O company/O pays/O $/O 21K/O claim/O in/O loose/O change/O By/O Natalie/PERSON O'Neill/PERSON August/O 6/O ,/O 2014/O |/O 10:27/O am/O They/O added/O insult/O to/O injury/O !/O 
An/O insurance/O company/O in/O California/LOCATION paid/O a/O senior/O citizen/O $/O 21,000/O in/O loose/O change/O after/O he/O won/O a/O settlement/O against/O them/O ,/O NBC/ORGANIZATION reports/O ./O 
Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION Inc./ORGANIZATION delivered/O the/O buckets/O of/O coins/O to/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 73/O ,/O after/O he/O filed/O a/O lawsuit/O claiming/O a/O worker/O at/O the/O firm/O assaulted/O him/O in/O 2012/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O station/O ./O 
``/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ./O 
We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ,/O ''/O Carrasco/PERSON blasted/O ./O 
He/O added/O ,/O ``/O Why/O do/O n't/O you/O like/O your/O clients/O ?/O ''/O 
Carrasco/PERSON recently/O suffered/O a/O hernia/O and/O was/O n't/O strong/O enough/O to/O lift/O the/O heavy/O buckets/O ,/O his/O lawyer/O Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON claimed/O ./O 
Eight/O of/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O employees/O delivered/O the/O five-gallon/O containers/O ,/O which/O were/O full/O of/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O pennies/O ,/O NBC/ORGANIZATION reported/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O gets/O paid/O with/O buckets/O of/O coins/O in/O settlement/O with/O insurance/O firm/O Insurance/ORGANIZATION company/ORGANIZATION settles/O suit/O with/O $/O 21K/O in/O loose/O coins/O By/O Veronica/PERSON Rocha/PERSON Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O sends/O man/O 16-18/O buckets/O of/O coins/O to/O pay/O lawsuit/O settlement/O of/O about/O $/O 21,000/O When/O Los/LOCATION Angeles-area/LOCATION resident/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON reached/O a/O settlement/O with/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O ,/O he/O expected/O a/O check/O ,/O but/O instead/O received/O more/O than/O a/O dozen/O buckets/O containing/O at/O least/O $/O 21,000/O in/O coins/O ./O 
Eight/O representatives/O with/O the/O insurance/O company/O delivered/O 16/O to/O 18/O paint/O buckets/O filled/O with/O quarters/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O pennies/O to/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O 's/O office/O as/O part/O of/O a/O settlement/O that/O had/O to/O be/O paid/O by/O July/O 25/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O unfortunate/O that/O a/O business/O like/O that/O would/O use/O some/O of/O these/O tactics/O ,/O ''/O said/O the/O attorney/O ,/O Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON ./O 
Settlement/O paid/O in/O coins/O Settlement/O paid/O in/O coins/O Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON with/O some/O of/O his/O $/O 21,000-plus/O settlement/O with/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O ./O 
Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON with/O some/O of/O his/O $/O 21,000-plus/O settlement/O with/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O ./O 
-LRB-/O Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON -RRB-/O Calls/O to/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O ,/O based/O in/O Rancho/LOCATION Cucamonga/LOCATION ,/O were/O not/O returned/O ./O 
The/O settlement/O was/O the/O result/O of/O a/O 2012/O lawsuit/O in/O which/O Carrasco/PERSON alleged/O that/O an/O employee/O at/O the/O company/O assaulted/O him/O when/O he/O tried/O to/O purchase/O insurance/O ,/O his/O attorney/O said/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON initially/O thought/O the/O coin/O delivery/O was/O a/O joke/O ,/O so/O he/O tried/O contacting/O the/O company/O for/O a/O check/O ./O 
But/O he/O says/O the/O company/O told/O him/O they/O were/O not/O issuing/O a/O check/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON said/O his/O client/O ,/O a/O retired/O 76-year-old/O bus/O driver/O ,/O ``/O feels/O like/O he/O is/O disrespected/O ./O ''/O 
The/O buckets/O of/O coins/O ,/O he/O said/O ,/O have/O been/O taken/O to/O the/O bank/O ,/O where/O they/O are/O being/O counted/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O gets/O $/O 21,000/O of/O settlement/O money/O in/O buckets/O of/O coins/O -LRB-/O NEWSER/O -RRB-/O --/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON was/O likely/O happy/O to/O hear/O in/O June/O that/O he/O was/O being/O awarded/O a/O settlement/O from/O an/O insurance/O company/O after/O one/O of/O its/O workers/O allegedly/O assaulted/O him/O ./O 
He/O was/O definitely/O not/O happy/O to/O see/O Loading/O .../O Post/O to/O Facebook/ORGANIZATION Man/ORGANIZATION gets/O $/O 21,000/O of/O settlement/O money/O in/O buckets/O of/O coins/O -LRB-/O NEWSER/O -RRB-/O --/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON was/O likely/O happy/O to/O hear/O in/O June/O that/O he/O was/O being/O awarded/O a/O settlement/O from/O an/O insurance/O company/O after/O one/O of/O its/O workers/O allegedly/O assaulted/O him/O ./O 
