Douche/O Move/O :/O Insurance/ORGANIZATION Company/ORGANIZATION Grudgingly/ORGANIZATION Pays/O $/O 21,000/O Settlement/O In/O Buckets/O Of/O Coins/O An/O insurance/O company/O dropped/O off/O a/O $/O 21,000/O settlement/O in/O buckets/O full/O of/O coins/O to/O a/O 73-year-old/O man/O from/O East/LOCATION L.A./LOCATION who/O could/O could/O n't/O lift/O them/O because/O he/O 's/O suffering/O from/O a/O hernia/O ./O 
Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON filed/O a/O lawsuit/O against/O Adriana/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION Inc./ORGANIZATION ,/O claiming/O that/O one/O of/O their/O employees/O physically/O assaulted/O him/O in/O 2012/O ,/O according/O to/O NBC/ORGANIZATION Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ./O 
And/O when/O the/O insurance/O company/O agreed/O in/O June/O to/O a/O settlement/O ,/O they/O paid/O him/O off/O with/O a/O check/O ,/O but/O also/O with/O more/O than/O $/O 21,000/O worth/O of/O loose/O change/O ./O 
According/O to/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O ,/O Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON ,/O eight/O Adriana/PERSON folks/O came/O by/O his/O office/O in/O a/O van/O and/O dropped/O off/O five-gallon/O containers/O full/O of/O coins/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON said/O that/O his/O client/O recently/O had/O a/O hernia/O operation/O and/O would/O in/O no/O way/O have/O been/O able/O to/O carry/O those/O buckets/O ./O 
``/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ,/O ''/O Carrasco/PERSON said/O in/O a/O statement/O ./O 
``/O We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O 62,000/O pennies/O used/O to/O pay/O off/O mortgage/O A/O Massachusetts/LOCATION penny-pincher/O makes/O his/O last/O mortgage/O payment/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
Ryan/PERSON Schulteis/PERSON reports/O ./O 
What/O started/O out/O as/O a/O joke/O 35/O years/O ago/O ended/O with/O a/O Massachusetts/LOCATION man/O paying/O off/O his/O mortgage/O using/O 62,000/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O I/O 've/O never/O saved/O anything/O other/O than/O pennies/O ./O 
And/O it/O started/O out/O as/O a/O whim/O ./O 
You/O know/O ,/O a/O penny/O for/O the/O mortgage/O ,/O ''/O Thomas/PERSON Daigle/PERSON told/O NBC/ORGANIZATION affiliate/O WHDH-TV/ORGANIZATION of/O Boston/LOCATION ./O 
Daigle/PERSON ,/O from/O Milford/LOCATION ,/O Mass./LOCATION ,/O recalled/O how/O ,/O after/O signing/O the/O mortgage/O papers/O 35/O years/O ago/O ,/O he/O found/O a/O penny/O on/O the/O ground/O ./O 
He/O and/O his/O wife/O then/O joked/O about/O collecting/O pennies/O to/O pay/O off/O the/O loan/O --/O and/O the/O rest/O is/O history/O ./O 
Over/O the/O next/O 35/O years/O ,/O Daigle/PERSON would/O roll/O pennies/O ,/O 50/O cents/O at/O a/O time/O ./O 
His/O bank/O found/O out/O the/O hard/O way/O just/O how/O much/O work/O that/O was/O --/O it/O reportedly/O took/O tellers/O two/O days/O to/O unroll/O the/O penny/O cases/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O 75-Year-Old/O Michigan/LOCATION Woman/O 's/O Reaction/O To/O $/O 570/O Water/O Bill/O Is/O Priceless/LOCATION Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION 's/O water/O department/O has/O long/O had/O billing/O issues/O ;/O one/O 75-year/O old/O found/O a/O humorous/O way/O to/O protest.Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION 's/O water/O department/O has/O long/O had/O billing/O issues/O ;/O one/O 75-year/O old/O found/O a/O humorous/O way/O to/O protest/O ./O 
What/O 's/O a/O 75-year-old-woman/O to/O do/O when/O she/O 's/O informed/O that/O the/O city-run/O water/O meter/O has/O been/O undercharging/O her/O for/O months/O and/O that/O she/O now/O must/O pay/O a/O $/O 569.81/O water/O bill/O or/O face/O having/O her/O water/O shut/O off/O ?/O 
Apparently/O ,/O if/O you/O 're/O from/O Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION ,/O Michigan/LOCATION ,/O you/O pay/O the/O bill/O ,/O but/O not/O by/O stroking/O a/O $/O 570/O check/O ./O 
//O MLive/O //O quotes/O Sarah/PERSON LeVasseur/PERSON :/O ``/O I/O want/O to/O let/O them/O know/O I/O 'm/O upset/O ./O 
I/O was/O told/O my/O reading/O has/O been/O a/O mistake/O for/O the/O past/O several/O months/O and/O that/O none/O of/O my/O past/O bills/O were/O accurate/O ./O ''/O 
An/O unexpected/O $/O 570/O water/O bill/O would/O be/O a/O sock/O in/O the/O gut/O for/O anyone/O ./O 
Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION 's/O financial/O services/O director/O George/PERSON Martini/PERSON explained/O how/O the/O water/O readings/O --/O which/O utilize/O new/O smart/O meters/O that/O recently/O cost/O the/O Michigan/LOCATION city/O $/O 6.8/O million/O --/O can/O create/O such/O large/O discrepancies/O in/O residents/O '/O water/O bills/O :/O ``/O For/O various/O reasons/O ,/O the/O outside/O meter/O does/O n't/O always/O line/O up/O with/O the/O inside/O meter/O ./O 
It/O could/O be/O as/O simple/O as/O a/O spider/O getting/O into/O the/O meter/O and/O gumming/O things/O up/O --/O it/O could/O be/O a/O number/O of/O things/O that/O might/O slow/O it/O down/O ./O 
That/O 's/O one/O of/O the/O reasons/O why/O we/O spent/O $/O 6/O million/O to/O upgrade/O to/O the/O AMI/O meters/O ./O 
Really/O ,/O one/O of/O the/O biggest/O problems/O we/O have/O are/O the/O people/O who/O literally/O pay/O their/O bill/O every/O month/O and/O never/O have/O any/O issues/O ./O 
We/O never/O get/O into/O their/O house/O to/O shut/O off/O the/O water/O ,/O look/O at/O their/O meter/O ,/O so/O we/O miss/O these/O things/O ./O 
It/O 's/O the/O squeaky/O wheel/O gets/O the/O grease/O analogy/O ./O ''/O 
So/O ,/O in/O other/O words/O ,/O Mrs./O LeVasseur/PERSON 's/O extra/O $/O 570/O water/O bill/O is/O her/O own/O fault/O //O for/O regularly/O paying/O her/O bills/O on/O time/O //O ./O 
Makes/O perfect/O sense/O ,/O right/O ?/O 
So/O ,/O what/O did/O the/O 75-year-old/O Michigan/LOCATION woman/O do/O ?/O 
She/O counted/O her/O pennies/O ./O 
And/O nickels/O ./O 
And/O dimes/O ./O 
Lots/O of/O them/O .../O $/O 569.81/O worth/O of/O them/O ./O 
Then/O ,/O she/O took/O the/O coins/O to/O City/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION and/O paid/O her/O $/O 570/O water/O bill/O with/O them/O ./O 
She/O 's/O not/O the/O first/O person/O to/O attempt/O to/O pay/O a/O utility/O bill/O in/O Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION ,/O Michigan/LOCATION with/O change/O ./O 
Another/O resident/O ,/O Richard/PERSON O'Hara/PERSON ,/O also/O tried/O to/O pay/O a/O city/O utility/O bill/O with/O coins/O five/O years/O ago/O ./O 
At/O the/O time/O ,/O the/O city/O refused/O to/O take/O his/O payment/O ,/O claiming/O that/O accepting/O the/O coins/O in/O payment/O for/O his/O utility/O bill/O presented/O a/O security/O risk/O ./O 
This/O time/O ,/O to/O his/O credit/O ,/O Martini/PERSON chose/O not/O to/O argue/O about/O it/O ./O 
Instead/O ,/O he/O counted/O the/O coins/O personally/O ,/O noting/O that/O LeVasseur/PERSON was/O understandably/O upset/O about/O the/O $/O 570/O water/O bill/O ./O 
LeVasseur/PERSON said/O that/O if/O the/O Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION accounts/O receivable/O office/O had/O refused/O to/O accept/O her/O water/O bill/O payment/O ,/O she/O would/O have/O loaded/O the/O coins/O into/O a/O wheelbarrow/O and/O taken/O them/O directly/O to/O the/O Bay/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Commission/ORGANIZATION ./O 
unique_identifier/O 1982/O :/O Paying/O alimony/O in/O pennies/O gets/O Morgan/LOCATION County/LOCATION man/O sent/O to/O jail/O for/O six/O days/O Back/O in/O 1982/O WHNT/O News/O 19/O did/O a/O story/O about/O a/O Morgan/LOCATION County/LOCATION man/O who/O decided/O to/O pay/O his/O alimony/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
A/O Morgan/LOCATION County/LOCATION judge/O said/O Norman/PERSON Guthrie/PERSON was/O making/O a/O mockery/O of/O the/O court/O and/O sentenced/O him/O to/O six/O days/O in/O the/O county/O jail/O ./O 
The/O story/O above/O originally/O aired/O on/O February/O 24/O ,/O 1982/O ./O 
Guthrie/PERSON likely/O could/O have/O appealed/O the/O judge/O 's/O sentence/O to/O a/O higher/O court/O and/O won/O ./O 
That/O 's/O because/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION Code/O says/O pennies/O can/O be/O used/O to/O pay/O debts/O to/O the/O court/O ./O 
//O However/O ,/O Guthrie/PERSON did/O not/O appeal/O the/O decision/O and/O served/O his/O six/O days/O in/O jail/O ./O 
He/O told/O us/O back/O in/O 2013/O that/O he/O no/O regrets/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Update/O On/O `/O The/O Kid/O With/O The/O Pennies/O `/O May/O 13/O ,/O 1991/O |/O By/O Bob/PERSON Greene/PERSON ./O 
At/O least/O once/O a/O week/O ,/O usually/O more/O ,/O a/O caller/O or/O letter-writer/O will/O get/O in/O touch/O with/O us/O and/O ask/O the/O question/O :/O ``/O Whatever/O happened/O to/O the/O kid/O with/O the/O pennies/O ?/O 
``/O That/O `/O s/O always/O the/O phrase/O :/O ``/O the/O kid/O with/O the/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O It/O seldom/O varies/O ./O 
Well/O .../O the/O kid/O with/O the/O pennies/O graduated/O from/O college/O Sunday/O ./O 
Which/O takes/O us/O back/O to/O where/O we/O all/O came/O in/O on/O this/O thing/O ./O 
In/O 1987/O ,/O a/O young/O man/O named/O Mike/PERSON Hayes/PERSON contacted/O me/O with/O an/O intriguing/O idea/O ./O 
Hayes/PERSON ,/O 18/O ,/O of/O Rochelle/LOCATION ,/O Ill./LOCATION ,/O was/O about/O to/O enroll/O at/O the/O University/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Illinois/ORGANIZATION ./O 
He/O was/O n`t/O an/O impoverished/O fellow/O ,/O but/O he/O did/O n`t/O know/O where/O his/O college/O money/O was/O going/O to/O come/O from/O ./O 
He/O did/O n`t/O want/O to/O borrow/O from/O his/O parents/O ,/O because/O they/O would/O have/O to/O go/O into/O debt/O to/O help/O him/O ./O 
So/O he/O came/O up/O with/O an/O idea/O :/O What/O if/O I/O asked/O the/O readers/O of/O my/O column/O to/O send/O him/O a/O penny/O ?/O 
Just/O a/O penny/O from/O any/O reader/O who/O was/O willing/O to/O do/O it/O ./O 
``/O A/O penny/O does/O n`t/O mean/O anything/O to/O anyone/O ,/O ``/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O A/O penny/O just/O does/O n`t/O count/O ./O 
``/O I/O asked/O him/O how/O many/O pennies/O he/O needed/O ./O 
``/O Well/O ,/O we/O `/O re/O talking/O about/O four/O years/O of/O college/O ,/O ``/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O Tuition/O ,/O room/O ,/O board/O ,/O books/O .../O ``/O ``/O How/O many/O ?/O 
``/O I/O said/O ./O 
``/O I/O figure/O 2.8/O million/O pennies/O ought/O to/O do/O it/O ,/O ``/O he/O said/O ./O 
2.8/O million/O pennies/O is/O the/O equivalent/O of/O $/O 28,000/O ./O 
$/O 28,000/O is/O a/O lot/O of/O money/O ,/O but/O a/O penny/O is/O n`t/O ./O 
So/O I/O wrote/O about/O Mike/PERSON Hayes/PERSON in/O a/O column/O ./O 
He/O rented/O a/O post/O office/O box/O -LRB-/O under/O the/O name/O ``/O Many/O Pennies/O for/O Mike/PERSON ``/O -RRB-/O in/O Rochelle/LOCATION ,/O which/O is/O in/O the/O middle/O of/O farm/O country/O and/O has/O a/O population/O of/O 9,000/O ./O 
He/O got/O his/O college/O money-all/O 2.8/O million/O pennies/O ,/O or/O at/O least/O the/O equivalent/O of/O that/O ./O 
Some/O people/O sent/O nickels/O ./O 
The/O pennies/O came/O from/O all/O 50/O states/O ,/O from/O many/O European/O nations/O ,/O from/O Mexico/LOCATION ,/O Canada/LOCATION ,/O the/O Bahamas/LOCATION and/O Japan/LOCATION ./O 
He/O went/O off/O to/O college-on/O a/O full/O ride/O from/O the/O penny-senders/O ./O 
So/O whatever/O happened/O to/O the/O kid/O with/O the/O pennies/O ?/O 
``/O My/O degree/O from/O the/O U./O of/O I./O is/O in/O food/O science/O ,/O ``/O Mike/PERSON Hayes/PERSON said/O the/O other/O day/O ./O 
``/O It/O `/O s/O been/O a/O great/O four/O years/O in/O college/O ,/O but/O now/O it/O `/O s/O time/O to/O graduate/O and/O go/O out/O and/O get/O a/O job/O ./O 
``/O At/O first/O ,/O he/O said/O ,/O he/O was/O a/O celebrity/O on/O campus-because/O of/O the/O publicity/O that/O came/O to/O him/O as/O the/O result/O of/O the/O penny/O stunt/O ,/O he/O was/O famous/O for/O a/O while/O ./O 
Television/O stations/O interviewed/O him/O ,/O young/O women/O from/O around/O the/O country/O sent/O him/O their/O pictures/O -LRB-/O apparently/O because/O they/O admired/O his/O entrepreneurial/O spirit/O -RRB-/O ,/O strangers/O stopped/O him/O to/O ask/O him/O questions/O ,/O a/O former/O Miss/ORGANIZATION America/ORGANIZATION even/O wrote/O him/O a/O friendly/O letter/O ./O 
Lately/O ,/O though/O ,/O he/O has/O been/O fairly/O anonymous/O ./O 
On/O a/O college/O campus/O ,/O four/O years/O is/O a/O lifetime/O ./O 
Mike/PERSON Hayes/PERSON ,/O as/O a/O senior/O ,/O became/O just/O another/O old-timer/O at/O the/O U./O of/O I./O ``/O My/O friends/O still/O know/O ,/O ``/O he/O said/O the/O other/O day/O ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n`t/O hear/O so/O much/O from/O strangers/O anymore/O ./O 
But/O my/O friends/O call/O me/O `/O Penny/PERSON Man/PERSON ./O 
`/O That/O `/O s/O their/O nickname/O for/O me/O ./O 
``/O He/O knows/O that/O there/O must/O be/O a/O certain/O amount/O of/O resentment/O toward/O him/O ./O 
After/O all/O ,/O he/O did/O n`t/O do/O anything/O to/O earn/O those/O 2.8/O million/O pennies/O ./O 
He/O was/O n`t/O a/O hard-luck/O case/O ./O 
He/O had/O n`t/O had/O an/O unfortunate/O upbringing/O ./O 
He/O was/O just/O a/O kid/O from/O the/O middle/O of/O the/O country/O who/O had/O a/O clever/O idea/O ./O 
It/O ended/O up/O putting/O him/O through/O four/O years/O of/O college/O ./O 
``/O I/O know/O this/O whole/O thing/O was/O sort/O of/O funny/O ,/O ``/O Hayes/PERSON said/O the/O other/O day/O ./O 
``/O But/O as/O I/O graduate/O ,/O I/O just/O want/O to/O thank/O everyone/O who/O sent/O a/O penny/O ./O 
The/O idea/O made/O people/O laugh/O ,/O but/O I/O `/O m/O not/O sure/O I/O would/O have/O made/O it/O all/O the/O way/O through/O college/O if/O this/O had/O n`t/O happened/O ./O 
So/O I/O `/O m/O glad/O that/O the/O penny/O thing/O caused/O people/O to/O smile-but/O I/O `/O m/O more/O glad/O that/O I/O got/O to/O go/O to/O college/O ./O 
``/O There/O `/O s/O one/O more/O thing/O :/O Mike/PERSON Hayes/PERSON needed/O the/O 2.8/O million/O pennies/O to/O pay/O for/O college/O ,/O but/O he/O ended/O up/O getting/O approximately/O 2.9/O million/O pennies/O ./O 
So/O there/O `/O s/O an/O extra/O $/O 1,000/O in/O the/O Many/O Pennies/O for/O Mike/PERSON account/O ./O 
He/O and/O his/O family/O saved/O a/O lot/O of/O the/O letters/O that/O arrived/O in/O Rochelle/LOCATION four/O years/O ago/O ./O 
``/O We/O have/O about/O 90,000/O of/O the/O letters/O stored/O in/O my/O brother/O `/O s/O basement/O ,/O ``/O he/O said/O ./O 
Mike/PERSON plans/O to/O give/O the/O extra/O $/O 1,000/O to/O a/O deserving/O college/O student/O from/O one/O of/O the/O families/O that/O sent/O him/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O I/O `/O m/O not/O going/O to/O be/O real/O scientific/O about/O it/O ,/O ``/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O I/O `/O m/O just/O going/O to/O stick/O my/O hand/O into/O those/O 90,000/O letters/O we/O saved/O ,/O start/O calling/O people/O whose/O names/O are/O on/O the/O envelopes/O I/O grab/O ,/O and/O ask/O if/O there/O `/O s/O a/O person/O in/O their/O family/O who/O needs/O $/O 1,000/O for/O college/O ./O 
I/O `/O m/O going/O to/O trust/O them-I/O `/O m/O going/O to/O count/O on/O them/O to/O tell/O me/O if/O they/O do/O n`t/O really/O need/O the/O college/O money/O ./O 
If/O they/O do/O n`t/O need/O it/O ,/O I/O `/O ll/O move/O on/O to/O the/O next/O envelope/O ./O 
``/O Sort/O of/O the/O Many/O Pennies/O for/O Mike/PERSON Scholarship/PERSON ./O 
``/O This/O whole/O thing/O has/O been/O very/O goofy/O ,/O ``/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O Tell/O everyone/O how/O much/O I/O appreciate/O it/O ./O 
``/O unique_identifier/O Taxpayers/O Coin/O Protest/O Slogan/O The/O Buck/O Stops/O Here/O ,/O They/O Tell/O School/O District/O August/O 30/O ,/O 1991/O |/O by/O MARIO/PERSON F./PERSON CATTABIANI/PERSON ,/O The/O Morning/O Call/O Muscles/O straining/O and/O brows/O dripping/O ,/O a/O group/O of/O Easton/ORGANIZATION Area/ORGANIZATION School/ORGANIZATION District/ORGANIZATION residents/O lugged/O bags/O ,/O boxes/O and/O pails/O of/O change/O to/O pay/O their/O property/O taxes/O yesterday/O ,/O and/O aiming/O a/O slogan/O at/O Easton/LOCATION school/O officials/O :/O The/O buck/O stops/O here/O --/O and/O so/O do/O the/O nickels/O and/O the/O dimes/O ./O 
In/O what/O has/O both/O a/O mild/O tax/O revolt/O and/O a/O media/O stunt/O ,/O the/O demonstrators/O yesterday/O hoped/O to/O get/O their/O message/O across/O as/O they/O paid/O what/O they/O considered/O ``/O inflated/O ''/O taxes/O with/O coins/O ./O 
``/O The/O school/O board/O wants/O my/O last/O nickel/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O here/O it/O is/O ,/O ''/O said/O Alan/PERSON Legath/PERSON of/O Easton/PERSON ,/O dumping/O his/O wrapped/O coins/O on/O a/O counter/O in/O the/O city/O tax/O collector/O 's/O office/O ./O 
Legath/PERSON ,/O along/O with/O his/O wife/O ,/O Michelle/PERSON ,/O said/O their/O property/O taxes/O jumped/O 62.1/O percent/O this/O year/O because/O of/O the/O county/O 's/O reassessment/O and/O increased/O school/O levies/O ./O 
Despite/O vocal/O objections/O at/O a/O seriesof/O public/O hearings/O ,/O school/O directors/O in/O June/O approved/O a/O $/O 38.5/O million/O 1991-92/O operating/O budget/O ./O 
A/O 13.6-percent/O tax/O increase/O --/O the/O largest/O in/O a/O decade/O --/O was/O required/O to/O fund/O the/O spending/O plan/O ./O 
``/O The/O buck/O stops/O here/O ,/O ''/O said/O Frank/PERSON Manazer/PERSON ,/O an/O Easton/LOCATION businessman/O and/O property/O owner/O ./O 
``/O We/O are/O trying/O to/O tell/O the/O school/O board/O ,/O `/O Lets/O be/O conservative/O ./O '/O ''/O 
Pat/PERSON Vulcano/PERSON Jr./PERSON ,/O city/O treasurer/O and/O tax/O collector/O ,/O did/O n't/O appear/O to/O mind/O the/O inconvenience/O of/O the/O coins/O ./O 
In/O fact/O ,/O he/O agreed/O with/O the/O event/O 's/O message/O ./O 
``/O It/O just/O shows/O that/O the/O school/O board/O is/O totally/O insensitive/O to/O the/O taxpayers/O ,/O ''/O Vulcano/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O I/O 've/O had/O people/O in/O here/O literally/O in/O tears/O because/O they/O were/O afraid/O they/O would/O lose/O their/O homes/O because/O they/O could/O n't/O afford/O the/O increased/O taxes/O ./O ''/O 
What/O effect/O the/O demonstration/O will/O have/O on/O future/O tax/O hikes/O remains/O to/O be/O seen/O ./O 
But/O for/O at/O least/O one/O resident/O ,/O the/O display/O was/O worth/O it/O ./O 
``/O I/O hope/O this/O tells/O other/O people/O that/O there/O are/O honest/O ways/O to/O protest/O ./O 
If/O you/O sit/O back/O ,/O they/O 'll/O steamroll/O over/O you/O ,/O ''/O said/O South/LOCATION Side/LOCATION resident/O Merrielee/PERSON Legath/PERSON after/O paying/O her/O $/O 686/O tax/O bill/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O $/O 686.05/O ./O 
Let/O 's/O not/O forget/O that/O loose/O nickel/O ,/O she/O added/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O September/O 27/O ,/O 1996/O </O //O 1996/sep/27/O //O >/O in/O Nation/World/O </O //O nation-world/O //O >/O Patrons/O Test/O Restaurants/O '/O Tolerance/O Researchers/O Try/O To/O Get/O Clerks/O Steamed/O By/O */O Richard/PERSON Roesler/PERSON */O The/O Spokesman-Review/O Nearly/O every/O September/O for/O the/O last/O 11/O years/O ,/O Palouse/O fast-food/O restaurants/O have/O been/O hit/O with/O a/O plague/O of/O customers/O from/O hell/O ./O 
They/O deliberately/O spill/O Cokes/O on/O floors/O ,/O haul/O bikes/O into/O dining/O rooms/O ,/O and/O bang/O on/O the/O drive-through/O windows/O ./O 
They/O put/O a/O hair/O on/O a/O cheeseburger/O and/O complain/O ./O 
They/O pay/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
They/O toss/O their/O keys/O in/O the/O trash/O and/O demand/O that/O a/O clerk/O fish/O them/O out/O ./O 
All/O this/O in/O the/O name/O of/O research/O ./O 
``/O We/O 're/O trying/O to/O determine/O the/O reaction/O we/O get/O by/O being/O jerks/O ,/O ''/O said/O Tony/PERSON Belsito/PERSON ,/O a/O Washington/ORGANIZATION State/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION senior/O ./O 
Nearly/O every/O September/O for/O the/O last/O 11/O years/O ,/O Palouse/O fast-food/O restaurants/O have/O been/O hit/O with/O a/O plague/O of/O customers/O from/O hell/O ./O 
They/O deliberately/O spill/O Cokes/O on/O floors/O ,/O haul/O bikes/O into/O dining/O rooms/O ,/O and/O bang/O on/O the/O drive-through/O windows/O ./O 
They/O put/O a/O hair/O on/O a/O cheeseburger/O and/O complain/O ./O 
They/O pay/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
They/O toss/O their/O keys/O in/O the/O trash/O and/O demand/O that/O a/O clerk/O fish/O them/O out/O ./O 
All/O this/O in/O the/O name/O of/O research/O ./O 
``/O We/O 're/O trying/O to/O determine/O the/O reaction/O we/O get/O by/O being/O jerks/O ,/O ''/O said/O Tony/PERSON Belsito/PERSON ,/O a/O Washington/ORGANIZATION State/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION senior/O ./O 
Welcome/O to/O the/O field/O trials/O of/O a/O class/O called/O Hospitality/O 382/O ,/O which/O sends/O more/O than/O two/O dozen/O students/O out/O each/O fall/O to/O secretly/O grade/O local/O restaurants/O on/O their/O friendliness/O under/O duress/O ./O 
``/O Service/O is/O not/O dead/O in/O America/LOCATION ./O 
It/O 's/O mediocre/O ,/O ''/O said/O Professor/O Don/PERSON Smith/PERSON ./O 
Smith/PERSON ,/O 67/O ,/O former/O president/O of/O the/O Shakey/O 's/O Pizza/O chain/O ,/O has/O taught/O the/O ``/O Chain/O Restaurant/O Management/O ''/O class/O at/O WSU/ORGANIZATION for/O more/O than/O a/O decade/O ./O 
The/O bad/O customer/O spree/O ,/O Smith/PERSON said/O ,/O also/O shows/O his/O students/O -/O many/O of/O whom/O will/O go/O on/O to/O manage/O restaurants/O and/O hotels/O -/O what/O it/O 's/O like/O to/O be/O a/O customer/O with/O a/O complaint/O ./O 
Students/O visited/O 14/O restaurants/O three/O times/O each/O ,/O looking/O for/O unusually/O good/O -/O or/O bad/O -/O service/O ./O 
The/O top/O three/O restaurants/O will/O be/O honored/O at/O an/O awards/O ceremony/O this/O morning/O ./O 
Smith/PERSON 's/O students/O would/O n't/O reveal/O the/O big/O three/O early/O ./O 
The/O students/O '/O meal/O tabs/O are/O picked/O up/O by/O a/O Kentucky/ORGANIZATION Fried/ORGANIZATION Chicken/ORGANIZATION executive/O who/O donates/O $/O 2,000/O per/O year/O for/O class/O expenses/O ./O 
Often/O ,/O students/O said/O ,/O their/O complaints/O and/O buffoonery/O were/O met/O with/O rolling/O eyes/O and/O scowls/O ./O 
One/O grill/O cook/O ,/O furious/O that/O a/O cheeseburger/O had/O been/O sent/O back/O ,/O hurled/O it/O into/O the/O trash/O ./O 
In/O past/O years/O ,/O workers/O have/O laughed/O at/O the/O problems/O people/O on/O crutches/O have/O trying/O to/O carry/O food/O trays/O ,/O or/O they/O have/O grossly/O inflated/O the/O bills/O of/O foreign/O students/O ./O 
Chad/PERSON Heilesen/PERSON and/O his/O partner/O rode/O their/O bicycles/O through/O the/O drive-through/O ,/O paid/O with/O small/O change/O ,/O then/O dragged/O the/O bikes/O into/O the/O Moscow/LOCATION Arby/LOCATION 's/O dining/O room/O ./O 
They/O were/O amazed/O when/O the/O manager/O ,/O unperturbed/O ,/O offered/O to/O park/O the/O bikes/O at/O a/O nearby/O table/O ./O 
Rona/PERSON Thang/PERSON and/O her/O partner/O went/O to/O the/O Arby/ORGANIZATION 's/O in/O Pullman/PERSON ./O 
They/O placed/O their/O order/O ,/O then/O hauled/O out/O a/O sack/O of/O 200/O coins/O to/O pay/O the/O $/O 7/O bill/O ./O 
Next/O ,/O they/O took/O Thang/PERSON 's/O house/O keys/O ,/O smeared/O them/O with/O ketchup/O and/O flicked/O them/O into/O a/O trash/O can/O ./O 
``/O My/O God/O !/O ''/O 
Thang/O announced/O ./O 
``/O I/O 've/O lost/O my/O keys/O !/O ''/O 
Without/O complaint/O ,/O the/O clerk/O hustled/O the/O trash/O bag/O into/O the/O back/O and/O emerged/O three/O minutes/O later/O with/O the/O keys/O ,/O which/O she/O 'd/O washed/O ./O 
``/O She/O even/O said/O ,/O `/O Oh/O ,/O it/O 's/O a/O pretty/O key/O chain/O ,/O '''/O recalled/O Thang/O ,/O still/O impressed/O ./O 
After/O a/O decade/O of/O these/O ``/O secret/O shopper/O ''/O exercises/O ,/O restaurant/O managers/O are/O on/O guard/O every/O September/O ./O 
But/O occasionally/O ,/O they/O run/O into/O genuinely/O snotty/O people/O ,/O Smith/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O They/O oftentimes/O think/O it/O 's/O our/O kids/O -/O and/O it/O is/O n't/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O ProQuest/O </O //O advanced?accountid/O =/O 12874/O >/O Chicago/ORGANIZATION Tribune/ORGANIZATION </O //O chicagotribune?accountid/O =/O 12874/O >/O TOLLWAY/O CHEATERS/O WARNED/O TO/O PAY/O UP/O VIDEOS/O COULD/O BRING/O LICENSE/O SUSPENSION/O :/O -LSB-/O CHICAGO/O SPORTS/O FINAL/O Edition/O -RSB-/O Abstract/O -LRB-/O summary/O -RRB-/O Translate/O -LSB-/O unavailable/O for/O this/O document/O -RSB-/O The/O report/O ,/O which/O Gov./O George/PERSON Ryan/PERSON asked/O tollway/O Director/O Thomas/PERSON Cuculich/PERSON to/O prepare/O last/O October/O ,/O was/O due/O in/O early/O December/O ./O 
But/O its/O complexity/O ,/O along/O with/O the/O difficulty/O of/O nailing/O down/O an/O appointment/O with/O the/O governor/O to/O present/O it/O ,/O have/O resulted/O in/O repeated/O delays/O ,/O Cuculich/PERSON said/O during/O a/O tollway/O board/O meeting/O Thursday/O ./O 
The/O report/O ,/O which/O Gov./O George/PERSON Ryan/PERSON asked/O tollway/O Director/O Thomas/PERSON Cuculich/PERSON to/O prepare/O last/O October/O ,/O was/O due/O in/O early/O December/O ./O 
But/O its/O complexity/O ,/O along/O with/O the/O difficulty/O of/O nailing/O down/O an/O appointment/O with/O the/O governor/O to/O present/O it/O ,/O have/O resulted/O in/O repeated/O delays/O ,/O Cuculich/PERSON said/O during/O a/O tollway/O board/O meeting/O Thursday/O ./O 
You/O have/O requested/O ``/O on-the-fly/O ''/O machine/O translation/O of/O selected/O content/O from/O our/O databases/O ./O 
This/O functionality/O is/O provided/O solely/O for/O your/O convenience/O and/O is/O in/O no/O way/O intended/O to/O replace/O human/O translation/O ./O 
Electric/O messaging/O signs/O on/O Illinois/LOCATION toll/O roads/O began/O blinking/O out/O a/O dire/O warning/O to/O toll/O cheats/O Thursday/O :/O ``/O Do/O n't/O nickel/O and/O dime/O your/O license/O away/O !/O ''/O 
warns/O one/O ./O 
``/O Do/O n't/O risk/O arrest/O ./O 
Pay/O your/O tolls/O !/O ''/O 
says/O another/O ./O 
The/O signs/O reflect/O a/O law/O that/O became/O effective/O Jan./O 1/O that/O gives/O the/O Illinois/ORGANIZATION State/ORGANIZATION Toll/ORGANIZATION Highway/ORGANIZATION Authority/ORGANIZATION and/O secretary/O of/O state/O 's/O office/O the/O power/O to/O suspend/O the/O driver/O 's/O licenses/O of/O those/O who/O ignore/O five/O toll/O violation/O tickets/O ./O 
Video/O enforcement/O cameras/O record/O the/O violations/O ./O 
Citations/O grow/O from/O $/O 20/O to/O $/O 50/O if/O ignored/O for/O 21/O days/O ./O 
Meanwhile/O ,/O the/O deadline/O has/O been/O pushed/O back/O again/O for/O a/O tollway/O report/O that/O outlines/O options/O for/O the/O road/O authority/O 's/O future/O --/O including/O its/O possible/O demise/O ./O 
The/O report/O ,/O which/O Gov./O George/PERSON Ryan/PERSON asked/O tollway/O Director/O Thomas/PERSON Cuculich/PERSON to/O prepare/O last/O October/O ,/O was/O due/O in/O early/O December/O ./O 
But/O its/O complexity/O ,/O along/O with/O the/O difficulty/O of/O nailing/O down/O an/O appointment/O with/O the/O governor/O to/O present/O it/O ,/O have/O resulted/O in/O repeated/O delays/O ,/O Cuculich/PERSON said/O during/O a/O tollway/O board/O meeting/O Thursday/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O very/O close/O to/O being/O done/O .../O We/O 're/O working/O with/O -LRB-/O Ryan/PERSON 's/O -RRB-/O staff/O to/O find/O the/O appropriate/O time/O for/O me/O to/O meet/O with/O him/O ,/O ''/O said/O Cuculich/PERSON ,/O who/O estimates/O it/O will/O now/O be/O some/O time/O in/O February/O before/O the/O governor/O sees/O the/O report/O ./O 
Board/ORGANIZATION Chairman/O Art/PERSON Philip/PERSON ,/O who/O sat/O in/O on/O sessions/O with/O tollway/O consultants/O advising/O Cuculich/PERSON ,/O played/O down/O any/O expectations/O that/O the/O report/O will/O contain/O any/O ``/O revelations/O ./O ''/O 
``/O We/O 're/O waiting/O for/O the/O shoe/O to/O drop/O .../O But/O we/O still/O owe/O $/O 880/O million/O -LRB-/O in/O bond/O debt/O -RRB-/O ,/O and/O somebody/O has/O to/O solve/O that/O problem/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
The/O board/O met/O the/O day/O before/O a/O planned/O ``/O penny/O protest/O ''/O called/O for/O by/O an/O anti-toll/O group/O based/O in/O Sugar/LOCATION Grove/LOCATION ./O 
``/O No/O Tolls/O ''/O is/O encouraging/O motorists/O to/O show/O their/O support/O for/O ending/O tolls/O by/O paying/O tolls/O with/O pennies/O every/O Friday/O starting/O Jan./O 28/O ./O 
Tollway/O officials/O dismissed/O the/O protest/O as/O minor/O ,/O saying/O the/O automated/O coin/O machines/O can/O count/O 40/O pennies/O in/O 11/O seconds/O and/O if/O traffic/O backs/O up/O in/O the/O manual/O lanes/O ,/O collectors/O may/O just/O estimate/O the/O amount/O and/O move/O on/O to/O the/O next/O customer/O ./O 
``/O It/O will/O be/O more/O of/O an/O inconvenience/O to/O motorists/O than/O it/O will/O be/O for/O us/O to/O count/O pennies/O ,/O ''/O Cuculich/PERSON said/O ./O 
Word/O count/O :/O */O 364/O */O unique_identifier/O */O MAN/O PAYS/O TRAFFIC/O FINE/O WITH/O 15,000/O PENNIES/O */O March/O 27/O ,/O 2003/O --/O 3:45/O pm/O PST/O NewsWithViews.com/O An/O Oregon/LOCATION man/O is/O so/O upset/O for/O being/O slapped/O with/O a/O $/O 150/O traffic/O fine/O for/O crossing/O a/O fog/O line/O on/O the/O freeway/O ,/O he/O is/O venting/O his/O anger/O toward/O the/O government/O by/O paying/O his/O fine/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
Ted/PERSON Wegener/PERSON ,/O a/O Grants/O Pass/O resident/O ,/O was/O ticketed/O last/O year/O for/O his/O car/O crossing/O over/O the/O painted/O fog/O line/O on/O the/O I-5/O freeway/O ,/O a/O relatively/O minor/O offense/O ./O 
The/O ticket/O carries/O a/O hefty/O $/O 150/O fine/O ./O 
``/O Yes/O ,/O I/O crossed/O over/O the/O fog/O line/O while/O making/O a/O cell/O call/O but/O corrected/O my/O driving/O and/O there/O was/O no/O danger/O to/O anyone/O ./O 
He/O could/O have/O just/O given/O me/O a/O warning/O ./O 
$/O 150/O fine/O for/O crossing/O over/O a/O painted/O line/O is/O an/O insult/O ./O 
In/O fact/O ,/O these/O excessive/O traffic/O fines/O are/O an/O insult/O to/O every/O working/O person/O ./O 
It/O 's/O no/O wonder/O that/O people/O are/O losing/O respect/O for/O government/O ./O ''/O 
Replied/O Mr./O Wegener/PERSON ./O 
Mr./O Wegener/PERSON says/O the/O whole/O traffic/O court/O system/O is/O corrupt/O ./O 
``/O I/O tried/O to/O make/O a/O motion/O in/O court/O for/O a/O jury/O trial/O but/O when/O Judge/O Ambrosini/PERSON of/O Douglas/LOCATION County/LOCATION ,/O OR/O found/O out/O what/O the/O motion/O was/O about/O he/O wouldn/O t/O even/O let/O me/O make/O it/O ./O 
And/O if/O I/O want/O to/O appeal/O to/O a/O higher/O court/O ,/O they/O want/O to/O charge/O me/O a/O non-refundable/O $/O 140/O filing/O fee/O for/O a/O $/O 150/O traffic/O fine/O ''/O Mr./O Wegener/PERSON says/O the/O traffic/O court/O is/O really/O a/O revenue/O enhancer/O ./O 
``/O What/O is/O happening/O is/O that/O the/O legislature/O is/O establishing/O excessive/O fines/O to/O raise/O money/O ./O 
This/O is/O not/O about/O safe/O highways/O ;/O this/O is/O about/O taxation/O in/O the/O guise/O of/O traffic/O enforcement/O ./O ''/O 
Mr./O Wegener/PERSON says/O people/O should/O be/O outraged/O about/O the/O excessive/O fines/O and/O that/O there/O is/O something/O they/O can/O do/O about/O it/O ./O 
``/O I/O ca/O n't/O appeal/O because/O of/O the/O high/O appeals/O fees/O ./O 
Writing/O my/O `/O legislooters/O '/O wo/O n't/O help/O either/O ,/O because/O they/O are/O the/O cause/O of/O the/O problem/O in/O the/O first/O place/O ./O 
I/O have/O no/O choice/O but/O to/O pay/O the/O fine/O ./O ''/O 
Mr./O Wegener/PERSON says/O he/O is/O going/O to/O mail/O the/O court/O the/O fine/O :/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O They/O don/O t/O think/O $/O 150/O is/O a/O lot/O of/O money/O ,/O so/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O send/O it/O to/O them/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
This/O is/O legal/O :/O pennies/O are/O legal/O tender/O ./O 
Maybe/O when/O they/O are/O counting/O it/O they/O will/O realize/O it/O s/O a/O lot/O of/O money/O ./O ''/O 
Ted/PERSON Wegener/PERSON 's/O E-Mail/O is/O tedw@internetcds.com/O 2003/O -/O NewsWithViews.com/O -/O All/O Rights/O Reserved/O unique_identifier/O Bucks/O Free/O Press/O :/O Site/O Logo/O Man/O pays/O council/O tax/O in/O coins/O as/O protest/O 1:50/O pm/O Friday/O 6th/O June/O 2003/O By/O Vince/PERSON Soodin/PERSON A/O DISGRUNTLED/O council/O taxpayer/O paid/O his/O bill/O in/O bags/O of/O coins/O weighing/O 15lbs/O in/O protest/O at/O tax/O increases/O ./O 
Peter/PERSON Zeyss/PERSON ,/O 62/O ,/O of/O Sycamore/PERSON Dean/PERSON ,/O Chesham/LOCATION ,/O took/O money/O bags/O full/O of/O 5p/O ,10/O p/O ,/O 50p/O and/O #/O 1/O coins/O to/O demonstrate/O his/O anger/O at/O 15/O per/O cent/O increases/O in/O council/O tax/O bills/O ./O 
Company/O director/O Mr/PERSON Zeyss/PERSON said/O :/O ``/O We/O have/O had/O the/O increase/O last/O year/O and/O this/O year/O of/O 15/O per/O cent/O and/O it/O is/O not/O justified/O ./O 
This/O is/O well/O beyond/O the/O rate/O of/O inflation/O ./O 
``/O At/O the/O same/O time/O as/O these/O increases/O our/O services/O seemed/O to/O have/O been/O reduced/O ./O 
That/O is/O what/O really/O annoys/O me/O and/O I/O just/O wanted/O to/O see/O what/O kind/O of/O reaction/O it/O would/O stir/O ./O ''/O 
Mr/O Zeyss/PERSON said/O he/O changed/O his/O payment/O of/O #/O 210/O ./O 
67/O into/O coins/O before/O visiting/O the/O payment/O centre/O at/O Chiltern/ORGANIZATION District/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION Offices/ORGANIZATION in/O King/O George/PERSON V/PERSON Road/PERSON ,/O Amersham/ORGANIZATION ,/O last/O Wednesday/O ./O 
But/O he/O said/O he/O was/O surprised/O at/O how/O well/O the/O cashiers/O dealt/O with/O the/O awkward/O payment/O ./O 
Mr/O Zeyss/PERSON said/O :/O ``/O I/O was/O surprised/O how/O cool/O the/O cashier/O took/O my/O payment/O and/O started/O to/O count/O the/O money/O ./O 
She/O called/O for/O help/O from/O another/O member/O of/O staff/O and/O they/O managed/O to/O count/O the/O money/O in/O 35/O minutes/O ./O ''/O 
But/O Mr/O Zeyss/PERSON believes/O his/O protest/O will/O only/O be/O noticed/O if/O more/O people/O show/O their/O anger/O at/O increases/O in/O a/O similar/O manner/O and/O disrupt/O council/O tax/O payments/O ./O 
Mr/O Zeyss/PERSON says/O he/O is/O angry/O at/O what/O he/O believes/O is/O a/O lack/O of/O transparency/O in/O how/O council/O tax/O money/O is/O spent/O and/O questions/O the/O usefulness/O of/O councillors/O ./O 
He/O said/O :/O ``/O What/O is/O the/O point/O of/O voting/O for/O councillors/O if/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O day/O they/O do/O not/O have/O sufficient/O power/O to/O challenge/O Government/O policies/O ?/O ''/O 
Mr/O Zeyss/PERSON '/O actions/O were/O applauded/O by/O Chris/PERSON Mellor/PERSON of/O the/O Council/ORGANIZATION Tax/ORGANIZATION Action/ORGANIZATION Group/ORGANIZATION ,/O which/O wants/O the/O tax/O abolished/O ./O 
Mr/O Mellor/PERSON said/O :/O ``/O I/O think/O it/O is/O a/O wonderful/O gesture/O ./O 
He/O is/O making/O the/O point/O and/O getting/O his/O message/O across/O ./O 
I/O think/O more/O people/O should/O pay/O by/O coins/O to/O make/O a/O point/O ./O 
``/O More/O pressure/O needs/O to/O be/O put/O on/O councillors/O so/O they/O start/O standing/O up/O for/O the/O people/O who/O elect/O them/O ./O 
They/O should/O start/O taking/O on/O the/O Government/O ./O 
``/O I/O think/O people/O power/O in/O the/O end/O will/O come/O through/O ./O ''/O 
A/O spokesman/O for/O Chiltern/ORGANIZATION District/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION said/O another/O payment/O in/O coins/O was/O also/O made/O on/O Tuesday/O evening/O and/O was/O dealt/O with/O ``/O in/O a/O couple/O of/O minutes/O ''/O by/O a/O council/O employee/O as/O the/O payment/O centre/O was/O closed/O ./O 
The/O spokesman/O added/O :/O ``/O We/O are/O grateful/O to/O receive/O any/O outstanding/O payment/O of/O council/O tax/O in/O anyway/O but/O we/O would/O obviously/O prefer/O that/O people/O set/O up/O a/O direct/O debit/O or/O cheque/O payment/O ./O 
``/O But/O we/O would/O never/O turn/O any/O payment/O away/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Penny/O awarded/O is/O a/O penny/O donated/O Small-claims/O victor/O to/O donate/O $/O 33,500/O in/O 1-cent/O coins/O to/O charity/O ./O 
Small-claims/O victor/O to/O donate/O $/O 33,500/O in/O 1-cent/O coins/O to/O charity/O ./O 
April/O 11/O ,/O 2007/O HOWELL/LOCATION ,/O Mich./LOCATION -LRB-/O AP/ORGANIZATION -RRB-/O --/O A/O penny/O saved/O is/O a/O penny/O earned/O ,/O but/O one/O man/O believes/O 33,500/O pennies/O won/O are/O best/O donated/O to/O a/O worthy/O cause/O ./O 
Bob/PERSON Wilson/PERSON ,/O of/O Livingston/LOCATION County/LOCATION 's/O Howell/LOCATION Township/LOCATION ,/O won/O a/O small-claims/O court/O case/O last/O month/O over/O motorcycle/O repairs/O and/O received/O a/O judgment/O of/O $/O 335/O ./O 
Karl/PERSON Stepen/PERSON ,/O owner/O of/O NSK/ORGANIZATION Motorsports/ORGANIZATION in/O Fowlerville/LOCATION ,/O said/O he/O paid/O Wilson/PERSON in/O pennies/O to/O show/O his/O contempt/O for/O him/O and/O things/O he/O said/O in/O court/O ``/O just/O basically/O to/O make/O us/O look/O bad/O ./O ''/O 
``/O We/O paid/O him/O in/O legal/O U.S./LOCATION currency/O ,/O ''/O Stepen/PERSON told/O the/O Livingston/ORGANIZATION County/ORGANIZATION Daily/ORGANIZATION Press/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION Argus/ORGANIZATION for/O a/O story/O Tuesday/O ./O 
Wilson/PERSON said/O he/O will/O donate/O the/O pennies/O to/O the/O Oakland/ORGANIZATION Livingston/ORGANIZATION Human/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION Agency/ORGANIZATION ,/O which/O has/O helped/O him/O with/O heating/O bills/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O not/O worth/O my/O time/O to/O reroll/O those/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
Wilson/PERSON said/O he/O bought/O a/O dirt/O bike/O for/O his/O 13-year-old/O son/O and/O took/O it/O to/O NSK/ORGANIZATION in/O May/O to/O get/O it/O running/O ./O 
He/O did/O not/O get/O the/O bike/O back/O until/O October/O ,/O and/O he/O said/O it/O stopped/O working/O almost/O immediately/O ./O 
He/O took/O the/O bike/O back/O to/O NSK/ORGANIZATION and/O it/O sat/O unfixed/O for/O a/O few/O more/O months/O ./O 
He/O picked/O it/O up/O and/O took/O it/O to/O another/O shop/O ,/O which/O charged/O him/O $/O 900/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
Wilson/PERSON said/O he/O filed/O the/O suit/O in/O small-claims/O court/O because/O it/O was/O n't/O fixed/O the/O first/O time/O ./O 
Stepen/PERSON said/O he/O had/O the/O bike/O ``/O for/O some/O time/O ,/O ''/O but/O he/O 's/O a/O one-man/O operation/O with/O as/O many/O as/O 70/O motorcycles/O waiting/O to/O be/O repaired/O ./O 
He/O said/O he/O did/O everything/O he/O could/O to/O help/O Wilson/PERSON with/O the/O 30-year-old/O bike/O and/O offered/O to/O fix/O a/O second/O problem/O for/O free/O ./O 
Stepen/PERSON said/O Wilson/PERSON became/O impatient/O and/O verbally/O abusive/O ,/O and/O showed/O up/O with/O a/O police/O officer/O to/O retrieve/O his/O bike/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O $/O 174K/O Salaried/O Dem/O `/O Saving/O My/O Pennies/O '/O For/O Fine/O in/O Wage/ORGANIZATION Inequality/ORGANIZATION Protest/ORGANIZATION Rep./O Gwen/PERSON Moore/PERSON -LRB-/O D-Wis/O ./O -RRB-/O 
tells/O FOX6/O Milwaukee/LOCATION that/O she/O will/O be/O ``/O saving/O my/O pennies/O ''/O to/O pay/O her/O $/O 691/O dollar/O disorderly/O conduct/O fine/O ./O 
Moore/PERSON was/O arrested/O in/O a/O Milwaukee/LOCATION protest/O Thursday/O involving/O fast/O food/O workers/O who/O are/O demanding/O a/O minimum/O wage/O of/O $/O 15/O per/O hour/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'll/O be/O saving/O my/O pennies/O to/O pay/O this/O $/O 691/O dollar/O fine/O ,/O ''/O Moore/PERSON told/O television/O reporters/O after/O her/O release/O ./O 
She/O is/O among/O 26/O protestors/O arrested/O after/O they/O refused/O to/O vacate/O the/O road/O they/O were/O blocking/O ./O 
Moore/PERSON ,/O like/O many/O lawmakers/O ,/O earns/O $/O 174,000/O a/O year/O for/O her/O work/O as/O a/O U.S./LOCATION Representative/O ./O 
Moore/PERSON told/O WISN-TV/O that/O she/O took/O part/O in/O the/O minimum/O wage/O rally/O ,/O ``/O to/O really/O protest/O the/O egregious/O inequality/O in/O our/O society/O ./O ''/O 
``/O I/O wanted/O to/O speak/O out/O on/O that/O ./O 
As/O I/O indicated/O earlier/O ,/O you/O know/O ,/O I/O 've/O put/O on/O my/O best/O suit/O ,/O had/O my/O hair/O done/O ,/O my/O nails/O done/O and/O used/O the/O King/O 's/O English/O to/O debate/O this/O in/O Congress/ORGANIZATION and/O no/O one/O is/O listening/O ./O ''/O 
``/O What/O we/O see/O is/O a/O tremendous/O inequality/O based/O on/O an/O unfairness/O --/O that/O gap/O --/O between/O what/O people/O at/O the/O top/O make/O and/O what/O low/O wage/O workers/O make/O ,/O ''/O Moore/PERSON said/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O STPNS/O -/O Penny/O Protest/O ,/O Merrimack/LOCATION ,/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION August/O 03/O ,/O 2007/O Penny/O Protest/O DOT/O has/O some/O concerns/O about/O Aug./O 27/O toll/O revolt/O Penny/ORGANIZATION Protest/ORGANIZATION The/ORGANIZATION Town/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION is/O asking/O residents/O to/O join/O a/O protest/O on/O Aug./O 27/O by/O paying/O highway/O tolls/O in/O pennies/O on/O that/O day/O ./O 
Andrew/PERSON M./PERSON Virzi/PERSON photo/O By/O Mark/PERSON Oullette/PERSON for/O Merrimack/ORGANIZATION Journal/ORGANIZATION MERRIMACK/ORGANIZATION ,/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION -LRB-/O STPNS/O -RRB-/O --/O With/O a/O month/O to/O prepare/O for/O Merrimack?s/O Toll/O Revolt/O Day/O on/O Aug./O 27/O ,/O the/O Department/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Transportation/ORGANIZATION is/O concerned/O about/O problems/O that/O could/O arise/O from/O residents/O paying/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
Bill/PERSON Boynton/PERSON ,/O the/O DOT?s/O public/O information/O officer/O the/O past/O 12/O years/O ,/O said/O this/O week/O that/O he?s/O never/O seen/O a/O protest/O like/O the/O one/O that/O is/O being/O planned/O for/O late/O August/O ./O 
?/O 
We/O normally/O get/O the/O kind/O of/O situation/O where/O people/O say/O they/O put/O the/O right/O amount/O of/O money/O in/O ,/O and/O the/O green/O light/O didn?t/O go/O off/O like/O it/O should/O have/O and/O that/O sort/O of/O thing/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O Boynton/LOCATION ,/O ?/O 
and/O ,/O occasionally/O ,/O the/O exact/O change/O machines/O will/O jam/O ./O 
But/O I/O don?t/O think/O they?ve/O seen/O or/O been/O asked/O to/O sustain/O this/O type/O of/O volume/O before/O ./O 
?/O 
When/O Executive/O Councilor/O Deb/PERSON Pignatelli/PERSON broke/O the/O news/O to/O the/O Town/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION last/O Thursday/O that/O the/O Legislature/ORGANIZATION had/O cut/O the/O Executive/O Council?s/O power/O to/O give/O toll/O discounts/O ,/O ?/O 
that/O was/O the/O straw/O that/O broke/O the/O camel?s/O back/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O Town/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION Chairman/O Dave/PERSON McCray/PERSON ./O 
Pignatelli/PERSON was/O attempting/O to/O give/O Merrimack/LOCATION residents/O two/O free/O EZPass/O passes/O for/O those/O with/O transponders/O and/O also/O allow/O town-owned/O vehicles/O free/O access/O to/O the/O F./PERSON E./PERSON Everett/PERSON Turnpike/PERSON for/O emergency/O calls/O ./O 
When/O McCray/PERSON got/O that/O news/O ,/O he/O made/O a/O motion/O to/O proclaim/O Aug./O 27/O ?/O 
Toll/O Revolt/O Day/O ,/O ?/O 
one/O where/O residents/O would/O pay/O tolls/O using/O pennies/O ./O 
Councilor/O Tom/PERSON Mahon/PERSON was/O not/O present/O for/O the/O meeting/O ,/O but/O the/O motion/O was/O unanimously/O approved/O ,/O 6-0/O ./O 
And/O since/O July/O 26/O ,/O McCray/PERSON has/O been/O busy/O organizing/O ?/O 
a/O peaceful/O protest/O ./O 
?/O 
?/O 
We/O hope/O it/O goes/O very/O smoothly/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O McCray/PERSON ./O 
?/O 
We?ve/O given/O them/O a/O month?s/O notice/O so/O it/O isn?t/O like/O we?ve/O dropped/O it/O on/O them/O -LRB-/O the/O DOT/O -RRB-/O ./O 
?/O 
McCray/PERSON said/O he/O plans/O to/O hold/O a/O penny/O drive/O at/O the/O Merrimack/LOCATION Transfer/LOCATION Station/LOCATION on/O Aug./O 25/O ./O 
?/O 
Instead/O of/O having/O to/O go/O to/O the/O bank/O ,/O people/O will/O be/O able/O to/O change/O in/O a/O couple/O of/O dollars/O for/O what/O we/O are/O calling/O ?/O 
toll/O revolt/O kits/O ?/O 
,/O ?/O 
said/O McCray/PERSON ./O 
?/O 
The/O toll/O revolt/O kits/O are/O going/O to/O have/O a/O couple/O baggies/O of/O pennies/O in/O it/O ,/O and/O there/O will/O be/O some/O very/O quick/O instructions/O like/O reminding/O people/O to/O remove/O their/O EZPass/O transponders/O and/O about/O safety/O ,/O obeying/O all/O rules/O and/O to/O make/O sure/O everyone/O understands/O that/O this/O is/O only/O meant/O to/O be/O a/O very/O peaceful/O and/O lawful/O protest/O ./O 
?/O 
But/O Boynton/LOCATION sees/O potential/O problems/O ./O 
?/O 
?/O 
I/O would/O be/O a/O little/O concerned/O just/O for/O those/O people/O looking/O to/O get/O from/O point/O A/O to/O point/O B/O in/O a/O reasonable/O amount/O of/O time/O ,/O and/O either/O aren?t/O aware/O of/O what/O is/O going/O on/O or/O aren?t/O necessarily/O in/O agreement/O with/O it/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O Boynton/LOCATION ./O 
?/O 
There/O is/O bound/O to/O be/O frustration/O ./O 
?/O 
Boynton/PERSON said/O the/O DOT?s/ORGANIZATION Turnpike/ORGANIZATION Department/ORGANIZATION has/O held/O discussions/O about/O the/O revolt/O ./O 
?/O 
I/O think/O they/O have/O done/O a/O few/O tests/O since/O publicity/O has/O come/O out/O -LRB-/O about/O the/O revolt/O -RRB-/O and/O the/O exact/O change/O machines/O do/O work/O when/O pennies/O are/O used/O ,/O but/O you/O are/O talking/O about/O a/O much/O longer/O process/O than/O paying/O with/O just/O three/O quarters/O ,/O ?/O 
he/O said/O ./O 
Boynton/LOCATION said/O pennies/O are/O legal/O tender/O ,/O but/O ?/O 
it/O certainly/O would/O take/O a/O while/O for/O each/O transaction/O to/O process/O ,/O and/O so/O that/O in/O and/O of/O itself/O could/O cause/O some/O problems/O even/O if/O the/O machines/O don?t/O jam/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O Boynton/LOCATION ./O 
?/O 
I/O would/O think/O ,/O in/O anticipation/O ,/O that/O they/O would/O staff/O the/O tolls/O more/O heavily/O that/O day/O ./O 
?/O 
McCray/PERSON ,/O who/O received/O more/O than/O 100/O e-mails/O ?/O 
the/O most/O he/O has/O ever/O received/O on/O any/O issue/O in/O town/O ?/O 
said/O there/O are/O only/O a/O few/O ways/O the/O protest/O could/O get/O ugly/O ./O 
?/O 
We?re/O hoping/O to/O have/O no/O issues/O ,/O and/O the/O only/O way/O I/O could/O see/O there/O being/O a/O confrontation/O is/O if/O the/O state/O somehow/O does/O something/O like/O block/O off/O the/O tolls/O or/O all/O of/O a/O sudden/O stop/O us/O from/O being/O able/O to/O use/O pennies/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O McCray/PERSON ./O 
?/O 
If/O we/O are/O not/O allowed/O to/O use/O the/O baskets/O and/O each/O person/O has/O to/O pay/O the/O toll/O collector/O ,/O that?s/O when/O there/O could/O be/O absolute/O chaos/O ./O 
?/O 
McCray/PERSON said/O the/O protest/O is/O to/O bring/O attention/O to/O the/O unfair/O toll/O situation/O the/O town/O has/O been/O dealing/O with/O for/O decades/O ,/O and/O not/O to/O stir/O up/O trouble/O ./O 
?/O 
One/O person/O I/O spoke/O with/O asked/O me/O ,/O ?/O 
Why/O don?t/O you/O hold/O the/O rally/O at/O 5/O p.m./O when/O it/O gets/O busy/O ??/O 
and/O I/O told/O him/O ,/O ?/O 
That?s/O not/O our/O goal/O here/O ,/O ??/O 
said/O McCray/PERSON ./O 
?/O 
This/O country/O was/O founded/O on/O peaceful/O protest/O ,/O and/O that?s/O why/O I/O always/O refer/O to/O the/O Boston/ORGANIZATION Tea/ORGANIZATION Party/ORGANIZATION ./O 
?/O 
All/O we/O want/O to/O do/O is/O have/O people/O throw/O pennies/O in/O that/O day/O ,/O and/O we?re/O not/O saying/O don?t/O pay/O the/O tolls/O because/O that/O would/O be/O wrong/O and/O unlawful/O ./O 
?/O 
As/O part/O of/O the/O protest/O ,/O a/O motorcade/O rally/O has/O been/O scheduled/O for/O noon/O on/O Aug./O 27/O ,/O where/O residents/O will/O leave/O from/O the/O parking/O lot/O at/O Abbie/PERSON Griffin/PERSON Park/PERSON ,/O go/O through/O the/O three/O tolls/O and/O then/O loop/O back/O through/O ,/O said/O McCray/PERSON ./O 
According/O to/O McCray/PERSON ,/O Sen./O Sheila/PERSON Roberge/PERSON and/O Merrimack/LOCATION state/O Rep./O Maureen/PERSON Mooney/PERSON have/O agreed/O to/O take/O part/O in/O the/O protest/O ./O 
?/O 
Sen./O Roberge/PERSON said/O she/O would/O throw/O pennies/O ,/O hold/O signs/O ,/O whatever/O we/O need/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O McCray/PERSON ./O 
?/O 
She?s/O all/O for/O the/O people/O of/O Merrimack/LOCATION ,/O and/O it?s/O great/O we?re/O getting/O full/O support/O from/O our/O state/O delegation/O ./O 
?/O 
But/O Boynton/LOCATION still/O fears/O the/O potential/O traffic/O problems/O that/O could/O be/O created/O during/O the/O rally/O ./O 
?/O 
Any/O time/O you/O constrict/O the/O traffic/O flow/O through/O a/O toll/O facility/O ,/O I/O guess/O that/O raises/O our/O level/O of/O concern/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O Boynton/LOCATION ./O 
In/O the/O event/O of/O severe/O traffic/O jams/O at/O the/O tolls/O ,/O Boynton/LOCATION said/O DOT/O Commissioner/O Chuck/PERSON O?Leary/PERSON would/O have/O the/O authority/O to/O allow/O the/O tolls/O to/O be/O opened/O up/O ,/O but/O that/O it/O is/O only/O used/O in/O extremely/O rare/O situations/O ./O 
While/O Boynton/PERSON understands/O the/O town?s/O frustrations/O over/O the/O tolls/O ,/O he/O isn?t/O so/O sure/O the/O penny/O protest/O is/O the/O most/O effective/O means/O of/O getting/O the/O point/O across/O ./O 
?/O 
Several/O Merrimack/O citizens/O have/O made/O their/O opinions/O known/O on/O this/O for/O quite/O some/O time/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O Boynton/LOCATION ./O 
?/O 
Ultimately/O ,/O any/O change/O that/O takes/O place/O is/O going/O to/O have/O to/O go/O through/O the/O Legislature/ORGANIZATION because/O that/O is/O where/O the/O policy/O is/O made/O and/O ,/O really/O ,/O that?s/O their/O best/O option/O ./O 
?/O 
The/O alternative/O solution/O ,/O however/O ,/O may/O be/O to/O file/O a/O class/O action/O lawsuit/O against/O the/O state/O ,/O said/O Town/ORGANIZATION Councilor/O Nancy/PERSON Harrington/PERSON last/O week/O ./O 
?/O 
I/O feel/O like/O Claremont/LOCATION with/O education/O and/O how/O they/O sued/O the/O state/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O Harrington/PERSON ./O 
?/O 
We/O need/O to/O get/O a/O consensus/O on/O this/O ./O 
?/O 
McCray/PERSON said/O a/O suit/O will/O be/O discussed/O at/O the/O Aug./O 9/O Town/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION meeting/O ./O 
?/O 
For/O 20/O years/O ,/O nothing/O has/O been/O done/O ,/O ?/O 
said/O McCray/PERSON ./O 
?/O 
A/O class/O action/O lawsuit/O is/O not/O going/O to/O hurt/O ./O 
If/O the/O people/O in/O April/O 2008/O -LRB-/O at/O the/O Town/O Deliberative/O Session/O -RRB-/O decide/O to/O sue/O the/O state/O ,/O then/O let?s/O rock/O ./O 
And/O if/O they/O don?t/O ,/O then/O we/O should/O all/O put/O our/O energies/O somewhere/O else/O and/O get/O on/O with/O our/O lives/O ./O 
?/O 
unique_identifier/O Tax/O bill/O paid/O in/O nickels/O and/O dimes/O Fed-up/O resident/O of/O Delaware/LOCATION County/LOCATION stages/O own/O protest/O ./O 
August/O 15/O ,/O 2007/O MUNCIE/LOCATION ,/O Ind./LOCATION -LRB-/O AP/ORGANIZATION -RRB-/O --/O Cary/PERSON Malchow/PERSON was/O so/O upset/O by/O his/O property/O tax/O bill/O he/O decided/O to/O make/O a/O scene/O by/O paying/O it/O --/O all/O $/O 12,656.07/O --/O with/O bags/O of/O change/O and/O $/O 1/O bills/O ./O 
Malchow/PERSON lugged/O the/O cash-filled/O bags/O to/O the/O Delaware/LOCATION County/LOCATION treasurer/O 's/O office/O Monday/O and/O plunked/O them/O onto/O the/O counter/O ./O 
His/O unorthodox/O payment/O stalled/O the/O line/O as/O cashiers/O labored/O to/O count/O it/O by/O hand/O ./O 
``/O I/O did/O it/O so/O people/O can/O physically/O see/O what/O $/O 12,000/O is/O ,/O ''/O said/O Malchow/PERSON ,/O who/O has/O staged/O other/O recent/O protests/O to/O draw/O attention/O to/O Indiana/LOCATION 's/O property/O tax/O increases/O ./O 
Malchow/PERSON arrived/O at/O the/O treasurer/O 's/O office/O about/O 3:30/O p.m./O ,/O with/O the/O money/O covering/O the/O bill/O for/O his/O Muncie/LOCATION home/O ,/O business/O and/O rental/O properties/O ./O 
It/O took/O all/O three/O of/O the/O office/O 's/O cashiers/O 75/O minutes/O to/O count/O out/O the/O cash/O ./O 
County/O Treasurer/O Warren/PERSON Beebe/PERSON said/O cashiers/O had/O to/O work/O overtime/O to/O count/O the/O money/O ,/O guarded/O by/O sheriff/O 's/O deputies/O ./O 
``/O They/O were/O fast/O ,/O they/O were/O hustling/O ./O 
They/O 're/O used/O to/O counting/O money/O ,/O but/O of/O course/O that/O left/O other/O people/O standing/O in/O line/O ./O 
It/O was/O an/O awkward/O situation/O ,/O ''/O Beebe/PERSON said/O Tuesday/O ./O 
Beebe/PERSON said/O the/O tax/O protest/O also/O prevented/O his/O office/O from/O making/O its/O daily/O deposit/O at/O a/O Muncie/LOCATION bank/O ./O 
That/O cost/O the/O county/O an/O estimated/O $/O 1,135.90/O in/O interest/O that/O would/O have/O otherwise/O accrued/O overnight/O by/O depositing/O the/O property/O tax/O payments/O collected/O Monday/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
Property/O taxes/O are/O a/O hot/O topic/O this/O summer/O in/O many/O Indiana/LOCATION communities/O ./O 
On/O average/O ,/O homeowners/O can/O expect/O a/O 24/O percent/O increase/O in/O their/O property/O taxes/O statewide/O this/O year/O ,/O although/O many/O face/O bills/O that/O have/O spiked/O higher/O ./O 
That/O 's/O led/O to/O protests/O and/O complaints/O by/O residents/O who/O call/O the/O increases/O too/O high/O ./O 
Malchow/PERSON said/O that/O when/O people/O pay/O by/O check/O or/O by/O an/O escrow/O account/O through/O a/O bank/O ,/O they/O might/O not/O notice/O the/O amount/O of/O the/O bill/O ./O 
``/O When/O you/O pay/O in/O cash/O ,/O you/O have/O a/O tendency/O to/O feel/O that/O pain/O a/O little/O more/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
Malchow/PERSON 's/O protest/O payment/O came/O a/O few/O days/O after/O state/O officials/O backed/O off/O Gov./O Mitch/PERSON Daniels/PERSON '/O recent/O order/O for/O a/O general/O property/O tax/O reassessment/O in/O Delaware/LOCATION County/LOCATION ./O 
Daniels/PERSON had/O ordered/O that/O all/O property/O be/O reassessed/O there/O and/O in/O Gibson/LOCATION ,/O Marion/PERSON and/O Posey/PERSON counties/O because/O of/O evidence/O that/O high/O percentages/O of/O commercial/O and/or/O industrial/O properties/O were/O undervalued/O ./O 
State/O officials/O now/O believe/O a/O primary/O reason/O that/O Delaware/LOCATION County/LOCATION 's/O residential/O bills/O increased/O significantly/O is/O because/O countywide/O spending/O went/O up/O 10.5/O percent/O this/O year/O ./O 
Malchow/PERSON plans/O to/O pay/O his/O fall/O property/O taxes/O installment/O in/O a/O more/O conventional/O fashion/O ./O 
He/O said/O that/O lugging/O around/O the/O heavy/O loads/O of/O coins/O and/O currency/O that/O he/O obtained/O from/O two/O Muncie/LOCATION banks/O left/O him/O ``/O out/O of/O breath/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Tax/O protester/O pays/O $/O 12,000/O tax/O bill/O in/O change/O ,/O $/O 1/O bills/O Muncie/LOCATION -/O Cary/PERSON Malchow/PERSON of/O Muncie/LOCATION was/O upset/O by/O his/O property/O tax/O bill/O ,/O but/O he/O paid/O it/O ./O 
In/O change/O and/O one-dollar/O bills/O ./O 
All/O $/O 12,656.07/O of/O it/O ./O 
Malchow/PERSON lugged/O the/O cash-filled/O bags/O to/O the/O Delaware/LOCATION County/LOCATION treasurer/O 's/O office/O Monday/O and/O plunked/O them/O onto/O the/O counter/O ./O 
His/O unorthodox/O payment/O stalled/O the/O line/O he/O had/O been/O waiting/O in/O as/O cashiers/O labored/O to/O count/O it/O out/O by/O hand/O ./O 
It/O took/O all/O three/O of/O the/O office/O 's/O cashiers/O 75/O minutes/O to/O count/O out/O the/O cash/O ./O 
Malchow/PERSON says/O he/O did/O it/O so/O people/O could/O see/O what/O $/O 12,000/O is/O ./O 
The/O bill/O was/O for/O taxes/O on/O Malchow/PERSON 's/O Muncie/LOCATION home/O ,/O his/O business/O and/O his/O rental/O properties/O ./O 
Malchow/PERSON has/O staged/O other/O recent/O protests/O to/O draw/O attention/O to/O Indiana/LOCATION 's/O property/O tax/O increases/O ./O 
The/O spring/O installment/O of/O Delware/LOCATION County/LOCATION property/O taxes/O were/O originally/O due/O Monday/O ./O 
That/O due/O date/O has/O been/O pushed/O back/O to/O November/O 13/O ,/O when/O the/O fall/O installment/O is/O also/O due/O ./O 
Delaware/LOCATION County/LOCATION was/O originally/O slated/O for/O a/O reassessment/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O decided/O last/O week/O not/O to/O reassess/O home/O values/O there/O ./O 
County/O officials/O were/O concerned/O that/O a/O reassessment/O would/O result/O in/O even/O higher/O values/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Penny/O protest/O produces/O minor/O disruptions/O in/O Merrimack/LOCATION NH/O August/O 27/O ,/O 2007/O By/O Peter/PERSON Samuel/PERSON Minor/PERSON disruptions/O were/O produced/O yesterday/O in/O a/O toll/O protest/O in/O which/O drivers/O were/O asked/O by/O local/O politicians/O to/O pay/O in/O pennies/O -LRB-/O one/O cent/O pieces/O -RRB-/O in/O Merrimack/LOCATION New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION ./O 
In/O the/O morning/O rush/O hour/O the/O protest/O flopped/O ./O 
Toll/O collectors/O and/O coin/O machines/O appeared/O to/O handle/O the/O penny/O payments/O just/O fine/O ,/O and/O traffic/O flowed/O through/O the/O toll/O plazas/O as/O usual/O ./O 
Motorists/O with/O transponders/O were/O asked/O by/O the/O publicity-seeking/O town/O councillors/O to/O take/O their/O E-ZPass/O transponders/O off/O the/O windshield/O and/O load/O up/O with/O pennies/O to/O block/O the/O toll/O lanes/O ./O 
That/O did/O n't/O work/O either/O ./O 
No/O one/O noticed/O a/O difference/O ./O 
Unusual/O backups/O wanted/O for/O publicity/O failed/O to/O eventuate/O ./O 
However/O at/O lunch/O time/O a/O council/O organized/O cavalcade/O drove/O slowly/O to/O the/O ramp/O toll/O plaza/O and/O caused/O delays/O ./O 
Police/O booked/O two/O motorists/O for/O obstruction/O for/O driving/O below/O 45mph/O on/O the/O Turnpike/O ./O 
One/O was/O town/O council/O chair/O and/O an/O organizer/O of/O the/O disruption/O ,/O David/PERSON McCray/PERSON ./O 
There/O were/O also/O citations/O issued/O for/O stopping/O on/O the/O Turnpike/O in/O the/O absence/O of/O an/O emergency/O and/O walking/O on/O the/O roadway/O ./O 
The/O toll/O protesters/O waved/O posters/O and/O honked/O their/O horns/O ./O 
NHDOT/ORGANIZATION spokesman/O Bill/PERSON Boynton/PERSON said/O the/O protesters/O were/O ``/O not/O adversarial/O ''/O to/O toll/O collectors/O ,/O who/O rather/O enjoyed/O the/O break/O in/O their/O routine/O ./O 
Merrimack/O politicians/O are/O moaning/O about/O people/O in/O Merrimack/LOCATION having/O to/O pay/O tolls/O while/O people/O in/O Nashua/LOCATION to/O the/O south/O and/O Manchester/LOCATION to/O the/O north/O have/O free/O ramps/O ./O 
That/O came/O about/O because/O a/O few/O years/O ago/O they/O had/O no/O ramp/O and/O wanted/O one/O ,/O and/O the/O deal/O reached/O was/O they/O 'd/O get/O their/O ramp/O with/O a/O toll/O ./O 
Now/O they/O 've/O got/O their/O ramp/O they/O want/O to/O welch/O on/O the/O toll/O part/O of/O the/O deal/O ./O 
COMMENT/O :/O The/O obviously/O solution/O is/O for/O the/O Turnpike/O to/O close/O the/O ramp/O at/O Merrimack/LOCATION with/O some/O Jersey/LOCATION barrier/O and/O see/O if/O the/O whiners/O like/O a/O return/O to/O pre-toll/O conditions/O ./O 
But/O seriously/O there/O is/O a/O problem/O with/O partial/O or/O ``/O open/O ''/O toll/O systems/O like/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION 's/O in/O which/O toll/O points/O provide/O for/O some/O trips/O to/O be/O tolled/O and/O others/O free/O within/O the/O same/O facility/O ./O 
The/O presence/O of/O freeloaders/O nurtures/O a/O constant/O sense/O of/O grievance/O among/O those/O paying/O the/O tolls/O ./O 
Miami-Dade/LOCATION ,/O West/LOCATION Virginia/LOCATION Turnpike/LOCATION ,/O Maryland/LOCATION 's/O Kennedy/LOCATION Highway/LOCATION ,/O Delaware/LOCATION Turnpike/LOCATION and/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION are/O all/O like/O this/O ./O 
Also/O increasingly/O the/O Pennsylvania/LOCATION Turnpike/LOCATION ./O 
Everyone/O should/O pay/O when/O they/O use/O a/O tollroad/O ./O 
Bastard/O roads/O half/O toll/O and/O half/O free/O can/O not/O long/O endure/O ,/O as/O Abraham/PERSON Lincoln/PERSON said/O in/O his/O famous/O 1858/O ``/O house/O divided/O ''/O speech/O ./O 
NOTE/O :/O an/O earlier/O report/O was/O based/O on/O the/O lack/O of/O any/O disruption/O during/O the/O morning/O rush/O hour/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O 8/30/2007/O Toll/O protest/O ends/O in/O ticket/O for/O city/O councilman/O in/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION Angry/LOCATION residents/O of/O Merrimack/LOCATION ,/O NH/O ,/O staged/O a/O slow-moving/O protest/O Monday/O ,/O Aug./O 27/O ,/O on/O the/O Everett/PERSON Turnpike/PERSON ./O 
The/O townspeople/O said/O they/O 're/O upset/O that/O the/O only/O practical/O way/O in/O and/O out/O of/O their/O town/O includes/O a/O 50-cent/O toll/O on/O every/O trip/O ./O 
So/O ,/O on/O Monday/O ,/O the/O drivers/O of/O 142/O vehicles/O made/O a/O seven-mile/O ,/O low-speed/O loop/O on/O the/O turnpike/O --/O and/O then/O paid/O their/O tolls/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION Chairman/O David/PERSON McCray/PERSON told/O ``/O Land/O Line/O Now/O ''/O on/O XM/O Satellite/O Radio/O that/O state/O transportation/O officials/O in/O Concord/LOCATION ,/O NH/O ,/O had/O approved/O the/O protest/O --/O but/O that/O he/O was/O ticketed/O anyway/O ./O 
``/O The/O state/O knew/O we/O were/O doing/O this/O motorcade/O ,/O and/O they/O knew/O we/O would/O be/O within/O 35/O to/O 40/O mph/O because/O we/O were/O trying/O to/O keep/O people/O together/O ,/O ''/O McCray/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O From/O the/O very/O beginning/O ,/O the/O police/O were/O lined/O up/O ./O 
They/O saw/O us/O go/O through/O the/O whole/O route/O ./O 
It/O was/O seven/O miles/O roundtrip/O ./O 
When/O I/O pulled/O off/O the/O ramp/O ,/O there/O were/O a/O total/O of/O seven/O cruisers/O and/O a/O police/O helicopter/O waiting/O for/O me/O as/O I/O come/O off/O ./O ''/O 
McCray/PERSON said/O his/O ticket/O was/O for/O going/O under/O the/O minimum/O speed/O of/O 45/O mph/O on/O the/O turnpike/O ./O 
Although/O he/O said/O he/O respects/O the/O job/O of/O law/O enforcement/O ,/O he/O believes/O that/O someone/O high/O up/O in/O command/O was/O ``/O letting/O me/O know/O who/O 's/O boss/O ./O ''/O 
``/O They/O work/O hard/O and/O put/O their/O lives/O on/O the/O line/O everyday/O ./O 
I/O believe/O they/O were/O given/O direction/O ./O 
That/O 's/O my/O opinion/O and/O we/O 're/O all/O entitled/O to/O our/O opinion/O ,/O ''/O McCray/PERSON said/O ./O 
McCray/PERSON said/O others/O in/O the/O protest/O convoy/O donated/O more/O than/O enough/O money/O for/O him/O to/O pay/O the/O $/O 57/O ticket/O ./O 
``/O They/O 've/O already/O paid/O it/O ,/O and/O if/O I/O do/O pay/O it/O ,/O I/O 'll/O pay/O it/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
That/O 's/O what/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O do/O on/O that/O ,/O ''/O McCray/PERSON said/O ./O 
McCray/PERSON said/O New/LOCATION Hampshire/LOCATION Gov./O John/PERSON Lynch/PERSON called/O immediately/O following/O the/O protest/O to/O set/O up/O a/O Sept./O 21/O meeting/O to/O discuss/O the/O toll/O situation/O ./O 
//O --/O By/O Reed/ORGANIZATION Black/ORGANIZATION ,/O staff/O writer/O //O //O reed_black@landlinemag.com/O //O unique_identifier/O Paying/O With/O Pennies/O Lands/O Middle/O Schoolers/O In/O Detention/O By/O consumeristcarey/O March/O 2/O ,/O 2008/O 29/O Readington/ORGANIZATION Middle/ORGANIZATION School/ORGANIZATION students/O earned/O two/O days/O detention/O after/O paying/O for/O their/O lunch/O with/O pennies/O School/O administrators/O took/O the/O penny/O treatment/O a/O sign/O of/O disrespect/O towards/O cafeteria/O workers/O ,/O who/O eventually/O collected/O 5,800/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O At/O first/O it/O started/O out/O as/O a/O joke/O ,/O then/O everyone/O else/O started/O saying/O we/O 're/O protesting/O against/O like/O how/O short/O our/O lunch/O is/O ,/O ''/O student/O Alyssa/PERSON Concannon/PERSON said/O ./O 
Several/O lunch/O ladies/O who/O had/O to/O do/O the/O counting/O did/O n't/O think/O it/O was/O funny/O ,/O even/O though/O some/O of/O the/O students/O put/O the/O coins/O in/O rolls/O ./O 
They/O 're/O not/O authorized/O to/O put/O in/O their/O two/O cents/O but/O school/O officials/O say/O they/O felt/O disrespected/O and/O other/O students/O did/O n't/O get/O to/O eat/O lunch/O ./O 
``/O There/O are/O ways/O to/O express/O yourself/O that/O are/O not/O disruptive/O to/O other/O kids/O and/O disrespectful/O to/O staff/O ,/O ''/O said/O Readington/LOCATION Superintendent/O of/O Schools/O Dr./O Jorden/PERSON Schiff/PERSON ./O 
Eighth/O grader/O Jenny/PERSON Hunt/PERSON said/O in/O hindsight/O ,/O the/O prank/O may/O have/O been/O a/O bad/O idea/O ./O 
``/O Maybe/O we/O should/O have/O thought/O before/O we/O did/O it/O ,/O ''/O Hunt/PERSON said/O ./O 
Student/O Sarah/PERSON Henschel/PERSON added/O :/O ``/O There/O was/O no/O rule/O in/O the/O rulebook/O about/O it/O ./O 
It/O was/O just/O unfair/O ./O 
It/O 's/O U.S./LOCATION currency/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Students/O get/O detention/O for/O paying/O with/O pennies/O by/O */O Sandy/PERSON Maple/PERSON */O Mar/O 2nd/O 2008/O 10:02/O AM/O Some/O people/O collect/O pennies/O in/O jars/O ,/O some/O use/O them/O to/O make/O art/O and/O some/O people/O actually/O use/O them/O to/O pay/O for/O things/O ./O 
Unfortunately/O ,/O using/O pennies/O to/O pay/O for/O lunch/O at/O Readington/ORGANIZATION Middle/ORGANIZATION School/ORGANIZATION in/O New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION can/O get/O you/O in/O trouble/O ./O 
It/O seems/O that/O 29/O eighth-graders/O got/O together/O and/O decided/O to/O all/O pay/O for/O their/O $/O 2/O lunches/O last/O Thursday/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
But/O when/O they/O all/O showed/O up/O with/O pennies/O in/O hand/O ,/O the/O lunch/O ladies/O were/O not/O amused/O ./O 
``/O When/O the/O lunch/O ladies/O caught/O wind/O that/O we/O were/O all/O trying/O to/O pay/O in/O pennies/O ,/O they/O were/O very/O aggravated/O and/O thought/O they/O were/O disrespected/O ,/O ''/O says/O student/O Amanda/PERSON Wolfenden/PERSON ./O 
Superintendent/O Dr./O Jorden/PERSON Schiff/PERSON agrees/O that/O it/O was/O disrespectful/O to/O the/O lunch/O aides/O and/O the/O other/O students/O ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n't/O think/O it/O was/O their/O intention/O to/O do/O much/O harm/O ,/O but/O there/O 's/O consequences/O for/O the/O behavior/O when/O other/O kids/O are/O inconvenienced/O that/O way/O and/O could/O n't/O get/O through/O the/O lunch/O line/O ,/O ''/O Schiff/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O Or/O the/O lunch/O ladies/O having/O to/O count/O thousands/O of/O pennies/O ./O ''/O 
He/O gave/O all/O the/O students/O involved/O two-day/O detentions/O ./O 
The/O students/O think/O the/O punishment/O is/O unfair/O and/O say/O that/O they/O were/O just/O trying/O to/O make/O the/O point/O that/O the/O 30-minutes/O they/O are/O allowed/O for/O lunch/O is/O n't/O long/O enough/O ./O 
``/O There/O 's/O no/O rule/O in/O the/O rule/O book/O that/O states/O that/O pennies/O ca/O n't/O be/O used/O to/O buy/O lunches/O ,/O ''/O eighth-grader/O Sarah/PERSON Henschel/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O We/O never/O thought/O they/O would/O do/O this/O ./O 
We/O thought/O they/O would/O give/O us/O a/O silent/O lunch/O or/O just/O yell/O at/O us/O ./O ''/O 
Some/O parents/O also/O think/O a/O two-day/O detention/O for/O paying/O with/O pennies/O is/O too/O harsh/O ./O 
What/O do/O you/O think/O ?/O 
unique_identifier/O Readington/LOCATION kids/O wo/O n't/O get/O punished/O for/O their/O penny-pay/O protest/O Claire/ORGANIZATION Heininger/Statehouse/ORGANIZATION Bureau/ORGANIZATION By/ORGANIZATION Claire/ORGANIZATION Heininger/Statehouse/ORGANIZATION Bureau/ORGANIZATION The/ORGANIZATION Star-Ledger/ORGANIZATION on/O March/O 03/O ,/O 2008/O at/O 8:30/O AM/O ,/O updated/O March/O 03/O ,/O 2008/O at/O 2:26/O PM/O Frank/PERSON H./PERSON Conlon/The/PERSON Star-LedgerPatrick/PERSON O'Donoghue/PERSON ,/O Andrew/PERSON Garibaldi/PERSON and/O Chris/PERSON Hranj/PERSON -LRB-/O L-R/O -RRB-/O ,/O three/O of/O the/O students/O given/O detention/O for/O buying/O lunch/O with/O pennies/O at/O Readington/ORGANIZATION Middle/ORGANIZATION School/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Three/O days/O after/O they/O were/O punished/O for/O using/O pennies/O to/O pay/O for/O school/O lunch/O ,/O students/O at/O Readington/ORGANIZATION Middle/ORGANIZATION School/ORGANIZATION learned/O they/O would/O not/O have/O to/O serve/O two/O days/O of/O detention/O ,/O so/O long/O as/O their/O parents/O agreed/O ./O 
Parents/O of/O the/O punished/O children/O received/O calls/O from/O administrators/O at/O the/O Hunterdon/LOCATION County/LOCATION school/O Sunday/O informing/O them/O that/O the/O punishments/O --/O handed/O out/O after/O students/O ,/O upset/O with/O the/O amount/O of/O time/O they/O receive/O for/O their/O daily/O lunch/O period/O ,/O protested/O by/O using/O the/O copper-plated/O coins/O --/O would/O not/O be/O enforced/O ,/O unless/O parents/O specifically/O asked/O ./O 
Some/O 29/O seventh/O -/O and/O eighth-graders/O at/O the/O school/O banded/O together/O during/O last/O Thursday/O 's/O 30-minute/O lunch/O period/O and/O paid/O their/O $/O 2.00/O lunch/O price/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
That/O amounted/O to/O 5,800/O individual/O or/O 32/O pounds/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
Administrators/O called/O it/O a/O sign/O of/O disrespect/O to/O cafeteria/O personnel/O and/O fellow/O students/O ,/O and/O punished/O the/O ``/O Readington/ORGANIZATION 29/O ''/O with/O two/O days/O of/O detention/O ./O 
As/O of/O Friday/O afternoon/O ,/O district/O Superintendent/O Jorden/PERSON Schiff/PERSON said/O the/O in-school/O punishments/O would/O stand/O ./O 
But/O Sunday/O night/O ,/O Schiff/PERSON ,/O in/O an/O e-mail/O to/O parents/O said/O he/O was/O ``/O concerned/O ''/O about/O the/O national/O media/O attention/O that/O the/O situation/O received/O ./O 
``/O The/O school/O community/O has/O been/O through/O a/O difficult/O period/O ,/O and/O we/O need/O to/O move/O forward/O ,/O ''/O he/O wrote/O ./O 
``/O We/O discussed/O how/O the/O incident/O has/O been/O blown/O out/O of/O proportion/O and/O how/O it/O has/O affected/O our/O children/O and/O our/O school/O community/O ./O ''/O 
The/O whole/O thing/O ,/O it/O seems/O ,/O was/O a/O miscommunication/O ./O 
``/O When/O the/O children/O were/O asked/O why/O they/O purchased/O their/O lunch/O with/O pennies/O ,/O they/O informed/O the/O administration/O that/O it/O was/O a/O prank/O ,/O ''/O he/O wrote/O ./O 
``/O If/O we/O had/O knowledge/O of/O a/O protest/O ,/O we/O would/O have/O reinforced/O with/O the/O students/O the/O importance/O of/O not/O being/O disrespectful/O and/O would/O have/O begun/O discussions/O about/O the/O issue/O ./O ''/O 
Some/O parents/O ,/O however/O ,/O called/O it/O bowing/O to/O pressure/O ./O 
``/O It/O seems/O like/O they/O are/O trying/O to/O make/O this/O right/O because/O the/O community/O is/O split/O ,/O ''/O said/O Carolyn/PERSON Evans/PERSON ,/O whose/O son/O Matt/PERSON was/O one/O of/O the/O 29/O punished/O ./O 
``/O It/O was/O an/O excessive/O punishment/O ./O ''/O 
According/O to/O students/O and/O parents/O ,/O even/O more/O of/O the/O middle-schoolers/O were/O planning/O to/O join/O in/O ,/O but/O were/O prevented/O by/O time/O constraints/O or/O fear/O of/O repercussion/O ./O 
The/O detentions/O outraged/O many/O of/O the/O parents/O ,/O who/O flooded/O the/O district/O with/O angry/O phone/O calls/O and/O e-mails/O ./O 
On/O Friday/O ,/O in/O a/O sign/O of/O support/O ,/O students/O brought/O their/O lunch/O from/O home/O and/O did/O not/O participate/O in/O RMS/O '/O hot/O lunch/O program/O ./O 
That/O protest/O ,/O students/O said/O ,/O could/O continue/O into/O this/O week/O ./O 
Phone/O messages/O left/O with/O Schiff/PERSON and/O Principal/O Catherine/PERSON Hollinger/PERSON were/O not/O returned/O Sunday/O night/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O School/O district/O backs/O off/O after/O penny/O protest/O Students/O get/O pardon/O after/O paying/O for/O lunch/O with/O pennies/O updated/O 3/3/2008/O 11:39:39/O AM/O ET/O 2008-03-03T16/O :39:39/O READINGTON/LOCATION TOWNSHIP/LOCATION ,/O N.J./LOCATION --/O Twenty-nine/O New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION students/O punished/O with/O two-day/O detentions/O after/O they/O used/O pennies/O to/O pay/O for/O their/O $/O 2/O lunches/O are/O getting/O a/O pardon/O ./O 
Readington/LOCATION ,/O N.J./LOCATION ,/O school/O Superintendent/O Jorden/PERSON Schiff/PERSON informed/O parents/O in/O an/O e-mail/O Sunday/O that/O he/O has/O rescinded/O the/O after-school/O detentions/O ./O 
They/O will/O only/O be/O restored/O if/O parents/O ask/O that/O their/O children/O serve/O them/O ./O 
Officials/O say/O a/O group/O of/O middle/O school/O students/O upset/O by/O their/O shortened/O lunch/O period/O paid/O for/O their/O meals/O with/O pennies/O Thursday/O ./O 
Schiff/PERSON gave/O them/O detentions/O for/O slowing/O down/O the/O lunch/O line/O and/O disrespecting/O cafeteria/O workers/O ./O 
In/O his/O e-mail/O ,/O Schiff/PERSON said/O the/O students/O described/O their/O actions/O as/O a/O prank/O and/O that/O news/O reports/O inaccurately/O called/O it/O a/O protest/O ./O 
Several/O parents/O had/O complained/O the/O punishment/O was/O too/O harsh/O ,/O but/O though/O some/O thought/O it/O too/O lenient/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Some/O parents/O prefer/O punishment/O for/O pupils/O paying/O in/O pennies/O Barry/PERSON Carter/PERSON |/O The/O Star-Ledger/O By/O Barry/PERSON Carter/PERSON |/O The/O Star-Ledger/O The/O Star-Ledger/O Email/O the/O author/O |/O Follow/O on/O Twitter/O on/O March/O 03/O ,/O 2008/O at/O 1:34/O PM/O ,/O updated/O March/O 03/O ,/O 2008/O at/O 2:45/O PM/O Eight/O students/O will/O serve/O detention/O for/O using/O pennies/O to/O pay/O for/O their/O lunches/O at/O a/O Hunterdon/LOCATION County/LOCATION middle/O school/O ,/O school/O officials/O said/O today/O ./O 
Parents/O of/O five/O students/O at/O the/O Readington/ORGANIZATION Middle/ORGANIZATION School/ORGANIZATION agreed/O their/O children/O should/O serve/O two/O days/O of/O detention/O ,/O and/O another/O three/O should/O serve/O only/O one/O day/O ,/O after/O the/O decision/O of/O going/O forward/O with/O the/O punishment/O was/O left/O to/O them/O this/O weekend/O ,/O said/O school/O Superintendent/O Jorden/PERSON Schiff/PERSON ./O 
The/O school/O had/O argued/O the/O original/O 29/O students/O who/O used/O pennies/O to/O pay/O for/O their/O $/O 2/O lunches/O on/O Thursday/O were/O playing/O a/O prank/O ./O 
However/O ,/O parents/O defended/O the/O students/O ,/O saying/O the/O pennies/O were/O paid/O in/O protest/O of/O a/O 30-minute/O lunch/O period/O ,/O sparking/O national/O media/O attention/O ./O 
The/O school/O backed/O off/O the/O punishment/O three/O days/O after/O the/O news/O reports/O ,/O leaving/O it/O up/O to/O parents/O if/O they/O still/O wanted/O their/O children/O to/O serve/O detention/O ./O 
Schiff/PERSON said/O the/O attention/O had/O become/O a/O distraction/O that/O hurt/O the/O school/O and/O the/O children/O ./O 
``/O We/O are/O concerned/O about/O the/O widespread/O focus/O and/O attention/O paid/O to/O this/O event/O ,/O ''/O Schiff/PERSON and/O Principal/O Catherine/PERSON Hollinger/PERSON wrote/O in/O a/O letter/O addressed/O to/O parents/O this/O morning/O ,/O which/O beckoned/O all/O to/O ``/O move/O forward/O ./O ''/O 
Those/O parents/O who/O did/O not/O want/O detention/O for/O their/O children/O either/O spoke/O to/O their/O children/O at/O home/O or/O were/O working/O with/O the/O administration/O on/O an/O alternative/O that/O would/O replace/O the/O punishment/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O letter/O ./O 
A/O new/O program/O also/O is/O in/O the/O works/O to/O give/O children/O an/O outlet/O for/O protest/O ,/O Schiff/PERSON said/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O $/O 200/O parking/O ticket/O paid/O in/O coins/O A/O disgruntled/O resident/O of/O central/O Israel/LOCATION paid/O a/O NIS/O 845/O -LRB-/O $/O 215/O -RRB-/O parking/O ticket/O in/O coins/O ,/O after/O he/O said/O police/O failed/O to/O inform/O him/O that/O the/O initial/O NIS/O 100/O -LRB-/O $/O 25/O -RRB-/O penalty/O had/O been/O raised/O ./O 
In/O a/O video/O aired/O on/O Channel/O 2/O ,/O Lioz/PERSON Cohen/PERSON of/O Rishon/ORGANIZATION Lezion/O is/O shown/O displaying/O the/O coins/O to/O a/O taken-aback/O collector/O ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O if/O I/O can/O accept/O it/O ,/O ''/O the/O police/O representative/O says/O ./O 
``/O You/O can/O accept/O it/O ,/O it/O 's/O cash/O ,/O ''/O the/O passive/O aggressive/O ticket-holder/O replies/O ./O 
Cohen/PERSON told/O Channel/O 2/O the/O piles/O of/O coins/O comprised/O primarily/O ten/O agorot/O -LRB-/O $/O 0.03/O -RRB-/O ,/O half-shekel/O coins/O -LRB-/O $/O 0.13/O -RRB-/O ,/O and/O shekel/O coins/O -LRB-/O $/O 0.25/O -RRB-/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O the/O simplest/O thing/O in/O the/O world/O ,/O ''/O he/O says/O ./O 
``/O You/O go/O break/O NIS/O 850/O at/O the/O bank/O ./O 
At/O the/O bank/O they/O also/O get/O angry/O at/O you/O ,/O but/O they/O make/O the/O change/O ,/O they/O have/O to/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Students/O pardoned/O March/O 04/O ,/O 2008/O |/O By/O FROM/O NEWS/O SERVICES/O Twenty-nine/O students/O punished/O with/O two-day/O detentions/O after/O they/O used/O pennies/O to/O pay/O for/O their/O $/O 2/O lunches/O are/O getting/O a/O pardon/O ./O 
Officials/O say/O a/O group/O of/O middle/O school/O students/O upset/O by/O their/O shortened/O lunch/O period/O paid/O for/O their/O meals/O with/O pennies/O on/O Thursday/O ./O 
Readington/LOCATION ,/O N.J./LOCATION ,/O school/O Superintendent/O Jorden/PERSON Schiff/PERSON gave/O them/O detentions/O for/O slowing/O down/O the/O lunch/O line/O and/O disrespecting/O cafeteria/O workers/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Seal/O protesters/O '/O bail/O paid/O in/O coins/O |/O The/O Australian/O Wayback/O Machine/O The/O Australian/O September/O 25/O ,/O 2008/O 05:47/O pm/O AEST/O Seal/O protesters/O '/O bail/O paid/O in/O coins/O By/O Michelle/PERSON Draper/PERSON |/O //O April/O 15/O ,/O 2008/O //O */O WHEN/O Canadian/O authorities/O set/O bail/O for/O two/O crew/O members/O arrested/O after/O their/O anti-sealing/O vessel/O was/O seized/O ,/O they/O probably/O did/O n't/O expect/O to/O be/O buried/O under/O a/O mountain/O of/O coins/O ./O 
*/O But/O one/O can/O only/O assume/O their/O surprise/O when/O the/O head/O of/O the/O Sea/ORGANIZATION Shepherd/ORGANIZATION Conservation/ORGANIZATION Society/ORGANIZATION ,/O Paul/PERSON Watson/PERSON ,/O dumped/O a/O pile/O of/O Canadian/O coins/O amounting/O to/O $/O 10,582/O to/O post/O bail/O ./O 
Mr/O Watson/PERSON said/O today/O he/O used/O 5000/O Canadian/O $/O 2/O coins/O to/O pay/O for/O the/O release/O of/O the/O Dutch/O captain/O of/O the/O //O Farley/PERSON Mowat/PERSON //O and/O its/O first/O officer/O ./O 
The/O pair/O were/O charged/O and/O released/O on/O bail/O to/O face/O a/O Canadian/O court/O on/O May/O 1/O ./O 
Mr/O Watson/PERSON said/O the/O payment/O amounted/O to/O ``/O ransom/O ,/O not/O bail/O ''/O and/O that/O all/O the/O other/O crew/O members/O who/O escaped/O charges/O had/O not/O had/O their/O property/O returned/O ./O 
``/O That/O 's/O piracy/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
The/O //O Farley/PERSON Mowat/PERSON //O was/O trailing/O Canadian/O seal/O hunters/O off/O Canada/LOCATION 's/O Nova/LOCATION Scotia/LOCATION coast/O when/O authorities/O boarded/O it/O on/O Saturday/O ./O 
The/O two/O men/O were/O charged/O with/O being/O in/O Canadian/O waters/O and/O interfering/O with/O a/O seal/O hunt/O ,/O a/O Melbourne-based/O Sea/ORGANIZATION Shepherd/ORGANIZATION spokesman/O Benjamin/PERSON Baldwin/PERSON said/O yesterday/O ./O 
The/O group/O said/O its/O ship/O was/O in/O international/O waters/O ./O 
The/O Sea/O Shepherd/O organisation/O says/O 275,000/O baby/O harp/O seals/O are/O ``/O brutally/O killed/O ''/O each/O year/O ./O 
Mr/O Watson/PERSON became/O the/O face/O of/O the/O Sea/O Shepherd/O 's/O recent/O protests/O in/O the/O Southern/LOCATION Ocean/LOCATION to/O stop/O Japanese/O whaling/O ./O 
Two/O Sea/O Shepherd/O protesters/O boarded/O the/O Japanese/O vessel/O //O Nisshin/ORGANIZATION Maru/ORGANIZATION //O ,/O sparking/O a/O diplomatic/O row/O between/O Australia/LOCATION and/O Japan/LOCATION to/O secure/O the/O activists/O '/O release/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Paying/O Your/O Verizon/O Bill/O With/O Cash/O ?/O 
That/O 'll/O Be/O $/O 3.99/O Extra/O By/O consumeristcarey/O June/O 7/O ,/O 2008/O Employees/O at/O the/O Verizon/ORGANIZATION store/O in/O Millington/LOCATION ,/O Tennessee/LOCATION told/O reader/O Josh/PERSON it/O would/O cost/O an/O extra/O $/O 3.99/O to/O pay/O his/O bill/O with/O cash/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O employees/O ,/O the/O charge/O was/O to/O offset/O the/O cost/O of/O ``/O new/O money/O software/O ./O ''/O 
Josh/PERSON writes/O :/O Just/O a/O few/O days/O ago/O ,/O I/O took/O my/O bill/O to/O the/O Verizon/ORGANIZATION wireless/O store/O in/O my/O hometown/O of/O Millington/PERSON ,/O TN/O ./O 
I/O had/O just/O cashed/O my/O paycheck/O and/O my/O bill/O was/O due/O ,/O so/O I/O decided/O to/O pay/O it/O ./O 
My/O bill/O looks/O somewhat/O like/O this/O :/O Monthly/O Access/O Charges/O :/O $/O 55.31/O Usage/ORGANIZATION Charges/ORGANIZATION Voice/ORGANIZATION Data/ORGANIZATION :/O $/O 3.39/O Verizon/ORGANIZATION Wireless/ORGANIZATION '/O Surcharges/O 's/O and/O Other/O Charges/O &/O Credits/O $/O 1.80/O Taxes/O ,/O Government/ORGANIZATION Surcharges/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION Fees/ORGANIZATION $/O 5.44/O Total/O Current/O Charges/O $/O 66.54/O So/O ,/O I/O assumed/O that/O I/O would/O need/O to/O pay/O $/O 66.54/O ,/O as/O stated/O on/O my/O bill/O ./O 
I/O entered/O the/O store/O and/O waited/O nicely/O for/O about/O 15/O minutes/O while/O the/O salesman/O discussed/O the/O merits/O of/O a/O newer/O bluetooth/O headset/O with/O a/O gentleman/O ./O 
When/O I/O made/O it/O to/O the/O counter/O ,/O I/O explained/O that/O I/O was/O just/O here/O to/O pay/O my/O bill/O ./O 
He/O brought/O up/O my/O information/O ,/O told/O me/O how/O much/O my/O bill/O was/O ,/O and/O I/O began/O to/O count/O out/O four/O twenties/O from/O my/O wallet/O ./O 
Before/O I/O handed/O the/O money/O over/O ,/O he/O explained/O that/O there/O is/O a/O $/O 3.99/O charge/O for/O using/O cash/O ./O 
I/O held/O onto/O the/O money/O and/O pointed/O out/O that/O my/O bill/O was/O for/O $/O 66.54/O ./O 
I/O also/O pointed/O out/O that/O I/O was/O paying/O in/O CASH/O and/O it/O is/O legal/O tender/O that/O Verizon/ORGANIZATION is/O obligated/O to/O honor/O ./O 
The/O young/O man/O explained/O to/O me/O that/O the/O store/O had/O new/O money/O software/O ./O 
The/O fee/O to/O use/O cash/O was/O to/O pay/O for/O that/O software/O ./O 
If/O I/O had/O exact/O change/O ,/O I/O would/O have/O given/O only/O the/O amount/O to/O cover/O the/O bill/O ,/O but/O I/O only/O had/O twenties/O at/O the/O time/O ./O 
So/O I/O left/O with/O an/O unpaid/O bill/O ./O 
I/O absolutely/O refuse/O to/O be/O nickeled/O and/O dimed/O like/O that/O ./O 
So/O how/O do/O I/O pay/O Verizon/ORGANIZATION in/O legal/O tender/O without/O paying/O for/O the/O privilege/O ?/O 
New/O money/O software/O ?/O 
For/O what/O ,/O the/O cash/O register/O ?/O 
Our/O guess/O is/O that/O a/O misguided/O Tennessee/LOCATION youth/O was/O trying/O to/O pocket/O $/O 4/O ./O 
Verizon/ORGANIZATION always/O places/O high/O in/O our/O personal/O bracket/O for/O Worst/ORGANIZATION Company/ORGANIZATION in/O America/LOCATION ,/O but/O charging/O for/O the/O privilege/O of/O accepting/O cash/O is/O cartoonishly/O evil/O ,/O and/O slightly/O beyond/O Verizon/ORGANIZATION 's/O capable/O and/O experienced/O reach/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O tries/O to/O pay/O fine/O with/O 5,000/O pennies/O A/O penny/O does/O n't/O buy/O much/O today/O ./O 
But/O one/O man/O hoped/O 5,000/O pennies/O thrown/O into/O a/O box/O with/O packing/O peanuts/O could/O help/O pay/O his/O fine/O ./O 
Municipal/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION officials/O said/O no/O ./O 
*/O By/O Benjamin/PERSON Duer/PERSON */O Washington/LOCATION Times-Reporter/O -/O Washington/LOCATION ,/O IL/O By/O Benjamin/PERSON Duer/PERSON Posted/O Aug./O 24/O ,/O 2008/O at/O 12:01/O AM/O Massillon/LOCATION ,/O Ohio/LOCATION A/O penny/O does/O n't/O buy/O much/O today/O ./O 
But/O one/O man/O hoped/O 5,000/O pennies/O thrown/O into/O a/O box/O with/O packing/O peanuts/O could/O help/O pay/O his/O fine/O ./O 
Municipal/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION officials/O said/O no/O ./O 
Philip/PERSON B./PERSON Simer/PERSON ,/O 27/O ,/O of/O Massillon/LOCATION ,/O said/O he/O spent/O $/O 14.31/O to/O mail/O first-class/O his/O penny/O payment/O to/O Municipal/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION ./O 
That/O delivery/O arrived/O Friday/O ./O 
Simer/PERSON tried/O to/O make/O a/O statement/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O tired/O not/O just/O me/O ,/O but/O other/O people/O in/O Massillon/LOCATION of/O getting/O treated/O like/O crap/O by/O -LRB-/O the/O court/O -RRB-/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
Earlier/O this/O month/O ,/O Simer/PERSON was/O found/O guilty/O of/O two/O traffic/O violations/O ./O 
He/O was/O ordered/O to/O pay/O $/O 243/O or/O $/O 50/O every/O two/O weeks/O in/O fines/O and/O court/O costs/O ./O 
His/O first/O $/O 50/O payment/O was/O due/O ./O 
That/O payment/O all/O in/O pennies/O arrived/O in/O a/O heavy/O ,/O large/O brown/O box/O ./O 
A/O postal/O worker/O needed/O a/O dolly/O to/O deliver/O the/O package/O ,/O addressed/O to/O Judge/O Edward/PERSON J./PERSON Elum/PERSON ./O 
But/O the/O package/O was/O refused/O ./O 
Elum/PERSON said/O the/O court/O can/O not/O accept/O payments/O ,/O only/O the/O clerk/O of/O courts/O can/O ./O 
Deputy/O Clerk/O of/O Court/O Shane/PERSON Jackson/PERSON said/O his/O office/O would/O have/O rejected/O the/O payment/O ,/O too/O ,/O citing/O an/O appellate/O decision/O that/O allows/O them/O to/O reject/O coin-only/O payments/O ./O 
Court/O officials/O sent/O the/O package/O back/O ./O 
Simer/PERSON said/O pennies/O are/O legal/O ,/O so/O the/O court/O should/O accept/O them/O ./O 
He/O said/O he/O has/O no/O intention/O of/O paying/O the/O court/O in/O anything/O but/O pennies/O ./O 
//O The/O Repository/O //O unique_identifier/O Michael/PERSON 's/O :/O ``/O It/O 's/O Store/O Policy/O Not/O To/O Accept/O Change/O ''/O By/O consumeristcarey/O September/O 27/O ,/O 2008/O Hayden/PERSON wanted/O to/O buy/O a/O $/O 4/O wood/O plaque/O for/O his/O mother/O as/O part/O of/O a/O last-minute/O birthday/O gift/O ,/O but/O Michael/PERSON 's/O would/O n't/O accept/O 16/O quarters/O as/O payment/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O store/O policy/O not/O to/O accept/O change/O ,/O ''/O a/O cashier/O explained/O ,/O forcing/O an/O embarrassed/O Hayden/PERSON to/O borrow/O a/O few/O bucks/O from/O his/O younger/O sister/O ./O 
Hayden/PERSON writes/O :/O I/O recently/O went/O to/O Michael/PERSON 's/O in/O Hemet/LOCATION ,/O California/LOCATION to/O make/O a/O last/O minute/O birthday/O present/O for/O my/O mother/O ./O 
I/O did/O n't/O have/O money/O on/O me/O at/O the/O time/O and/O the/O bank/O was/O closed/O so/O I/O had/O to/O use/O 4/O dollars/O in/O quarters/O to/O buy/O a/O wood/O plaque/O ./O 
When/O I/O went/O to/O check/O out/O ,/O an/O older/O woman/O told/O me/O ``/O It/O 's/O story/O policy/O not/O to/O accept/O change/O ./O ''/O 
Is/O it/O really/O legal/O for/O a/O store/O to/O not/O accept/O change/O ?/O 
It/O 's/O still/O legal/O tender/O ,/O and/O it/O 's/O not/O as/O if/O I/O was/O paying/O in/O pennies/O ;/O it/O was/O quarters/O and/O I/O was/O counting/O them/O out/O for/O the/O cashier/O ./O 
I/O was/O in/O a/O hurry/O so/O I/O had/O to/O borrow/O money/O from/O my/O younger/O sister/O to/O buy/O it/O ,/O which/O was/O pretty/O embarrassing/O ./O 
Michael/PERSON 's/O is/O about/O 10/O miles/O farther/O from/O my/O house/O than/O Joanne/PERSON 's/O ,/O but/O needless/O to/O say/O I/O 'm/O not/O going/O back/O ./O 
At/O least/O Joanne/PERSON 's/O accepts/O legal/O money/O ./O 
It/O 's/O not/O like/O this/O in/O other/O countries/O ./O 
Watch/O here/O as/O a/O pair/O of/O Marines/O try/O to/O shock/O an/O unsuspecting/O Japanese/O waitress/O by/O paying/O for/O their/O whole/O meal/O with/O //O nothing/O but/O change/O //O :/O It/O 's/O not/O an/O issue/O because/O it/O 's/O not/O unreasonable/O to/O ask/O employees/O to/O count/O change/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Store/O policy/O stops/O Michaels/PERSON from/O taking/O quarters/O as/O payment/O Josh/PERSON Smith/PERSON Sep/O 29th/O 2008/O 3:30/O PM/O Updated/O Sep/O 30th/O 2008/O 7:46/O PM/O Michaels/PERSON ,/O a/O craft/O store/O with/O over/O 900/O locations/O in/O the/O U.S./LOCATION and/O Canada/LOCATION ,/O or/O at/O least/O one/O of/O its/O stores/O has/O taken/O a/O unique/O view/O on/O change/O ./O 
Recently/O the/O Michaels/PERSON in/O Hernet/LOCATION California/LOCATION would/O n't/O let/O Hayden/PERSON ,/O who/O was/O shopping/O for/O her/O mother/O 's/O birthday/O present/O ,/O pay/O for/O a/O $/O 4/O purchase/O in/O quarters/O ./O 
When/O she/O began/O counting/O out/O the/O 16/O coins/O for/O the/O cashier/O she/O was/O informed/O that/O it/O was/O store/O policy/O not/O to/O accept/O change/O forcing/O Hayden/PERSON to/O borrow/O the/O cash/O from/O her/O younger/O sister/O to/O ensure/O a/O happy/O birthday/O for/O her/O mom/O ./O 
I/O 've/O put/O in/O an/O email/O to/O Michaels/PERSON to/O find/O out/O if/O this/O ridiculous/O policy/O is/O in/O fact/O store/O policy/O or/O simply/O an/O employee/O exercising/O poor/O customer/O service/O but/O I/O have/O n't/O heard/O back/O from/O them/O yet/O ./O 
Even/O if/O such/O a/O policy/O exists/O ,/O refusing/O to/O take/O 16/O quarters/O for/O a/O purchase/O is/O simply/O lazy/O ;/O I/O can/O see/O the/O same/O cashier/O refusing/O to/O take/O 16/O singles/O next/O week/O becasue/O countign/O them/O is/O too/O hard/O ./O 
Turning/O down/O this/O small/O of/O a/O quantity/O of/O change/O would/O obviously/O violate/O the/O spirit/O of/O any/O such/O policy/O ./O 
If/O like/O me/O you/O wondered/O how/O a/O store/O can/O refuse/O a/O government/O issued/O coin/O ,/O which/O is/O >/O Michaels/O ,/O a/O craft/O store/O with/O over/O 900/O locations/O in/O the/O U.S./LOCATION and/O Canada/LOCATION ,/O has/O taken/O a/O rather/O unique/O view/O on/O change/O --/O or/O at/O least/O one/O store/O has/O ./O 
Recently/O the/O Michaels/PERSON in/O Hemet/LOCATION ,/O California/LOCATION would/O n't/O let/O a/O youngster/O ,/O who/O was/O shopping/O for/O her/O mother/O 's/O birthday/O present/O ,/O pay/O for/O a/O $/O 4/O purchase/O in/O quarters/O ./O 
When/O she/O began/O counting/O out/O the/O 16/O coins/O for/O the/O cashier/O she/O was/O informed/O that/O it/O was/O store/O policy/O not/O to/O accept/O change/O ./O 
This/O forced/O Hayden/PERSON to/O borrow/O from/O her/O younger/O sister/O in/O order/O to/O ensure/O a/O happy/O birthday/O for/O her/O mom/O ./O 
I/O 've/O put/O in/O an/O email/O to/O Michaels/PERSON to/O find/O out/O if/O this/O ridiculous/O policy/O is/O in/O fact/O store/O policy/O ,/O or/O simply/O an/O employee/O exercising/O poor/O customer/O service/O ,/O but/O I/O have/O n't/O heard/O back/O from/O them/O yet/O ./O 
Even/O if/O such/O a/O policy/O exists/O ,/O refusing/O to/O take/O 16/O quarters/O for/O a/O purchase/O is/O simply/O lazy/O ./O 
I/O can/O see/O the/O same/O cashier/O refusing/O to/O take/O 16/O singles/O next/O week/O because/O counting/O them/O would/O be/O too/O much/O of/O an/O inconvenience/O ./O 
Turning/O down/O this/O small/O of/O a/O quantity/O of/O change/O would/O obviously/O violate/O the/O spirit/O of/O any/O such/O policy/O if/O one/O exists/O ./O 
If/O like/O me/O you/O wondered/O how/O a/O store/O can/O refuse/O a/O government/O issued/O coin/O ,/O which/O is/O ``/O legal/O tender/O for/O all/O debts/O public/O and/O private/O ''/O it/O 's/O because/O while/O these/O coins/O can/O be/O used/O to/O satisfy/O any/O debt/O ,/O private/O businesses/O do/O not/O have/O to/O accept/O them/O ./O 
</O http://www.ustreas.gov/education/faq/currency/legal-tender.html#q1/O >/O The/O Coinage/O act/O of/O 1965/O set/O this/O policy/O into/O place/O meaning/O that/O coins/O and/O bills/O are/O a/O legal/O means/O of/O paying/O a/O creditor/O but/O allowing/O private/O businesses/O to/O set/O rules/O on/O forms/O of/O payment/O on/O their/O own/O ./O 
I/O can/O understand/O how/O at/O some/O point/O a/O store/O might/O say/O that/O they/O wo/O n't/O take/O accept/O pennies/O for/O items/O over/O $/O 20/O since/O it/O can/O hold/O up/O all/O of/O the/O other/O customers/O ./O 
Aside/O from/O any/O store/O policy/O it/O 's/O downright/O rude/O to/O pay/O for/O high/O ticket/O items/O only/O in/O change/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O sure/O if/O you/O had/O asked/O me/O whether/O stores/O should/O ban/O all/O coin/O purchases/O 8/O years/O ago/O while/O I/O was/O busy/O counting/O out/O $/O 50/O worth/O in/O my/O Kmart/ORGANIZATION vest/O I/O would/O have/O agreed/O with/O you/O but/O stores/O should/O n't/O be/O banning/O reasonable/O amounts/O of/O change/O ./O 
I/O think/O business/O need/O to/O remember/O ,/O money/O is/O money/O ,/O no/O matter/O how/O small/O and/O customer/O service/O is/O the/O most/O important/O of/O all/O ./O 
Taking/O change/O is/O simply/O good/O business/O and/O when/O many/O retailers/O are/O suffering/O poor/O same/O store/O sales/O ;/O refusing/O to/O take/O cash/O of/O any/O kind/O is/O a/O surefire/O way/O to/O fail/O !/O 
unique_identifier/O Santa/LOCATION Cruz/LOCATION man/O ,/O 74/O ,/O tries/O to/O pay/O parking/O tickets/O with/O 30,000/O pennies/O By/O Jennifer/PERSON Squires/PERSON Santa/PERSON Cruz/PERSON Sentinel/O Posted/O :/O 10/16/2008/O 02:39:47/O PM/O PDT/O Updated/O :/O 10/16/2008/O 10:19:23/O PM/O PDT/O Robert/PERSON Havens/PERSON ,/O 74/O ,/O had/O a/O first/O recently/O at/O the/O Lee/LOCATION Street/LOCATION home/O he/O 's/O lived/O in/O for/O nearly/O a/O half-century/O ./O 
He/O got/O parking/O tickets/O ./O 
So/O he/O tried/O to/O pay/O them/O with/O 30,000/O pennies/O ./O 
Havens/O has/O several/O vehicles/O that/O do/O n't/O all/O fit/O in/O his/O driveway/O ./O 
So/O he/O parks/O his/O motor/O home/O ,/O dump/O truck/O and/O flat/O bed/O on/O the/O quiet/O neighborhood/O street/O off/O Emeline/LOCATION Avenue/LOCATION ./O 
A/O city/O ordinance/O states/O vehicles/O parked/O on/O public/O streets/O must/O be/O moved/O every/O 72/O hours/O --/O a/O rule/O to/O prevent/O people/O from/O storing/O or/O abandoning/O their/O cars/O on/O streets/O --/O and/O Havens/PERSON said/O that/O 's/O a/O dance/O he/O 's/O gotten/O used/O to/O ./O 
He/O said/O he/O moves/O his/O vehicles/O every/O time/O a/O city/O parking/O officer/O or/O police/O community/O service/O officer/O marks/O his/O tires/O ./O 
Havens/O had/O escaped/O parking/O problems/O until/O this/O fall/O ,/O when/O he/O found/O three/O tickets/O on/O three/O vehicles/O after/O spending/O a/O long/O weekend/O visiting/O his/O son/O in/O Modesto/LOCATION ./O 
He/O racked/O up/O three/O $/O 100/O parking/O tickets/O ./O 
He/O plans/O to/O contest/O the/O tickets/O ,/O but/O the/O city/O requires/O people/O to/O pay/O their/O parking/O fines/O before/O an/O appeal/O hearing/O is/O scheduled/O ./O 
So/O in/O protest/O he/O tried/O to/O pay/O the/O fine/O in/O pennies/O Wednesday/O ./O 
He/O went/O to/O four/O banks/O to/O exchange/O a/O portion/O of/O his/O Social/ORGANIZATION Security/ORGANIZATION check/O for/O 30,000/O pennies/O ,/O which/O he/O delivered/O to/O the/O downtown/O parking/O office/O Wednesday/O afternoon/O ./O 
Havens/O anticipated/O a/O showdown/O :/O ``/O I/O know/O they/O 're/O going/O to/O have/O a/O fit/O --/O for/O sure/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O before/O rolling/O the/O 180/O pounds/O of/O pennies/O the/O block/O and/O a/O half/O from/O his/O car/O to/O the/O parking/O office/O on/O Locust/LOCATION Street/LOCATION ./O 
After/O parking/O office/O supervisor/O Claudia/PERSON Carlson/PERSON told/O him/O coins/O were/O n't/O an/O acceptable/O form/O of/O payment/O --/O the/O office/O does/O n't/O take/O loose/O change/O ,/O not/O just/O Havens/O '/O 30,000/O pennies/O --/O he/O reluctantly/O rolled/O the/O dolly/O of/O buckets/O back/O to/O his/O car/O ./O 
``/O Ha/O ha/O ,/O I/O knew/O that/O was/O coming/O ,/O ''/O Havens/O said/O ./O 
But/O his/O real/O disappointment/O was/O the/O lack/O of/O resolution/O to/O the/O parking/O problems/O in/O his/O neighborhood/O ./O 
When/O the/O pennies/O were/O n't/O accepted/O ,/O he/O was/O given/O until/O 5/O p.m./O Wednesday/O to/O pay/O the/O $/O 300/O fine/O and/O decided/O not/O to/O ./O 
By/O not/O making/O the/O payment/O ,/O Havens/O '/O hearing/O to/O appeal/O the/O tickets/O was/O n't/O scheduled/O ./O 
He/O 's/O not/O sure/O what/O will/O happen/O next/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O let/O it/O go/O to/O the/O next/O level/O ,/O whatever/O that/O is/O ,/O ''/O Havens/O said/O ,/O speculating/O that/O a/O warrant/O may/O be/O issued/O for/O his/O arrest/O ./O 
``/O I/O guess/O I/O 'll/O find/O out/O ./O ''/O 
But/O Havens/O did/O make/O one/O decision/O Wednesday/O :/O to/O deposit/O the/O pennies/O in/O his/O granddaughter/O 's/O bank/O account/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O pays/O property/O taxes/O with/O 400/O pounds/O of/O coins/O Josh/PERSON Smith/PERSON </O //O writers/josh-smith/O //O >/O Dec/O 22nd/O 2008/O 11:00/O AM/O Following/O the/O examples/O of/O upset/O individuals/O everywhere/O ,/O Frank/PERSON Alford/PERSON of/O New/LOCATION Albany/LOCATION is/O paying/O his/O property/O taxes/O in/O coins/O to/O protest/O the/O skyrocketing/O property/O tax/O rates/O !/O 
Rates/O in/O New/LOCATION Albany/LOCATION have/O increased/O almost/O 50/O %/O since/O 2006/O ,/O and/O while/O single/O home/O owners/O have/O received/O some/O relief/O thanks/O to/O recent/O legislation/O ,/O individuals/O who/O own/O multiple/O rental/O properties/O like/O Frank/PERSON have/O been/O left/O in/O the/O cold/O ./O 
This/O is/O n't/O the/O first/O time/O Frank/PERSON has/O used/O a/O small/O denomination/O to/O pay/O his/O property/O tax/O bill/O --/O which/O came/O to/O $/O 21,000/O this/O year/O !/O 
The/O county/O clerk/O recognized/O Frank/PERSON because/O he/O paid/O in/O singles/O last/O year/O ./O 
This/O year/O he/O hauled/O in/O a/O trash/O can/O containing/O approximately/O 400/O pounds/O of/O Susan/PERSON B./PERSON Anthony/PERSON coins/O to/O pay/O his/O debt/O to/O the/O county/O ,/O while/O carrying/O a/O sign/O that/O read/O ,/O ``/O Property/O taxes/O gone/O wild/O ./O 
``/O Unlike/O most/O of/O his/O other/O no/O non-cents/O protesters/O ,/O Frank/PERSON Alford/PERSON was/O lucky/O :/O the/O county/O had/O no/O problem/O accepting/O his/O heavy/O duty/O payment/O ;/O quickly/O summoning/O a/O sheriff/O deputy/O to/O escort/O the/O payment/O to/O a/O bank/O for/O processing/O ./O 
According/O to/O Frank/PERSON ,/O this/O wo/O n't/O be/O the/O last/O time/O he/O pays/O in/O coins/O ./O 
