Man/O repays/O $/O 500,000/O in/O insurance/O awarded/O for/O death/O of/O son/O with/O four/O tonnes/O of/O quarters/O The/O quarters/O were/O in/O 150/O separate/O bags/O each/O weighing/O 50/O pounds/O and/O containing/O $/O 1,000/O worth/O of/O quarters/O Rob/PERSON Williams/PERSON Friday/O 02/O August/O 2013/O A/O US/LOCATION man/O angry/O at/O having/O to/O repay/O $/O 500,000/O insurance/O money/O he/O received/O after/O the/O death/O of/O his/O son/O in/O a/O car/O crash/O caused/O chaos/O at/O law/O offices/O in/O Southern/LOCATION Illinois/LOCATION after/O he/O decided/O to/O pay/O $/O 150,000/O of/O it/O in/O quarters/O ./O 
Roger/PERSON Herrin/PERSON 's/O son/O Michael/PERSON died/O in/O a/O car/O crash/O in/O 2001/O ./O 
He/O was/O in/O the/O vehicle/O with/O three/O other/O people/O when/O it/O was/O hit/O by/O a/O truck/O that/O failed/O to/O stop/O at/O an/O junction/O ./O 
Michael/PERSON Herrin/PERSON was/O the/O only/O one/O of/O four/O passengers/O who/O died/O so/O his/O father/O received/O the/O bulk/O of/O the/O $/O 800,000/O settlement/O from/O the/O car/O 's/O insurers/O ./O 
Mr/O Herrin/PERSON also/O received/O $/O 1.65/O million/O in/O other/O insurance/O payments/O ./O 
However/O ,/O the/O other/O families/O involved/O in/O the/O incident/O contested/O the/O damages/O and/O a/O legal/O battle/O ensued/O ./O 
Following/O the/O row/O Mr/O Herrin/PERSON was/O ordered/O to/O return/O $/O 500,000/O of/O the/O money/O ./O 
Mr/O Herrin/PERSON delivered/O part/O of/O the/O payment/O via/O truck/O to/O the/O local/O law/O offices/O in/O Southern/LOCATION Illinois/LOCATION ./O 
The/O quarters/O were/O in/O 150/O separate/O bags/O each/O weighing/O 50/O lbs/O and/O containing/O $/O 1,000/O worth/O of/O quarters/O ./O 
When/O asked/O the/O reason/O why/O he/O paid/O in/O quarters/O Mr/O Herrin/PERSON told/O WSIL/O :/O ``/O Because/O I/O could/O n't/O do/O it/O in/O pennies/O ./O ''/O 
``/O They/O can/O have/O all/O the/O money/O in/O the/O world/O ,/O and/O I/O 'd/O take/O my/O son/O back/O ,/O ''/O Herrin/PERSON told/O WSIL/ORGANIZATION ./O 
``/O To/O support/O ,/O my/O deceased/O son/O and/O ex-wife/O ,/O I/O have/O to/O fight/O it/O to/O the/O very/O end/O ,/O and/O this/O is/O the/O final/O end/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O The/O Penny/ORGANIZATION Protest/ORGANIZATION A/ORGANIZATION Frederick/ORGANIZATION man/O wants/O to/O change/O rising/O taxes/O with/O .../O change/O By/O John/PERSON Wist/PERSON Cupped/PERSON hands/O full/O of/O coins/O Updated/O at/O 2:46/O PM/O EST/O on/O Friday/O ,/O Aug/O 6/O ,/O 2010/O You/O know/O those/O people/O who/O pay/O for/O everything/O with/O exact/O change/O ,/O counting/O out/O every/O penny/O ./O 
It/O seems/O like/O it/O takes/O an/O eternity/O ,/O but/O they/O 're/O not/O willing/O to/O pay/O any/O other/O way/O ./O 
Well/O one/O Frederick/PERSON ,/O Md./LOCATION ,/O man/O was/O dead/O set/O on/O paying/O one/O particular/O bill/O with/O change/O --/O his/O taxes/O ./O 
Joe/PERSON Schmidtlein/PERSON took/O several/O bags/O of/O coins/O he/O had/O been/O collecting/O for/O years/O to/O the/O Frederick/ORGANIZATION County/ORGANIZATION Treasury/ORGANIZATION last/O week/O to/O pay/O for/O his/O property/O taxes/O ./O 
He/O told/O the/O Frederick/PERSON News-Post/O the/O thousands/O of/O coins/O were/O meant/O to/O send/O a/O message/O ./O 
``/O I/O figured/O I/O might/O as/O well/O put/O -LRB-/O the/O coins/O -RRB-/O to/O use/O ,/O ''/O Schmidtlein/PERSON told/O the/O News-Post/O ./O 
``/O Take/O it/O to/O the/O man/O ,/O the/O tax/O man/O ./O ''/O 
Basically/O ,/O Schmidtlein/PERSON is/O tired/O of/O his/O taxes/O going/O up/O ./O 
Are/O n't/O we/O all/O !/O 
For/O the/O record/O ,/O Schmidtlein/PERSON ,/O property/O taxes/O went/O up/O this/O year/O from/O $/O 5,012/O to/O $/O 5,174/O ./O 
Frederick/PERSON County/PERSON said/O that/O they/O accept/O coins/O and/O cash/O as/O payment/O ,/O but/O the/O clerk/O has/O to/O count/O every/O coin/O ,/O and/O the/O person/O paying/O with/O change/O has/O to/O stay/O and/O watch/O the/O coins/O be/O counted/O ./O 
Seems/O to/O us/O like/O the/O county/O wanted/O them/O to/O have/O a/O little/O taste/O of/O their/O own/O medicine/O ./O 
Not/O only/O that/O ,/O but/O the/O county/O wo/O n't/O authorize/O overtime/O for/O a/O clerk/O to/O count/O the/O coins/O ./O 
That/O means/O if/O the/O counting/O continues/O until/O closing/O time/O or/O the/O end/O of/O the/O shift/O ,/O the/O person/O paying/O would/O have/O to/O come/O back/O for/O day/O two/O of/O ``/O sticking/O it/O to/O the/O man/O !/O ''/O 
That/O 'll/O teach/O `/O em/O ./O 
Schmidtlein/PERSON decided/O he/O did/O n't/O want/O to/O wait/O around/O that/O long/O and/O ultimately/O wrote/O a/O check/O ./O 
But/O he/O did/O take/O the/O coins/O to/O a/O counter/O and/O found/O out/O he/O had/O $/O 966.86/O in/O coins/O ./O 
Lori/PERSON Depies/PERSON ,/O the/O Frederick/ORGANIZATION County/ORGANIZATION Treasury/ORGANIZATION Director/O ,/O told/O the/O News-Post/ORGANIZATION that/O someone/O tries/O to/O pay/O with/O coins/O as/O a/O statement/O about/O once/O a/O year/O ./O 
The/O tactic/O is/O questionable/O considering/O the/O penny/O protest/O winds/O up/O costing/O county/O employees/O hours/O of/O time/O in/O counting/O ,/O she/O said/O ./O 
``/O They/O 're/O wasting/O government/O resources/O to/O do/O this/O ,/O ''/O Depies/PERSON told/O the/O News-Post/O ./O 
``/O So/O they/O 're/O really/O punishing/O themselves/O and/O other/O taxpayers/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O day/O ./O ''/O 
------------------------------------------------------------------------/O unique_identifier/O New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION Man/O Launches/O Protest/O With/O Pennies/O //O August/O 19/O ,/O 2010/O 10:50/O AM/O //O Pennies/O are/O seen/O in/O a/O pile/O -/O Des/LOCATION Plaines/LOCATION ,/O IL/O -/O Jul/O 6/O ,/O 2006/O -/O Photo/O :/O Tim/O */O LYNDHURST/LOCATION ,/O NJ/O -LRB-/O WCBS/ORGANIZATION 880/O -RRB-/O -/O */O Sam/PERSON Corkin/PERSON hopes/O big/O changes/O will/O come/O about/O from/O his/O small/O change/O ./O 
He/O 's/O had/O it/O with/O property/O tax/O increases/O in/O Lyndhurst/LOCATION ,/O as/O WCBS/ORGANIZATION 880/ORGANIZATION 's/O Sean/PERSON Adams/PERSON reports/O ./O 
``/O I/O did/O n't/O want/O to/O make/O a/O sign/O and/O protest/O ,/O ''/O Corkin/PERSON he/O told/O Sean/PERSON Adams/PERSON ./O 
``/O So/O ,/O I/O protested/O with/O pennies/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O ,/O and/O quarters/O !/O ''/O 
He/O filled/O a/O black/O plastic/O bucket/O with/O $/O 385.66/O -LRB-/O the/O amount/O of/O his/O latest/O increase/O -RRB-/O and/O marched/O down/O to/O the/O tax/O collector/O 's/O office/O ./O 
Corkin/PERSON says/O he/O was/O told/O ``/O You/O 're/O short/O ./O ''/O 
and/O replied/O ``/O No/O ./O 
No/O ./O 
It/O 's/O in/O the/O bucket/O here/O ./O ''/O 
The/O tax/O collector/O would/O n't/O accept/O the/O loose/O change/O ./O 
Corkin/PERSON had/O to/O go/O to/O the/O bank/O to/O get/O cash/O ./O 
The/O retired/O computer/O system/O designer/O wanted/O to/O drive/O home/O a/O point/O about/O senior/O citizens/O trying/O to/O keep/O up/O with/O tax/O increases/O ./O 
The/O mayor/O tells/O The/O Record/O that/O they/O are/O going/O to/O try/O to/O reassess/O home/O values/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Pennies/O used/O to/O protest/O tax/O bill/O County/ORGANIZATION says/O it/O will/O accept/O coins/O under/O `/O reasonable/O standards/O '/O Ron/PERSON Spears/PERSON Posted/O :/O Thursday/O ,/O August/O 26/O ,/O 2010/O 4:00/O pm/O Pennies/ORGANIZATION used/O to/O protest/O tax/O bill/O By/O MARY/PERSON SWIFT/PERSON staff/O writer/O The/O Daily/O Record/O |/O 11/O comments/O CLE/O ELUM/O --/O A/O penny/O for/O your/O thoughts/O ?/O 
How/O about/O 33,000/O pennies/O to/O pay/O your/O past/O due/O personal/O property/O tax/O bill/O ?/O 
That/O 's/O what/O Cle/PERSON Elum/PERSON 's/O Ron/PERSON Spears/PERSON toted/O into/O the/O Kittitas/ORGANIZATION County/ORGANIZATION Treasurer/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Office/ORGANIZATION in/O buckets/O on/O a/O hand/O truck/O Tuesday/O to/O pay/O a/O past/O due/O bill/O for/O $/O 330/O ./O 
Spears/PERSON ,/O a/O businessman/O who/O owns/O Spears/ORGANIZATION Interiors/ORGANIZATION in/O Cle/LOCATION Elum/LOCATION and/O who/O also/O serves/O on/O the/O Cle/ORGANIZATION Elum/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION ,/O says/O like/O many/O other/O small/O business/O owners/O he/O 's/O been/O struggling/O to/O stay/O afloat/O in/O a/O down/O economy/O ./O 
Spears/PERSON ignored/O a/O personal/O property/O tax/O bill/O for/O $/O 34/O that/O was/O due/O in/O April/O ./O 
``/O It/O was/O my/O fault/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O To/O be/O honest/O I/O just/O did/O n't/O have/O the/O money/O ./O ''/O 
Late/O payments/O are/O subject/O to/O interest/O and/O penalties/O and/O personal/O property/O taxpayers/O are/O sent/O three/O notices/O before/O risking/O a/O type/O of/O foreclosure/O called/O distraint/O that/O can/O cause/O a/O taxpayer/O to/O lose/O his/O property/O ./O 
Deanna/PERSON Panattoni/PERSON ,/O Kittitas/LOCATION County/LOCATION treasurer/O ,/O says/O when/O Spears/PERSON did/O n't/O pay/O his/O taxes/O in/O April/O he/O received/O a/O delinquent/O notice/O in/O June/O and/O a/O second/O notice/O in/O July/O ./O 
When/O he/O did/O n't/O respond/O ,/O her/O office/O mailed/O a/O notice/O of/O distraint/O on/O Aug./O 6/O ./O 
By/O then/O ,/O his/O $/O 34/O tax/O bill/O increased/O to/O $/O 330/O ./O 
Spears/PERSON said/O a/O letter/O he/O got/O from/O the/O county/O demanding/O payment/O by/O Aug./O 30/O specified/O that/O he/O could/O pay/O with/O cash/O ,/O a/O cashier/O 's/O check/O or/O a/O money/O order/O ./O 
Spears/PERSON chose/O cash/O -/O only/O it/O was/O n't/O the/O kind/O the/O county/O had/O in/O mind/O ./O 
He/O went/O to/O a/O Cle/O Elum/O bank/O ,/O got/O machine-rolled/O rolls/O of/O pennies/O and/O took/O them/O to/O county/O Treasurer/O Deanna/PERSON Pannattoni/PERSON 's/O office/O ./O 
``/O I/O did/O it/O as/O a/O protest/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O I/O think/O charging/O 10/O times/O the/O amount/O you/O owe/O ,/O almost/O all/O of/O it/O in/O fees/O ,/O is/O outrageous/O ./O ''/O 
Spears/PERSON said/O a/O clerk/O in/O Panattoni/LOCATION 's/O office/O began/O counting/O the/O rolls/O of/O pennies/O but/O then/O Panattoni/PERSON came/O out/O and/O said/O she/O could/O n't/O accept/O the/O rolls/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
This/O is/O where/O the/O two/O stories/O separate/O ./O 
``/O She/O told/O me/O there/O could/O be/O `/O plugs/O '/O -LRB-/O which/O would/O make/O them/O appear/O to/O be/O full/O rolls/O when/O they/O were/O n't/O -RRB-/O and/O that/O she/O could/O n't/O accept/O them/O ,/O ''/O he/O says/O ./O 
*/O Options/O offered/O */O Panattoni/O ,/O who/O says/O she/O does/O n't/O have/O the/O resources/O to/O have/O her/O staff/O count/O 33,000/O pennies/O ,/O says/O she/O offered/O him/O options/O ,/O including/O unrolling/O and/O counting/O the/O pennies/O there/O ./O 
She/O says/O she/O also/O offered/O to/O accompany/O him/O to/O a/O bank/O to/O have/O them/O counted/O or/O to/O have/O a/O security/O guard/O accompany/O him/O to/O a/O bank/O to/O be/O counted/O ./O 
Spears/PERSON says/O he/O told/O her/O they/O 'd/O already/O been/O counted/O by/O the/O bank/O where/O he/O 'd/O gotten/O them/O ./O 
Panattoni/O ,/O in/O a/O prepared/O release/O ,/O says/O Spears/PERSON ``/O angrily/O refused/O these/O options/O creating/O such/O a/O disturbance/O that/O he/O had/O to/O be/O removed/O by/O a/O security/O guard/O ./O ''/O 
Spears/PERSON says/O he/O did/O n't/O raise/O his/O voice/O ./O 
``/O That/O makes/O me/O mad/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O That/O is/O so/O inflated/O ./O ''/O 
Spears/PERSON went/O to/O the/O prosecuting/O attorney/O 's/O office/O where/O a/O staff/O member/O met/O with/O him/O ./O 
Panattoni/O says/O the/O staff/O member/O explained/O ``/O that/O a/O government/O agency/O has/O reasonable/O discretion/O to/O determine/O how/O payment/O is/O received/O ./O ''/O 
The/O issue/O of/O whether/O a/O government/O agency/O must/O accept/O pennies/O as/O payment/O was/O the/O subject/O of/O a/O ``/O featured/O inquiry/O ''/O at/O the/O website/O for/O the/O Municipal/ORGANIZATION Research/ORGANIZATION and/ORGANIZATION Services/ORGANIZATION Center/ORGANIZATION of/O Washington/LOCATION -LRB-/O MSRC/ORGANIZATION -RRB-/O published/O on/O July/O 23/O of/O this/O year/O ,/O Panattoni/PERSON said/O in/O her/O prepared/O statement/O ./O 
``/O The/O opinion/O states/O that/O a/O city/O or/O county/O may/O set/O reasonable/O limits/O on/O the/O acceptance/O of/O loose/O coins/O in/O payment/O of/O amounts/O due/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O in/O her/O prepared/O statement/O ./O 
``/O Several/O Washington/LOCATION jurisdictions/O will/O accept/O no/O more/O than/O $/O 2/O in/O coinage/O as/O payment/O of/O citizen/O obligations/O ./O ''/O 
Spears/PERSON says/O he/O meant/O his/O act/O as/O a/O citizen/O protest/O ./O 
But/O the/O whole/O thing/O would/O have/O been/O avoided/O if/O one/O of/O two/O things/O had/O happened/O ,/O he/O says/O ./O 
``/O As/O far/O as/O I/O 've/O been/O able/O to/O figure/O out/O ,/O pennies/O are/O still/O legal/O tender/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O If/O there/O had/O been/O a/O footnote/O on/O that/O letter/O saying/O they/O would/O not/O accept/O coins/O then/O I/O would/O n't/O have/O even/O bothered/O doing/O it/O ./O ''/O 
He/O says/O if/O Panattoni/PERSON had/O taken/O the/O time/O to/O explain/O that/O there/O 'd/O been/O an/O opinion/O about/O under/O what/O conditions/O and/O how/O much/O coinage/O a/O county/O had/O to/O accept/O ,/O that/O would/O have/O been/O different/O ./O 
He/O says/O she/O did/O n't/O do/O that/O ./O 
Panattoni/O says/O the/O incident/O does/O n't/O mean/O her/O office/O wo/O n't/O accept/O coins/O in/O payment/O ,/O just/O that/O a/O taxpayer/O has/O to/O ``/O conform/O to/O reasonable/O standards/O ''/O such/O as/O those/O offered/O by/O her/O office/O ./O 
``/O I/O can/O handle/O four/O or/O five/O rolls/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O in/O a/O phone/O conversation/O Wednesday/O afternoon/O ./O 
``/O But/O if/O somebody/O brings/O coins/O in/O on/O a/O hand/O truck/O I/O ca/O n't/O handle/O it/O ./O ''/O 
Spears/PERSON ,/O who/O says/O he/O risks/O losing/O the/O tools/O he/O needs/O for/O work/O ,/O says/O he/O will/O pay/O the/O bill/O in/O more/O a/O conventional/O manner/O by/O the/O deadline/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Pay/O Your/O Tax/O Bill/O in/O Coins/O and/O Small/O Bills/O by/O Ryan/PERSON Guina/PERSON Indiana/LOCATION resident/O Cary/PERSON Malchow/PERSON ,/O protested/O Indiana/LOCATION 's/O rising/O property/O taxes/O by/O making/O his/O property/O tax/O payment/O in/O cash/O ./O 
Statewide/O ,/O Indiana/LOCATION property/O taxes/O rose/O an/O average/O of/O */O 24/O %/O */O over/O the/O last/O year/O ./O 
Malchow/PERSON paid/O over/O $/O 12,000/O in/O pennies/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O ,/O quarters/O ,/O and/O dollar/O bills/O ./O 
The/O $/O 12,000/O covered/O only/O half/O the/O annual/O property/O taxes/O for/O his/O residence/O ,/O business/O ,/O and/O rental/O properties/O ./O 
Yahoo!/O has/O a/O video/O segment/O and/O interview/O and/O shows/O Malchow/PERSON dragging/O the/O money/O through/O the/O halls/O of/O the/O county/O 's/O treasury/O department/O ./O 
On/O the/O Yahoo!/O video/O ,/O he/O stated/O he/O would/O make/O his/O next/O payment/O in/O cash/O as/O well/O ./O 
The/O video/O also/O shows/O the/O county/O treasurer/O getting/O upset/O with/O Malchow/PERSON and/O telling/O him/O to/O take/O it/O out/O of/O there/O and/O bring/O it/O back/O as/O a/O normal/O payment/O ./O 
He/O refused/O ./O 
Apparently/O the/O county/O does/O not/O have/O any/O policy/O in/O place/O against/O payment/O in/O cash/O ,/O so/O they/O were/O required/O to/O accept/O the/O payment/O ./O 
It/O took/O all/O three/O treasury/O office/O workers/O over/O an/O hour/O to/O count/O the/O cash/O by/O hand/O ,/O while/O others/O waited/O in/O line/O ./O 
The/O treasury/O also/O had/O to/O hire/O a/O security/O guard/O to/O transport/O the/O cash/O ./O 
Cash/O is/O legal/O tender/O for/O all/O debts/O public/O and/O private/O ,/O so/O I/O 'm/O pretty/O sure/O the/O county/O was/O required/O to/O accept/O the/O payment/O ./O 
This/O unorthodox/O payment/O did/O cause/O other/O problems/O for/O the/O county/O ,/O as/O well/O ./O 
The/O county/O was/O not/O able/O to/O make/O its/O deposit/O Monday/O night/O and/O missed/O out/O on/O over/O $/O 1,100/O in/O interest/O !/O 
Personally/O ,/O I/O would/O n't/O do/O anything/O along/O those/O lines/O ,/O but/O sometimes/O a/O little/O civil/O disobedience/O goes/O a/O long/O way/O !/O 
*/O Note/O :/O */O Think/O twice/O about/O doing/O this/O for/O your/O taxes/O ./O 
Carrying/O around/O large/O sums/O of/O cash/O is/O not/O always/O the/O safest/O thing/O to/O do/O ,/O and/O it/O if/O is/O lost/O or/O stolen/O ,/O you/O have/O no/O recourse/O to/O recover/O your/O funds/O ./O 
;-RRB-/O unique_identifier/O Man/O uses/O pennies/O to/O pay/O $/O 6,500/O credit/O card/O bill/O March/O 15/O ,/O 2011/O 12:00:00/O AM/O PDT/O MIRA/LOCATION MESA/LOCATION ,/O Calif./LOCATION --/O A/O San/LOCATION Diego/LOCATION County/LOCATION man/O created/O a/O bit/O of/O a/O problem/O when/O he/O went/O to/O pay/O off/O a/O $/O 6,500/O credit/O card/O bill/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
Thierry/PERSON Cahez/PERSON loaded/O the/O pennies/O into/O his/O van/O ,/O all/O 650,000/O of/O them/O rolled/O in/O plastic/O and/O put/O in/O crates/O ./O 
He/O then/O drove/O the/O pennies/O to/O his/O bank/O in/O Mira/LOCATION Mesa/LOCATION and/O unloaded/O them/O ./O 
The/O man/O said/O the/O bank/O turned/O him/O away/O several/O times/O ./O 
Eventually/O ,/O he/O was/O sent/O to/O a/O branch/O with/O a/O bigger/O vault/O that/O could/O handle/O all/O the/O coins/O ./O 
Cahez/PERSON said/O he/O decided/O to/O pay/O his/O credit/O card/O bill/O with/O pennies/O because/O he/O was/O upset/O with/O his/O bank/O over/O a/O refinance/O he/O could/O n't/O get/O ,/O and/O charges/O and/O fees/O on/O his/O card/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O */O Man/O pays/O off/O credit/O card/O with/O pennies/O */O |/O March/O ./O 
16/O ,/O 2011/O Posted/O on/O */O 03/17/2011/O 7:49:02/O AM/O PDT/O */O by/O */O JoeProBono/O */O MIRA/LOCATION MESA/LOCATION ,/O Calif./LOCATION -/O A/O California/LOCATION man/O upset/O with/O his/O bank/O for/O disallowing/O his/O requested/O refinance/O said/O he/O decided/O to/O pay/O off/O his/O $/O 6,500/O credit/O card/O bill/O entirely/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
Thierry/PERSON Cahez/PERSON of/O San/LOCATION Diego/LOCATION County/LOCATION rolled/O 650,000/O pennies/O in/O plastic/O ,/O loaded/O them/O into/O crates/O and/O drove/O the/O lot/O to/O his/O Mira/LOCATION Mesa/LOCATION bank/O ,/O KABC-TV/ORGANIZATION ,/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ,/O reported/O ./O 
Cahez/PERSON was/O turned/O away/O by/O the/O bank/O several/O times/O but/O eventually/O was/O sent/O to/O a/O branch/O with/O a/O vault/O large/O enough/O to/O handle/O the/O coins/O ./O 
Cahez/PERSON said/O he/O opted/O to/O pay/O his/O credit/O card/O bill/O with/O pennies/O because/O he/O was/O turned/O down/O for/O a/O refinance/O and/O for/O the/O amount/O of/O charges/O and/O fees/O on/O his/O credit/O card/O ,/O KABC-TV/ORGANIZATION said/O Tuesday/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O Pays/O Credit/O Card/O Debt/O at/O Chase/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION With/ORGANIZATION Pennies/ORGANIZATION -/O Atlanta/O Bankruptcy/O Law/O News/O Man/O Pays/O Credit/O Card/O Debt/O at/O Chase/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION With/O Pennies/O By/O Laura/PERSON Fishman/PERSON on/O March/O 18/O ,/O 2011/O 3:03/O PM/O A/O man/O who/O was/O frustrated/O by/O the/O charges/O and/O fees/O and/O on/O his/O Chase/PERSON credit/O card/O decided/O that/O he/O would/O get/O revenge/O on/O Chase/ORGANIZATION Bank/ORGANIZATION by/O paying/O off/O his/O $/O 6,500/O of/O credit/O card/O debt/O with/O pennies/O ./O 
That/O 's/O right/O ,/O ABC/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION reported/O that/O a/O California/LOCATION business/O owner/O named/O Thirry/PERSON Chahez/PERSON decided/O that/O he/O would/O pay/O the/O bill/O with/O 650,000/O pennies/O and/O not/O one/O cent/O more/O ./O 
This/O story/O shows/O how/O every/O penny/O really/O does/O add/O up/O when/O trying/O to/O pay/O bills/O ./O 
Perhaps/O Atlanta/LOCATION consumers/O can/O pay/O off/O their/O debts/O quicker/O just/O by/O hanging/O on/O to/O their/O loose/O change/O or/O by/O being/O a/O bit/O more/O frugal/O with/O individual/O purchases/O ./O 
Chahez/PERSON made/O quite/O a/O statement/O this/O week/O by/O walking/O into/O the/O bank/O with/O crates/O full/O of/O individual/O rolls/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
At/O first/O ,/O Chase/PERSON reportedly/O turned/O Chahez/PERSON and/O his/O pennies/O away/O by/O saying/O that/O their/O branch/O did/O n't/O have/O the/O capacity/O to/O accept/O such/O a/O payment/O ./O 
But/O eventually/O the/O business/O owner/O was/O able/O to/O deposit/O his/O money/O and/O pay/O off/O the/O full/O balance/O of/O his/O credit/O card/O debt/O when/O he/O went/O to/O a/O different/O branch/O with/O a/O bigger/O vault/O ./O 
The/O law/O in/O this/O country/O is/O a/O little/O hard/O to/O understand/O when/O it/O comes/O to/O paying/O off/O your/O debts/O with/O cold/O hard/O cash/O ./O 
Section/O 102/O of/O the/O Coinage/O Act/O of/O 1965/O -LRB-/O Title/O 31/O United/O States/O Code/O ,/O Section/O 392/O states/O that/O all/O coins/O and/O currencies/O of/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION can/O be/O used/O to/O pay/O for/O debts/O ,/O public/O charges/O ,/O taxes/O ,/O duties/O and/O dues/O ./O 
However/O ,/O there/O is/O no/O federal/O law/O that/O says/O that/O private/O businesses/O have/O to/O accept/O cash/O as/O a/O form/O of/O payment/O ./O 
So/O ,/O if/O you/O are/O going/O to/O pull/O a/O Thirry/O Chahez/O and/O try/O to/O pay/O your/O credit/O card/O debt/O or/O maybe/O your/O phone/O bill/O in/O pennies/O ,/O do/O n't/O be/O surprised/O if/O the/O company/O gives/O you/O a/O hard/O time/O ./O 
Even/O so/O ,/O it/O still/O helps/O to/O save/O your/O pennies/O ,/O you/O never/O know/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Police/O cite/O Vernal/ORGANIZATION man/O accused/O of/O paying/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O Follow/O @GeoffLiesik/O </O https://twitter.com/GeoffLiesik/O >/O Published/O :/O Friday/O ,/O June/O 3/O 2011/O 8:02/O p.m./O MDT/O Summary/O A/O Vernal/O man/O has/O been/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O after/O police/O say/O he/O caused/O alarm/O when/O he/O paid/O for/O a/O disputed/O medical/O bill/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
VERNAL/ORGANIZATION A/O Vernal/O man/O has/O been/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O after/O police/O say/O he/O caused/O alarm/O when/O he/O paid/O for/O a/O disputed/O medical/O bill/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
On/O May/O 27/O ,/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON went/O to/O Basin/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION prepared/O to/O dispute/O an/O outstanding/O bill/O ,/O according/O to/O Assistant/O Vernal/O Police/O Chief/O Keith/PERSON Campbell/PERSON ./O 
West/O ,/O 38/O ,/O apparently/O did/O not/O believe/O he/O owed/O the/O clinic/O the/O $/O 25/O it/O said/O he/O did/O ./O 
After/O asking/O if/O they/O accepted/O cash/O ,/O West/O dumped/O 2,500/O pennies/O onto/O the/O counter/O and/O demanded/O that/O they/O count/O it/O ,/O Campbell/ORGANIZATION said/O ./O 
The/O pennies/O were/O strewn/O about/O the/O counter/O and/O the/O floor/O ./O 
The/O incident/O upset/O clinic/O staff/O ,/O said/O Campbell/PERSON ,/O adding/O that/O West/LOCATION 's/O behavior/O served/O ``/O no/O legitimate/O purpose/O ./O ''/O 
Clinic/O staff/O told/O West/O they/O were/O calling/O police/O and/O he/O left/O the/O office/O ./O 
Officers/O caught/O up/O with/O West/LOCATION later/O and/O issued/O him/O a/O citation/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O ,/O an/O infraction/O ,/O which/O carries/O a/O potential/O fine/O of/O $/O 140/O ./O 
The/O case/O will/O be/O heard/O in/O Vernal/LOCATION City/LOCATION Justice/LOCATION Court/LOCATION ./O 
unique_identifier/O Utah/LOCATION man/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O for/O trying/O to/O pay/O doctor/O 's/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O Utah/LOCATION man/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O for/O trying/O to/O pay/O doctor/O 's/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O BY/O Philip/PERSON Caulfield/PERSON DAILY/O NEWS/O STAFF/O WRITER/O Sunday/O ,/O June/O 5th/O 2011/O ,/O 10:59/O AM/O A/O Utah/LOCATION man/O was/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O after/O he/O tried/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 25/O doctor/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ./O 
Susan/PERSON Watts/News/PERSON A/O Utah/LOCATION man/O was/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O after/O he/O tried/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 25/O doctor/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ./O 
Take/O our/O Poll/O Chump/O change/O Should/O the/O clinic/O have/O accepted/O the/O pennies/O as/O payment/O ?/O 
Of/O course/O ./O 
Pennies/O are/O money/O !/O 
No/O ,/O it/O was/O a/O dumb/O stunt/O ./O 
He/O deserved/O to/O be/O fined/O ./O 
Only/O if/O he/O rolled/O them/O up/O ./O 
I/O do/O n't/O care/O ./O 
A/O Utah/LOCATION man/O was/O slapped/O with/O a/O disorderly/O conduct/O charge/O for/O attempting/O to/O pay/O his/O doctor/O bill/O --/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ./O 
Jason/PERSON West/PERSON ,/O 38/O ,/O showed/O up/O at/O the/O Basin/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION in/O Vernal/LOCATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION ,/O late/O last/O month/O to/O dispute/O a/O $/O 25/O charge/O ,/O the/O Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION reported/O ./O 
``/O After/O asking/O if/O they/O accepted/O cash/O ,/O West/O dumped/O 2,500/O pennies/O onto/O the/O counter/O and/O demanded/O that/O they/O count/O it/O ,/O ''/O Police/O Chief/O Keith/PERSON Campbell/PERSON told/O the/O newspaper/O ./O 
``/O The/O pennies/O were/O strewn/O about/O the/O counter/O and/O the/O floor/O ./O ''/O 
When/O the/O clinic/O staff/O freaked/O out/O and/O called/O the/O cops/O ,/O West/O fled/O the/O office/O ./O 
Police/O tracked/O him/O down/O later/O and/O gave/O him/O the/O citation/O ,/O which/O carries/O a/O potential/O fine/O of/O $/O 140/O ./O 
West/O was/O n't/O the/O first/O person/O to/O try/O to/O settle/O a/O bill/O using/O small/O change/O this/O year/O to/O send/O a/O message/O ./O 
In/O January/O ,/O a/O University/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Colorado/ORGANIZATION student/O paid/O his/O $/O 14,000/O spring/O tuition/O in/O one/O dollar/O bills/O ./O 
The/O student/O ,/O Nic/PERSON Ramos/PERSON ,/O said/O he/O pulled/O the/O stunt/O to/O draw/O attention/O to/O the/O high/O cost/O of/O college/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O Gets/O Cited/O For/O Paying/O A/O Disputed/O Medical/O Bill/O Of/O $/O 25/O Dollars/O With/O Pennies/O June/O 6/O ,/O 2011/O --/O We/O understand/O that/O sometimes/O we/O all/O will/O have/O to/O pay/O a/O fine/O or/O bill/O that/O we/O just/O do/O n't/O agree/O on/O ./O 
As/O the/O founder/O of/O this/O site/O i/O ca/O n't/O think/O of/O one/O speeding/O ticket/O that/O i/O enjoyed/O paying/O and/O had/O i/O not/O read/O the/O following/O article/O this/O may/O have/O been/O an/O option/O in/O payment/O if/O i/O did/O n't/O think/O the/O outcome/O could/O happen/O to/O me/O ./O 
//O Huffington/ORGANIZATION Post/ORGANIZATION //O VERNAL/LOCATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION --/O A/O Utah/LOCATION man/O has/O been/O cited/O on/O a/O charge/O of/O disorderly/O conduct/O after/O paying/O for/O a/O disputed/O medical/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ./O 
The/O Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Salt/ORGANIZATION Lake/LOCATION City/LOCATION reports/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON went/O to/O Basin/LOCATION Clinic/LOCATION in/O Vernal/LOCATION on/O May/O 27/O prepared/O to/O dispute/O an/O outstanding/O $/O 25/O bill/O ./O 
Assistant/O Vernal/O Police/O Chief/O Keith/PERSON Campbell/PERSON says/O that/O after/O asking/O staff/O members/O whether/O they/O accepted/O cash/O ,/O West/O dumped/O 2,500/O pennies/O on/O the/O counter/O and/O demanded/O that/O staff/O count/O them/O ./O 
Campbell/ORGANIZATION says/O the/O incident/O upset/O staff/O because/O pennies/O were/O strewn/O about/O the/O counter/O and/O floor/O ,/O and/O West/LOCATION 's/O action/O served/O ``/O no/O legitimate/O purpose/O ./O ''/O 
Police/O later/O issued/O the/O 38-year-old/O West/O a/O citation/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O ./O 
That/O carries/O a/O fine/O of/O as/O much/O as/O $/O 140/O ./O 
Or/O 14,000/O pennies/O ./O 
//O //O Now/O despite/O whether/O or/O not/O we/O feel/O that/O the/O police/O who/O wrote/O the/O citation/O were/O not/O only/O haters/O but/O also/O douche/O bags/O -LRB-/O just/O calling/O a/O spade/O a/O spade/O -RRB-/O it/O takes/O nothing/O away/O from/O the/O fact/O that/O had/O he/O not/O been/O written/O a/O citation/O for/O disorderly/O conductand/O fined/O $/O 140/O he/O and/O we/O might/O think/O that/O he/O had/O won/O ./O 
Won/O the/O battle/O against/O bullsh/O */O t/O bills/O and/O poor/O customer/O service/O ./O 
But/O instead/O his/O effort/O was/O foiled/O and/O the/O haters/O won/O ,/O twice/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O Pays/O Medical/O Bill/O With/O 2,500/O Pennies/O ,/O Gets/O $/O 140/O Fine/O By/O Jenny/PERSON Wilson/PERSON June/O 06,2011/O Out/O of/O 2,500/O pennies/O ,/O this/O Utah/LOCATION man/O did/O n't/O get/O one/O lucky/O one/O ./O 
Jason/PERSON West/PERSON ,/O 38/O ,/O of/O Vernal/LOCATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION ,/O has/O been/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O after/O trying/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 25/O disputed/O medical/O bill/O entirely/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
West/O did/O n't/O believe/O he/O owed/O Basin/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION money/O ,/O so/O decided/O to/O settle/O an/O outstanding/O bill/O by/O dumping/O 2,500/O pennies/O onto/O the/O counter/O ,/O an/O action/O that/O disrupted/O clinic/O routine/O and/O caused/O coins/O to/O spill/O across/O the/O counter/O and/O floor/O ./O 
Assistant/O Vernal/O Police/O Chief/O Keith/PERSON Campbell/PERSON told/O the/O Salt/LOCATION Lake/LOCATION City/LOCATION //O Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION //O that/O the/O incident/O ,/O ``/O served/O no/O legitimate/O purpose/O ./O ''/O 
Do/O //O pennies/O //O serve/O any/O legitimate/O purpose/O ?/O 
At/O least/O here/O they/O helped/O prove/O a/O point/O ./O 
But/O it/O turns/O out/O that/O West/O 's/O actions/O may/O cost/O him/O more/O than/O 2,500/O pennies/O :/O his/O disorderly/O conduct/O citation/O could/O cost/O him/O up/O to/O $/O 140/O ./O 
Is/O it/O okay/O to/O pay/O that/O with/O 1,400/O dimes/O ?/O 
unique_identifier/O Peeved/O patient/O proud/O of/O penny/O protest/O By/O Geoff/PERSON Liesik/PERSON ,/O Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION Jason/PERSON West/PERSON explains/O how/O his/O frustration/O over/O a/O disputed/O $/O 25/O medical/O bill/O led/O him/O to/O pay/O Basin/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION in/O pennies/O 2,500/O of/O them/O on/O Sunday/O June/O 5/O ,/O 2011/O ./O 
The/O Vernal/O man/O was/O cited/O on/O May/O 31/O ,/O 2011/O ,/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O not/O for/O paying/O in/O pennies/O ,/O according/O to/O police/O but/O for/O the/O manner/O in/O which/O he/O did/O it/O ./O 
Geoff/PERSON Liesik/PERSON ,/O Uintah/ORGANIZATION Basin/ORGANIZATION Standard/ORGANIZATION Police/ORGANIZATION cite/O Vernal/ORGANIZATION man/O accused/O of/O paying/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O VERNAL/O It/O 's/O fair/O to/O say/O it/O was/O his/O cents/O of/O humor/O that/O brought/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON to/O the/O attention/O of/O the/O coppers/O ./O 
It/O 's/O also/O fair/O to/O say/O that/O despite/O the/O criminal/O charge/O he/O 's/O now/O facing/O the/O Vernal/ORGANIZATION man/O would/O n't/O change/O what/O he/O did/O when/O he/O could/O n't/O make/O heads/O or/O tails/O of/O a/O $/O 25/O billing/O dispute/O with/O his/O doctor/O 's/O office/O ./O 
Vernal/O police/O ,/O responding/O to/O a/O signed/O complaint/O from/O Basin/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION ,/O cited/O West/LOCATION with/O disorderly/O conduct/O on/O May/O 31/O ./O 
West/O is/O accused/O of/O unnecessarily/O causing/O alarm/O when/O he/O unloaded/O 2,500/O pennies/O onto/O a/O receptionist/O 's/O counter/O at/O the/O clinic/O to/O settle/O his/O bill/O ./O 
Officers/O emphasized/O that/O West/LOCATION was/O n't/O cited/O for/O paying/O in/O pennies/O ,/O but/O for/O the/O manner/O in/O which/O he/O did/O it/O ./O 
Police/O photos/O ,/O released/O Tuesday/O through/O a/O public/O records/O request/O ,/O support/O Assistant/O Vernal/O Police/O Chief/O Keith/PERSON Campbell/PERSON 's/O statement/O last/O week/O that/O pennies/O were/O strewn/O about/O the/O counter/O and/O the/O floor/O ./O 
West/O 's/O actions/O served/O no/O legitimate/O purpose/O ,/O Campbell/ORGANIZATION said/O ./O 
I/O would/O say/O that/O I/O had/O a/O legitimate/O purpose/O and/O it/O was/O to/O resolve/O a/O billing/O dispute/O and/O pay/O it/O ,/O West/PERSON said/O ,/O and/O to/O protest/O how/O I/O 'd/O been/O treated/O ./O 
Basin/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION 's/O doctors/O issued/O a/O brief/O statement/O Tuesday/O saying/O the/O clinic/O has/O ``/O always/O accepted/O all/O legal/O currency/O as/O payment/O ./O 
We/O will/O not/O tolerate/O pennies/O or/O any/O other/O objects/O being/O thrown/O at/O our/O employees/O ,/O the/O statement/O said/O ./O 
West/O denies/O acting/O aggressively/O toward/O any/O clinic/O staffer/O ,/O including/O the/O billing/O clerk/O he/O says/O refused/O to/O help/O him/O during/O the/O past/O month/O while/O he/O tried/O to/O resolve/O his/O questions/O about/O a/O $/O 25/O co-pay/O he/O claims/O he/O paid/O in/O December/O ./O 
I/O did/O n't/O at/O any/O time/O yell/O at/O them/O ,/O West/PERSON said/O ,/O referring/O to/O the/O May/O 27/O visit/O that/O landed/O him/O in/O hot/O water/O ./O 
I/O did/O n't/O go/O on/O a/O rant/O ./O 
I/O was/O n't/O irate/O ./O 
West/PERSON maintains/O that/O he/O calmly/O asked/O the/O billing/O clerk/O ,/O Do/O you/O take/O cash/O ?/O 
He/O was/O prepared/O to/O pay/O with/O his/O debit/O card/O ,/O he/O said/O ,/O but/O found/O out/O that/O was/O n't/O necessary/O ./O 
She/O very/O haughtily/O said/O ,/O `/O Well/O ,/O yes/O we/O do/O ,/O '/O West/O said/O ./O 
So/O I/O said/O ,/O `/O Lucky/O for/O me/O ,/O I/O happen/O to/O have/O it/O on/O me/O ./O '/O 
The/O police/O report/O from/O the/O incident/O states/O that/O West/LOCATION told/O clinic/O workers/O he/O was/O `/O sorry/O '/O for/O what/O he/O was/O about/O to/O do/O and/O dumped/O pennies/O from/O a/O cardboard/O box/O ,/O which/O was/O found/O in/O the/O clinic/O waiting/O room/O ,/O on/O the/O front/O counter/O ./O 
West/O ,/O however/O ,/O says/O he/O had/O carried/O the/O 14/O pounds/O of/O loose/O pennies/O in/O a/O large/O bowl/O inside/O a/O black/O plastic/O sack/O ./O 
He/O admits/O to/O pouring/O them/O onto/O the/O top/O counter/O ./O 
Some/O of/O the/O coins/O ,/O he/O acknowledges/O ,/O spilled/O onto/O the/O desk/O below/O where/O the/O receptionist/O was/O seated/O and/O onto/O the/O floor/O ./O 
That/O 's/O just/O the/O nature/O of/O pennies/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
They/O 're/O round/O ./O 
There/O were/O people/O in/O the/O waiting/O room/O who/O witnessed/O the/O incident/O ,/O but/O West/LOCATION maintains/O that/O no/O one/O appeared/O to/O be/O upset/O by/O his/O actions/O ./O 
There/O was/O giggles/O and/O snickers/O and/O outright/O laughter/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
West/O added/O that/O he/O never/O demanded/O that/O someone/O count/O out/O his/O penny/O payment/O ./O 
He/O did/O ask/O for/O a/O receipt/O and/O said/O he/O told/O the/O billing/O clerk/O ,/O I/O 'm/O willing/O to/O wait/O if/O you/O want/O to/O count/O them/O so/O you/O can/O make/O sure/O you/O got/O every/O penny/O ./O 
West/PERSON said/O the/O woman/O told/O the/O receptionist/O to/O write/O out/O a/O receipt/O and/O then/O told/O him/O she/O was/O calling/O the/O police/O to/O have/O him/O removed/O from/O the/O building/O ./O 
West/O was/O n't/O there/O ,/O however/O ,/O when/O an/O officer/O arrived/O ./O 
The/O girl/O handed/O me/O my/O receipt/O ,/O I/O had/O no/O more/O business/O with/O them/O and/O I/O left/O ,/O he/O said/O ,/O noting/O that/O he/O lives/O about/O four/O blocks/O from/O the/O clinic/O and/O was/O n't/O contacted/O by/O a/O police/O officer/O for/O about/O five/O hours/O ./O 
By/O then/O ,/O West/LOCATION was/O more/O than/O an/O hour/O away/O ,/O heading/O to/O a/O Memorial/O Day/O weekend/O gathering/O with/O family/O ./O 
He/O offered/O to/O return/O to/O Vernal/LOCATION immediately/O to/O meet/O with/O the/O officer/O ,/O but/O said/O he/O was/O told/O that/O was/O n't/O necessary/O ./O 
He/O finally/O met/O with/O the/O officer/O May/O 31/O ,/O the/O day/O he/O was/O cited/O ./O 
West/PERSON said/O he/O was/O n't/O trying/O to/O harm/O anyone/O or/O cause/O alarm/O ;/O he/O was/O only/O trying/O to/O show/O his/O frustration/O over/O the/O poor/O customer/O service/O he/O believes/O he/O received/O from/O the/O clinic/O 's/O billing/O department/O ,/O and/O do/O it/O in/O a/O humorous/O way/O ./O 
I/O did/O stand-up/O comedy/O in/O college/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
This/O is/O how/O I/O deal/O with/O stress/O ./O 
I/O make/O jokes/O ./O 
As/O for/O the/O $/O 64,000/O question/O or/O rather/O the/O 6,400,000/O penny/O question/O ?/O 
West/O says/O he/O will/O not/O pay/O his/O $/O 140/O fine/O in/O one-cent/O pieces/O ,/O if/O he/O 's/O ultimately/O convicted/O of/O the/O disorderly/O conduct/O charge/O ./O 
I/O recognize/O my/O place/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
I/O recognize/O it/O 's/O a/O court/O of/O law/O and/O I/O have/O respect/O for/O the/O legal/O process/O ./O 
E-mail/O :/O geoff@ubstandard.com/O unique_identifier/O The/O Upshot/O Penny/O offense/O :/O Man/O fined/O for/O paying/O fee/O in/O pennies/O By/O Claudine/PERSON Zap/PERSON June/O 6/O ,/O 2011/O 5:08/O PM/O The/O Upshot/O </O //O blogs/upshot/O //O >/O No/O lucky/O pennies/O here/O :/O Police/O have/O charged/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON ,/O an/O aggrieved/O medical/O patient/O in/O Vernal/LOCATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION ,/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O His/O alleged/O crime/O ?/O 
Attempting/O to/O pay/O a/O disputed/O medical/O bill/O of/O $/O 25/O entirely/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
The/O story/O ,/O reported/O in/O the/O Salt/LOCATION Lake/LOCATION City/LOCATION Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION describes/O the/O ``/O penny/O offense/O ''/O this/O way/O :/O West/O ,/O 38/O ,/O did/O not/O believe/O he/O owed/O the/O medical/O clinic/O $/O 25/O but/O came/O in/O to/O pay/O the/O fee/O in/O person/O ./O 
He/O first/O asked/O the/O clinic/O staff/O if/O the/O facility/O accepted/O cash/O payments/O ,/O and/O then/O dumped/O 2,500/O pennies/O onto/O the/O counter/O and/O demanded/O that/O they/O be/O counted/O ./O 
But/O West/O apparently/O had/O n't/O counted/O on/O the/O clinic/O calling/O the/O police/O ;/O the/O arresting/O officer/O contended/O that/O West/PERSON 's/O protest/O served/O ``/O no/O legitimate/O purpose/O ./O ''/O 
The/O charge/O carries/O a/O fine/O that/O can/O go/O as/O high/O as/O $/O 140/O --/O and/O there/O 's/O no/O word/O as/O yet/O on/O what/O currency/O West/O will/O use/O to/O pay/O it/O ./O 
West/O is/O n't/O alone/O in/O the/O ranks/O of/O penny/O protesters/O ./O 
A/O wise/O guy/O in/O Frederick/LOCATION ,/O Maryland/LOCATION ,/O showed/O up/O at/O the/O county/O clerk/O 's/O office/O last/O summer/O with/O bags/O of/O cash/O to/O pay/O off/O his/O tax/O bill/O with/O $/O 966.86/O in/O change/O ./O 
And/O a/O New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION school/O district/O a/O few/O years/O back/O punished/O 29/O students/O who/O paid/O for/O their/O $/O 2/O school/O lunches/O in/O pennies/O --/O possibly/O as/O a/O prank/O --/O with/O two-day/O detentions/O ./O 
After/O parents/O protested/O ,/O the/O students/O were/O pardoned/O ./O 
The/O school/O explained/O that/O the/O use/O of/O the/O small/O change/O slowed/O down/O the/O lunch/O line/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O Who/O Paid/O $/O 25/O Bill/O In/O Pennies/O Is/O Proud/O By/O Ben/PERSON Popken/PERSON June/O 7/O ,/O 2011/O A/O man/O who/O made/O a/O scene/O when/O he/O voiced/O his/O dissatisfaction/O with/O a/O clinic/O 's/O billing/O department/O by/O paying/O a/O $/O 25/O disputed/O bill/O in/O all/O pennies/O is/O proud/O of/O what/O he/O did/O ./O 
``/O I/O would/O say/O that/O I/O had/O a/O legitimate/O purpose/O and/O it/O was/O to/O resolve/O a/O billing/O dispute/O and/O pay/O it/O ,/O ''/O the/O man/O told/O KSL/ORGANIZATION ,/O ``/O and/O to/O protest/O how/O I/O 'd/O been/O treated/O ./O ''/O 
The/O man/O said/O he/O was/O frustrated/O with/O the/O poor/O customer/O service/O he/O felt/O he/O got/O from/O the/O billing/O department/O and/O that/O he/O wanted/O to/O show/O it/O in/O a/O humorous/O way/O ./O 
He/O says/O he/O asked/O the/O billing/O clerk/O in/O a/O calm/O voice/O if/O she/O took/O cash/O ./O 
``/O She/O very/O haughtily/O said/O ,/O `/O Well/O ,/O yes/O we/O do/O ,/O '/O ''/O the/O man/O said/O ./O 
``/O So/O I/O said/O ,/O `/O Lucky/O for/O me/O ,/O I/O happen/O to/O have/O it/O on/O me/O ./O '/O ''/O 
The/O man/O disputed/O earlier/O reports/O and/O said/O he/O did/O not/O demand/O the/O pennies/O be/O counted/O there/O immediately/O ./O 
He/O said/O he/O did/O however/O ask/O for/O a/O receipt/O and/O say/O ,/O ``/O I/O 'm/O willing/O to/O wait/O if/O you/O want/O to/O count/O them/O so/O you/O can/O make/O sure/O you/O got/O every/O penny/O ./O ''/O 
He/O did/O acknowledge/O some/O of/O the/O pennies/O fell/O on/O the/O floor/O after/O he/O poured/O 13.8/O pounds/O of/O pennies/O on/O the/O receptionist/O 's/O desk/O ./O 
``/O That/O 's/O just/O the/O nature/O of/O pennies/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
``/O They/O 're/O round/O ./O ''/O 
The/O man/O says/O he/O does/O not/O plan/O on/O paying/O his/O $/O 140/O fine/O in/O pennies/O if/O he/O 's/O convicted/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O ./O 
``/O I/O recognize/O my/O place/O ,/O ''/O the/O man/O told/O KSL/ORGANIZATION ./O 
``/O I/O recognize/O it/O 's/O a/O court/O of/O law/O and/O I/O have/O respect/O for/O the/O legal/O process/O ./O ''/O 
Peeved/O patient/O proud/O of/O penny/O protest/O unique_identifier/O Man/O fined/O for/O `/O paying/O in/O pennies/O '/O A/O man/O who/O tried/O to/O pay/O a/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O has/O been/O fined/O --/O who/O 's/O in/O the/O right/O ?/O 
Wed/O ,/O Jun/O 8/O ,/O 2011/O 13:03/O BST/O When/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON turned/O up/O in/O person/O to/O pay/O a/O bill/O he/O disputed/O ,/O he/O ended/O up/O being/O landed/O with/O a/O fine/O ./O 
Why/O ?/O 
Because/O he/O tried/O to/O pay/O it/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ./O 
West/PERSON said/O he/O paid/O the/O charge/O -/O to/O Basin/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION ,/O USA/LOCATION -/O months/O ago/O ,/O but/O failed/O to/O get/O the/O current/O bill/O revoked/O ./O 
He/O then/O calmly/O asked/O the/O teller/O :/O ``/O Do/O you/O take/O cash/O ?/O ''/O 
When/O told/O they/O did/O ,/O West/LOCATION replied/O :/O ``/O Lucky/O for/O me/O I/O happen/O to/O have/O it/O on/O me/O ./O ''/O 
He/O then/O poured/O 2,500/O pennies/O on/O the/O counter/O ``/O I/O 'm/O willing/O to/O wait/O if/O you/O want/O to/O count/O them/O so/O you/O can/O make/O sure/O you/O get/O every/O penny/O ,/O ''/O he/O added/O ./O 
But/O while/O he/O told/O local/O paper/O The/O Vernal/ORGANIZATION Express/ORGANIZATION that/O all/O this/O was/O done/O in/O a/O calm/O manner/O ,/O and/O that/O all/O that/O resulted/O from/O it/O was/O giggles/O from/O other/O customers/O waiting/O ,/O the/O clinic/O disagreed/O and/O called/O the/O police/O ./O 
West/O ended/O up/O being/O cited/O for/O ``/O disorderly/O conduct/O ''/O and/O now/O faces/O a/O $/O 140/O fine/O --/O or/O 14,000/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O The/O pennies/O were/O strewn/O about/O the/O counter/O and/O the/O floor/O ,/O ''/O said/O the/O police/O ./O 
The/O clinic/O maintains/O it/O would/O have/O taken/O the/O money/O ,/O but/O does/O ``/O not/O tolerate/O pennies/O or/O any/O other/O objects/O being/O thrown/O at/O our/O employees/O ''/O ,/O according/O to/O a/O statement/O ./O 
West/PERSON says/O he/O did/O n't/O throw/O anything/O ,/O they/O spilled/O :/O ``/O That/O 's/O just/O the/O nature/O of/O pennies/O ,/O ''/O he/O told/O the/O Vernal/ORGANIZATION Express/ORGANIZATION ./O 
``/O They/O 're/O round/O ./O ''/O 
*/O Can/O you/O pay/O in/O pennies/O then/O ?/O 
*/O In/O the/O US/LOCATION any/O amount/O in/O coins/O counts/O as/O legal/O tender/O --/O but/O there/O is/O no/O law/O that/O forces/O shops/O and/O other/O retailers/O to/O accept/O them/O ./O 
That/O means/O businesses/O can/O ask/O for/O payment/O in/O any/O denomination/O they/O want/O ./O 
But/O where/O would/O you/O stand/O if/O you/O decided/O to/O pay/O up/O in/O pence/O in/O the/O UK/LOCATION ?/O 
Well/O ,/O it/O 's/O come/O up/O ./O 
Back/O in/O 2006/O Michael/PERSON Rees/PERSON of/O Tonteg/LOCATION ,/O South/LOCATION Wales/LOCATION ,/O was/O told/O he/O could/O no/O longer/O keep/O paying/O his/O #/O 650/O debt/O in/O instalments/O of/O 4,000/O penny/O pieces/O -LRB-/O as/O he/O had/O been/O for/O months/O -RRB-/O ./O 
Meanwhile/O in/O 2009/O ,/O Gary/PERSON Southall/PERSON tried/O to/O settle/O a/O #/O 1,300/O fine/O with/O a/O shopping/O trolley/O full/O of/O 1p/O pieces/O --/O he/O was/O also/O refused/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O Coinage/O Act/O of/O 1971/O ,/O 1ps/O and/O 2ps/O are/O only/O legal/O tender/O up/O to/O the/O value/O of/O 20p/O ./O 
But/O that/O does/O n't/O mean/O you/O ca/O n't/O pay/O more/O than/O that/O in/O pennies/O if/O the/O person/O or/O business/O you/O 're/O paying/O agrees/O ./O 
Legal/O tender/O has/O a/O very/O narrow/O meaning/O in/O the/O UK/LOCATION ./O 
Put/O simply/O ,/O you/O ca/O n't/O be/O successfully/O sued/O for/O non-payment/O of/O a/O debt/O if/O you/O give/O the/O correct/O amount/O of/O money/O in/O legal/O tender/O ./O 
That/O 's/O it/O ./O 
Everything/O else/O is/O up/O to/O the/O two/O parties/O involved/O in/O the/O transaction/O ./O 
And/O fans/O of/O wacky/O ways/O to/O protest/O can/O take/O heart/O from/O one/O thing/O :/O #/O 1/O and/O #/O 2/O coins/O are/O legal/O tender/O up/O to/O any/O amount/O you/O like/O ./O 
Even/O if/O they/O 're/O frozen/O in/O ice/O or/O put/O in/O a/O bathtub/O full/O of/O honey/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Wednesday/O ,/O 08/O June/O 2011/O Utah/LOCATION Man/O Cited/O After/O Paying/O Disputed/O Medical/O BIll/O With/O 2,500/O Pennies/O Written/O by/O Bruce/PERSON Walker/PERSON When/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON of/O Vernal/LOCATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION ,/O tried/O to/O pay/O his/O disputed/O medical/O bill/O last/O week/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ,/O he/O was/O issued/O a/O citation/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O ./O 
The/O reason/O for/O the/O charge/O was/O that/O West/O allegedly/O dumped/O the/O pennies/O onto/O the/O cashier/O 's/O desk/O and/O asked/O her/O to/O count/O all/O of/O them/O ./O 
While/O the/O manner/O in/O which/O West/O delivered/O his/O payment/O may/O have/O been/O a/O bit/O extreme/O -LRB-/O placing/O rolled/O coins/O gently/O on/O the/O desk/O might/O have/O avoided/O the/O citation/O -RRB-/O there/O was/O an/O irony/O in/O his/O case/O that/O points/O to/O a/O more/O important/O principle/O than/O good/O manners/O ,/O which/O are/O more/O frequently/O these/O days/O being/O enforced/O by/O the/O local/O constabulary/O ,/O rather/O than/O by/O Emily/ORGANIZATION Post/ORGANIZATION ./O 
That/O is/O ,/O had/O he/O paid/O the/O bill/O with/O federal/O reserve/O notes/O --/O backed/O ,/O really/O ,/O by/O nothing/O more/O than/O the/O promise/O of/O the/O federal/O government/O that/O the/O paper/O money/O has/O value/O --/O then/O he/O would/O have/O faced/O no/O legal/O problems/O at/O all/O ./O 
Also/O ironic/O is/O the/O fact/O that/O the/O pennies/O -LRB-/O known/O also/O as/O ``/O coppers/O ''/O -RRB-/O have/O inherent/O economic/O value/O ./O 
Gold/O and/O silver/O coins/O ,/O of/O course/O ,/O have/O value/O much/O greater/O than/O their/O face/O value/O ./O 
The/O price/O of/O copper/O has/O risen/O so/O quickly/O that/O pennies/O minted/O before/O 1982/O have/O a/O ``/O melt/O value/O ''/O of/O 2.7/O cents/O ./O 
Pennies/O minted/O in/O the/O last/O three/O decades/O have/O a/O metal/O value/O of/O only/O 60/O percent/O of/O the/O face/O value/O -LRB-/O the/O copper/O has/O been/O replaced/O almost/O completely/O by/O zinc/O -RRB-/O ./O 
Our/O coins/O did/O n't/O always/O contain/O baser/O metals/O ,/O however/O ./O 
The/O American/O Republic/O was/O founded/O upon/O the/O idea/O of/O sound/O money/O ,/O and/O the/O Constitution/O in/O Article/O I/O ,/O Section/O 8/O lays/O out/O most/O of/O the/O relevant/O language/O ./O 
Congress/ORGANIZATION can/O ``/O coin/O money/O ,/O regulate/O the/O value/O thereof/O ,/O and/O of/O foreign/O coins/O ,/O and/O to/O fix/O the/O standard/O of/O weights/O and/O measurements/O ''/O and/O ''/O .../O provide/O for/O the/O punishment/O of/O counterfeiting/O the/O securities/O and/O current/O coin/O of/O the/O United/LOCATION States/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
Sound/O money/O meant/O either/O species/O --/O money/O made/O out/O of/O metals/O of/O value/O --/O or/O paper/O currency/O redeemable/O in/O exact/O measurements/O of/O money/O ./O 
We/O are/O accustomed/O to/O thinking/O of/O money/O in/O the/O Federal/ORGANIZATION Reserve/ORGANIZATION System/ORGANIZATION sense/O of/O one/O ``/O dollar/O ''/O being/O some/O vague/O promise/O by/O the/O federal/O government/O to/O support/O that/O piece/O of/O printed/O paper/O ./O 
Why/O use/O the/O term/O ``/O dollar/O ''/O ?/O 
What/O does/O one/O ``/O dollar/O ''/O mean/O ?/O 
In/O our/O economic/O system/O the/O dollar/O referred/O to/O a/O physical/O measurement/O of/O gold/O ./O 
When/O currency/O is/O backed/O by/O a/O clear/O promise/O to/O pay/O a/O set/O measurement/O of/O gold/O in/O redemption/O for/O that/O currency/O ,/O then/O the/O economy/O has/O great/O inherent/O stability/O ./O 
Today/O we/O take/O inflation/O for/O granted/O ,/O even/O to/O the/O point/O of/O having/O ``/O cost/O of/O living/O adjustments/O ''/O in/O pensions/O and/O entitlement/O spending/O ./O 
We/O assume/O that/O the/O value/O of/O our/O paper/O currency/O ,/O the/O dollar/O ,/O will/O shrink/O over/O time/O ./O 
But/O during/O the/O first/O century/O of/O our/O nation/O ,/O inflation/O was/O essentially/O unknown/O ./O 
Money/O retained/O its/O value/O ./O 
And/O that/O laid/O the/O foundation/O for/O aggressive/O investment/O in/O productive/O enterprises/O ./O 
This/O system/O actually/O worked/O better/O than/O the/O coin/O currency/O which/O had/O served/O as/O money/O since/O ancient/O times/O ./O 
Regimes/O in/O the/O ancient/O and/O medieval/O world/O which/O wanted/O to/O devalue/O their/O metal/O coins/O would/O ``/O clip/O ''/O them/O ,/O shaving/O off/O part/O of/O the/O silver/O or/O gold/O ,/O and/O re-stamping/O the/O coins/O with/O the/O lower/O metallic/O value/O ./O 
-LRB-/O The/O milled/O edges/O on/O modern/O coins/O are/O designed/O to/O discourage/O that/O practice/O ./O -RRB-/O 
But/O in/O our/O country/O ,/O when/O one/O ``/O dollar/O ''/O was/O an/O exact/O weight/O of/O gold/O ,/O the/O Treasury/ORGANIZATION had/O no/O way/O to/O cheat/O currency/O holders/O ./O 
There/O was/O another/O assurance/O given/O to/O buyers/O and/O sellers/O using/O currency/O ./O 
Private/O banks/O issued/O notes/O redeemable/O in/O gold/O ./O 
The/O very/O term/O ``/O banknote/O ''/O seems/O meaningless/O to/O us/O today/O ,/O but/O they/O were/O once/O ubiquitous/O in/O our/O nation/O 's/O economy/O ./O 
The/O integrity/O of/O the/O banking/O industry/O was/O particularly/O vital/O when/O currency/O largely/O meant/O these/O redemption/O notes/O issued/O by/O private/O businesses/O ./O 
As/O far/O a/O our/O coins/O go/O ,/O our/O government/O today/O has/O ,/O in/O effect/O ,/O ``/O clipped/O ''/O our/O coins/O just/O like/O a/O corrupt/O king/O of/O England/LOCATION or/O a/O dissolute/O emperor/O of/O Rome/LOCATION ./O 
Zinc/O is/O much/O cheaper/O than/O copper/O ,/O but/O even/O so/O a/O zinc/O penny/O may/O soon/O be/O worth/O more/O than/O its/O face/O value/O ./O 
Since/O 1982/O ,/O the/O price/O of/O zinc/O has/O tripled/O More/O pointedly/O ,/O at/O one/O point/O in/O 2005-2006/O ,/O its/O price/O was/O about/O 600/O percent/O higher/O than/O when/O it/O essentially/O replaced/O copper/O as/O the/O basic/O ingredient/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
At/O that/O time/O ,/O the/O metallic/O value/O of/O a/O penny/O would/O have/O been/O worth/O about/O 50/O percent/O more/O than/O the/O face/O value/O of/O the/O coin/O ./O 
The/O prices/O of/O the/O metals/O used/O to/O make/O our/O coins/O --/O zinc/O ,/O copper/O and/O nickel/O -/O have/O been/O rising/O since/O President/O Obama/PERSON took/O office/O ,/O and/O his/O ``/O stimulus/O ''/O package/O -LRB-/O which/O involves/O a/O gross/O devaluing/O of/O the/O American/O currency/O -RRB-/O seems/O certain/O to/O push/O those/O prices/O higher/O than/O inflation/O ./O 
What/O will/O happen/O when/O the/O price/O of/O zinc/O rises/O above/O the/O cost/O of/O a/O penny/O ?/O 
Perhaps/O the/O Treasury/ORGANIZATION will/O do/O as/O during/O WWII/O and/O mint/O steel/O pennies/O ./O 
Is/O the/O Constitution/O being/O followed/O when/O copper/O coins/O are/O replaced/O with/O zinc/O ,/O or/O silver/O coins/O with/O copper/O ?/O 
What/O is/O the/O purpose/O of/O fixing/O the/O weight/O and/O measurement/O of/O coins/O ,/O if/O the/O very/O metals/O from/O which/O the/O coins/O are/O minted/O have/O been/O changed/O to/O baser/O metals/O ?/O 
The/O downward/O spiral/O to/O baser/O ingredients/O in/O our/O coins/O suggests/O that/O sometime/O in/O the/O future/O the/O old/O advice/O ,/O ``/O Do/O n't/O take/O any/O wooden/O nickels/O !/O ''/O 
may/O not/O be/O so/O very/O funny/O after/O all/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Updated/O :/O 6:45/O p.m./O Tuesday/O ,/O June/O 7/O ,/O 2011/O |/O Posted/O :/O 6:44/O p.m./O Tuesday/O ,/O June/O 7/O ,/O 2011/O Patient/O 's/O penny/O protest/O seems/O mostly/O `/O centsless/O '/O By/O D.L./PERSON Stewart/PERSON To/O the/O thousands/O --/O perhaps/O millions/O --/O of/O Americans/O who/O have/O heard/O his/O story/O ,/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON may/O qualify/O as/O some/O sort/O of/O hero/O ./O 
A/O ``/O mad/O as/O hell/O and/O I/O 'm/O not/O going/O to/O take/O it/O anymore/O ''/O kind/O of/O guy/O ./O 
West/O 's/O story/O ,/O widely/O reported/O in/O newspapers/O ,/O television/O ,/O radio/O and/O online/O ,/O clearly/O speaks/O to/O the/O frustrations/O and/O irritations/O we/O all/O have/O experienced/O ./O 
The/O 38-year-old/O Utah/LOCATION man/O disagreed/O with/O a/O $/O 25/O bill/O he/O received/O from/O a/O medical/O clinic/O ./O 
The/O story/O did/O n't/O detail/O whether/O the/O bill/O was/O justified/O or/O what/O steps/O he/O may/O have/O taken/O to/O resolve/O the/O dispute/O ./O 
What/O it/O did/O detail/O is/O how/O he/O handled/O it/O :/O He/O went/O to/O the/O clinic/O and/O asked/O staffers/O at/O the/O front/O desk/O if/O they/O accepted/O cash/O ./O 
When/O they/O said/O they/O did/O ,/O he/O dumped/O 2,500/O pennies/O on/O the/O counter/O and/O insisted/O that/O they/O count/O it/O ./O 
Protesting/O with/O a/O sack/O of/O pennies/O is/O not/O a/O particularly/O innovative/O tactic/O ./O 
The/O Internet/O is/O rife/O with/O similar/O stories/O ,/O some/O of/O which/O probably/O are/O true/O ./O 
*/O The/O power/O company/O customer/O */O in/O Virginia/LOCATION who/O protested/O his/O $/O 300/O electric/O bill/O with/O 30,000/O pennies/O ./O 
*/O The/O man/O in/O Michigan/LOCATION */O who/O paid/O a/O $/O 335/O court/O judgment/O with/O 33,500/O pennies/O ./O 
*/O The/O California/LOCATION man/O */O who/O paid/O his/O $/O 6,500/O credit/O card/O bill/O with/O 650,000/O pennies/O ./O 
*/O The/O 29/O eighth-graders/O */O in/O New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION who/O each/O paid/O for/O their/O $/O 2/O school/O lunches/O with/O 200/O pennies/O to/O protest/O a/O shortening/O of/O the/O cafeteria/O schedule/O ./O 
What/O made/O this/O story/O newsworthy/O is/O what/O happened/O next/O ./O 
The/O cops/O busted/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON ./O 
According/O to/O the/O police/O report/O ,/O the/O 2,500/O pennies/O did/O n't/O just/O land/O on/O the/O counter/O ./O 
A/O lot/O of/O them/O overflowed/O and/O cascaded/O onto/O the/O floor/O ./O 
So/O he/O was/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O ./O 
But/O that/O 's/O probably/O because/O there/O are/O no/O laws/O on/O the/O books/O specifically/O against/O self-centered/O rudeness/O ./O 
Because/O the/O only/O people/O inconvenienced/O by/O this/O senseless/O temper/O tantrum/O were/O the/O employees/O at/O the/O front/O desk/O who/O had/O to/O pick/O up/O and/O count/O the/O coins/O ,/O even/O though/O they/O probably/O had/O nothing/O to/O do/O with/O determining/O the/O bill/O in/O question/O ./O 
Oh/O ,/O and/O the/O patients/O waiting/O patiently/O in/O the/O waiting/O room/O who/O had/O to/O patiently/O wait/O even/O longer/O because/O because/O the/O staff/O was/O busy/O picking/O up/O and/O counting/O pennies/O ./O 
So/O there/O was/O nothing/O all/O that/O heroic/O or/O useful/O about/O his/O protest/O ./O 
It/O was/O like/O griping/O to/O a/O minimum-wage/O clerk/O at/O the/O corner/O Speedway/O because/O multibillion/O dollar/O oil/O companies/O continue/O to/O hike/O the/O price/O of/O gas/O ./O 
Like/O complaining/O to/O the/O cashier/O at/O Kroger/ORGANIZATION because/O the/O price/O of/O peanut/O butter/O keeps/O going/O up/O ./O 
And/O all/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON really/O got/O for/O it/O was/O a/O few/O seconds/O of/O satisfaction/O ,/O a/O few/O days/O of/O Internet/O fame/O and/O a/O possible/O $/O 140/O -LRB-/O 14,000/O pennies/O -RRB-/O fine/O ./O 
Perhaps/O it/O was/O worth/O it/O to/O him/O ./O 
But/O ,/O as/O protests/O go/O ,/O it/O was/O strictly/O penny-ante/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O `/O We/O gave/O him/O the/O money/O and/O he/O tossed/O it/O on/O floor/O '/O TEN/O years/O ago/O tonight/O ,/O a/O group/O of/O local/O businessmen/O wrestled/O control/O of/O Swansea/LOCATION City/LOCATION away/O from/O controversial/O chairman/O Tony/PERSON Petty/PERSON ,/O beginning/O the/O revival/O which/O has/O led/O all/O the/O way/O to/O the/O Premier/ORGANIZATION League/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Here/O we/O look/O back/O on/O an/O incredible/O period/O with/O some/O of/O the/O key/O men/O involved/O ./O 
A/O DECADE/O on/O ,/O Tony/PERSON Petty/PERSON would/O probably/O argue/O --/O as/O he/O did/O when/O he/O left/O --/O that/O he/O was/O good/O for/O Swansea/LOCATION City/LOCATION ./O 
It/O was/O ten/O years/O ago/O today/O that/O a/O dramatic/O ,/O late-night/O meeting/O at/O Cardiff/LOCATION 's/O Copthorne/ORGANIZATION Hotel/ORGANIZATION ended/O with/O Petty/O throwing/O a/O pound/O 's/O worth/O of/O loose/O change/O on/O the/O floor/O and/O relinquishing/O control/O of/O the/O club/O ./O 
The/O Londoner/O who/O lived/O in/O Australia/LOCATION did/O not/O leave/O empty-handed/O --/O he/O walked/O away/O with/O a/O supermarket/O carrier/O bag/O stuffed/O with/O around/O #/O 20,000/O in/O cash/O ./O 
``/O I/O had/O held/O meetings/O with/O him/O at/O the/O Vetch/O where/O he/O 'd/O said/O he/O was/O n't/O interested/O in/O selling/O ,/O ''/O remembers/O Steve/PERSON Penny/PERSON ,/O a/O local/O solicitor/O and/O now/O a/O Swansea/ORGANIZATION director/O who/O was/O there/O the/O night/O Petty/O finally/O walked/O ./O 
``/O Things/O suddenly/O changed/O ./O 
Eventually/O he/O said/O he/O 'd/O had/O enough/O ,/O that/O he/O would/O be/O leaving/O the/O country/O the/O following/O morning/O and/O that/O he/O would/O like/O to/O pass/O control/O of/O the/O club/O over/O ./O 
``/O Mel/O Nurse/O 's/O consortium/O gave/O me/O a/O figure/O and/O we/O negotiated/O a/O price/O ,/O but/O he/O said/O he/O was/O not/O going/O to/O do/O the/O deal/O in/O Swansea/LOCATION ./O 
``/O David/PERSON Morgan/PERSON and/O I/O dropped/O everything/O ,/O we/O got/O the/O finances/O arranged/O and/O drove/O to/O Cardiff/LOCATION to/O buy/O the/O club/O ./O ''/O 
Penny/O ,/O of/O John/PERSON Collins/PERSON and/O Partners/O ,/O describes/O the/O method/O of/O payment/O as/O ``/O slightly/O unusual/O ''/O ./O 
Saying/O something/O similar/O about/O the/O whole/O Petty/O reign/O would/O be/O unfair/O ./O 
It/O was/O much/O more/O extreme/O than/O that/O ./O 
Petty/PERSON had/O insisted/O when/O he/O took/O over/O at/O Vetch/LOCATION Field/LOCATION in/O October/O 2001/O that/O he/O was/O no/O white/O knight/O who/O would/O pump/O big/O money/O into/O the/O club/O ./O 
He/O was/O not/O lying/O ./O 
Instead/O he/O took/O the/O cost-cutting/O approach/O ,/O attempting/O to/O sack/O seven/O players/O and/O slash/O the/O wages/O of/O eight/O others/O only/O seven/O days/O after/O arriving/O in/O Wales/LOCATION ./O 
Within/O a/O few/O more/O days/O ,/O the/O first/O meeting/O of/O the/O consortium/O which/O would/O eventually/O oust/O Petty/PERSON had/O taken/O place/O ./O 
At/O one/O stage/O Petty/PERSON was/O offered/O #/O 50,001/O to/O leave/O but/O declined/O ,/O opting/O instead/O to/O sell/O star/O man/O Stuart/PERSON Roberts/PERSON for/O just/O #/O 100,000/O and/O then/O getting/O another/O #/O 100,000/O bonus/O when/O Sky/O Sports/O decided/O to/O screen/O Swansea/ORGANIZATION 's/O FA/O Cup/O tie/O with/O Queens/ORGANIZATION Park/ORGANIZATION Rangers/ORGANIZATION ./O 
Petty/PERSON was/O by/O now/O a/O hate/O figure/O for/O the/O fans/O ,/O but/O Nurse/O 's/O attempt/O to/O force/O him/O out/O by/O acquiring/O an/O #/O 801,000/O debt/O against/O the/O club/O and/O then/O calling/O it/O in/O failed/O in/O court/O ./O 
Petty/PERSON won/O that/O battle/O by/O claiming/O he/O had/O #/O 1/O million/O of/O investment/O lined/O up/O ,/O but/O there/O was/O no/O sign/O of/O the/O cash/O as/O the/O players/O '/O wages/O were/O not/O paid/O over/O Christmas/O ./O 
Captain/O Nick/PERSON Cusack/PERSON branded/O Swansea/ORGANIZATION 's/O owner/O a/O disgrace/O ,/O yet/O Petty/PERSON was/O adamant/O the/O club/O were/O better/O off/O thanks/O to/O the/O drastic/O measures/O he/O had/O taken/O as/O he/O prepared/O to/O sell/O up/O ./O 
``/O He/O was/O a/O business/O person/O who/O took/O advantage/O of/O something/O which/O he/O could/O see/O could/O be/O a/O thriving/O situation/O for/O him/O ,/O ''/O reckons/O Nurse/O ,/O the/O former/O Swansea/ORGANIZATION player/O who/O became/O the/O figurehead/O for/O those/O trying/O to/O bring/O Petty/O down/O ./O 
``/O But/O we/O came/O together/O as/O a/O city/O to/O make/O sure/O our/O football/O club/O survived/O ./O 
``/O I/O suppose/O I/O played/O a/O big/O part/O in/O that/O ,/O and/O I/O am/O proud/O of/O what/O I/O did/O ./O 
``/O I/O put/O my/O business/O aside/O and/O the/O outlay/O was/O tremendous/O ,/O but/O I/O never/O thought/O about/O that/O ./O 
``/O I/O let/O my/O heart/O rule/O my/O head/O at/O that/O time/O ,/O and/O I/O look/O back/O now/O and/O think/O about/O what/O a/O risk/O I/O took/O ./O 
Thankfully/O ,/O of/O course/O ,/O it/O was/O worth/O it/O ./O ''/O 
Morgan/PERSON ,/O now/O one/O of/O Swansea/LOCATION 's/O associate/O directors/O ,/O reckons/O Petty/PERSON did/O not/O fancy/O a/O final/O trip/O to/O South/LOCATION West/LOCATION Wales/LOCATION this/O time/O ten/O years/O ago/O because/O he/O no/O longer/O felt/O safe/O in/O these/O parts/O ./O 
``/O The/O taxman/O was/O due/O to/O come/O into/O the/O Vetch/O the/O next/O day/O to/O seize/O assets/O ,/O so/O Petty/PERSON 's/O hands/O were/O tied/O ,/O ''/O he/O explains/O ./O 
``/O He/O either/O got/O something/O for/O the/O club/O by/O selling/O to/O us/O ,/O or/O he/O ended/O up/O with/O nothing/O ./O 
A/O phone/O call/O came/O through/O to/O me/O and/O all/O he/O said/O was/O something/O like/O `/O Do/O you/O want/O to/O buy/O a/O football/O club/O ?/O '/O 
``/O It/O was/O a/O worrying/O time/O ,/O because/O I/O really/O do/O n't/O think/O he/O would/O have/O cared/O if/O he/O 'd/O walked/O away/O and/O left/O no/O football/O club/O behind/O ./O 
``/O The/O meeting/O that/O night/O started/O around/O 7pm/O ./O 
I/O thought/O we/O would/O sign/O here/O and/O sign/O there/O and/O say/O goodbye/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O very/O difficult/O to/O deal/O with/O and/O it/O dragged/O on/O until/O something/O like/O 11pm/O ./O 
``/O At/O the/O end/O ,/O those/O of/O us/O who/O were/O there/O --/O myself/O ,/O Steve/PERSON ,/O Mel/PERSON and/O Tim/PERSON Jones/PERSON -LRB-/O Nurse/O 's/O solicitor/O -RRB-/O --/O had/O a/O whip-round/O to/O give/O him/O the/O pound/O he/O had/O paid/O for/O the/O club/O in/O the/O first/O place/O back/O ./O 
``/O We/O gave/O him/O it/O in/O loose/O change/O and/O he/O just/O tossed/O it/O on/O the/O floor/O ./O 
That/O was/O his/O parting/O shot/O ./O ''/O 
The/O following/O morning/O ,/O as/O Petty/O flew/O home/O ,/O Morgan/ORGANIZATION ,/O Penny/ORGANIZATION and/ORGANIZATION Co/ORGANIZATION faced/O the/O media/O at/O the/O Vetch/O ./O 
``/O We/O were/O like/O rabbits/O in/O the/O headlights/O ,/O ''/O Morgan/PERSON remembers/O ./O 
And/O Penny/PERSON concedes/O :/O ``/O The/O press/O conference/O was/O an/O interesting/O experience/O for/O us/O ./O 
``/O We/O knew/O the/O club/O had/O severe/O financial/O difficulties/O ,/O but/O it/O was/O only/O when/O we/O took/O over/O that/O we/O found/O out/O the/O extent/O of/O them/O ./O 
``/O I/O spent/O the/O next/O three/O months/O basically/O working/O full-time/O for/O the/O club/O ,/O and/O there/O were/O many/O others/O doing/O the/O same/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O team/O effort/O ,/O and/O thankfully/O we/O were/O able/O to/O keep/O professional/O football/O alive/O in/O Swansea/LOCATION ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O incredible/O to/O think/O that/O we/O are/O now/O a/O Premier/ORGANIZATION League/ORGANIZATION club/O ./O ''/O 
A/O debt/O of/O around/O #/O 1.7/O million/O --/O minimal/O now/O ,/O but/O massive/O then/O --/O had/O to/O be/O cleared/O by/O Swansea/ORGANIZATION 's/O new/O owners/O ,/O hence/O the/O company/O voluntary/O arrangement/O which/O came/O that/O spring/O ./O 
``/O Everybody/O feared/O for/O the/O long-term/O future/O of/O the/O club/O at/O that/O stage/O ,/O ''/O recalls/O Huw/PERSON Jenkins/PERSON ,/O a/O background/O figure/O as/O Petty/PERSON was/O toppled/O but/O one/O who/O would/O soon/O become/O Swansea/ORGANIZATION 's/O next/O chairman/O ./O 
``/O I/O think/O support/O for/O the/O club/O was/O at/O an/O all-time/O low/O around/O the/O city/O ,/O and/O the/O first/O objective/O was/O to/O make/O sure/O we/O survived/O ./O 
``/O All/O we/O were/O hoping/O for/O was/O to/O secure/O some/O kind/O of/O future/O ./O 
We/O were/O not/O looking/O any/O further/O than/O that/O ./O ''/O 
It/O was/O a/O rough/O ride/O for/O a/O while/O --/O the/O CVA/ORGANIZATION was/O no/O fun/O for/O anyone/O ,/O and/O Swansea/LOCATION came/O perilously/O close/O to/O non-league/O football/O a/O little/O over/O a/O year/O later/O ./O 
The/O club/O were/O forced/O to/O do/O things/O on/O the/O cheap/O for/O a/O time/O and/O they/O almost/O paid/O the/O price/O ./O 
``/O We/O were/O going/O from/O day/O to/O day/O ,/O ''/O Jenkins/PERSON adds/O ./O 
``/O Nobody/O was/O ploughing/O in/O millions/O of/O pounds/O to/O start/O us/O moving/O forward/O ./O 
All/O we/O had/O was/O hard/O work/O ,/O commitment/O and/O belief/O in/O our/O club/O ./O 
``/O We/O brought/O a/O bit/O of/O common/O sense/O into/O the/O way/O the/O club/O was/O run/O ./O 
We/O realised/O that/O everything/O had/O to/O pay/O for/O itself/O ,/O and/O that/O started/O us/O on/O the/O path/O to/O where/O we/O are/O now/O ./O 
``/O I/O think/O we/O can/O all/O take/O a/O bit/O of/O pride/O from/O the/O progress/O we/O have/O made/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O not/O for/O ourselves/O ,/O but/O for/O our/O football/O club/O and/O our/O city/O ./O 
People/O all/O over/O the/O world/O are/O now/O hearing/O about/O Swansea/LOCATION City/LOCATION ./O ''/O 
Whatever/O he/O claimed/O about/O the/O good/O he/O was/O doing/O ,/O Petty/PERSON would/O have/O put/O paid/O to/O any/O hopes/O of/O reaching/O the/O Premier/ORGANIZATION League/ORGANIZATION had/O he/O stuck/O around/O much/O longer/O ./O 
Yet/O perhaps/O the/O lows/O he/O dragged/O Swansea/LOCATION to/O played/O a/O part/O in/O inspiring/O the/O highs/O they/O are/O experiencing/O today/O ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n't/O know/O where/O he/O is/O now/O ,/O ''/O Morgan/PERSON says/O ./O 
``/O But/O in/O a/O sense/O ,/O he/O was/O the/O reason/O why/O an/O ugly/O duckling/O became/O a/O high-flying/O Swan/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Motorist/O pays/O parking/O fine/O -/O with/O 29/O cheques/O !/O 
A/O Southampton/ORGANIZATION motorist/O who/O was/O caught/O illegally/O parked/O in/O a/O disabled/O bay/O sent/O in/O 29/O cheques/O to/O pay/O the/O fine/O ./O 
The/O driver/O was/O handed/O a/O parking/O ticket/O after/O being/O caught/O by/O car/O park/O officials/O at/O Bournemouth/LOCATION 's/O Castlepoint/O shopping/O complex/O ./O 
The/O female/O driver/O of/O the/O Volvo/ORGANIZATION car/O settled/O the/O fine/O by/O sending/O in/O cheques/O worth/O #/O 1/O and/O #/O 2/O ,/O but/O because/O she/O paid/O up/O within/O 10/O days/O the/O #/O 100/O fine/O was/O reduced/O to/O #/O 60/O ./O 
Castlepoint/O manager/O Peter/PERSON Matthews/PERSON said/O he/O could/O see/O the/O funny/O side/O ./O 
He/O said/O :/O ``/O In/O one/O sense/O it/O 's/O quite/O funny/O and/O in/O another/O sense/O she/O is/O making/O a/O point/O ./O 
``/O But/O by/O parking/O in/O a/O disabled/O bay/O without/O a/O blue/O badge/O ,/O her/O point/O about/O the/O way/O she/O thinks/O she/O can/O behave/O has/O already/O been/O made/O ./O ''/O 
The/O Volvo/ORGANIZATION ,/O registration/O number/O T819/O JPP/O ,/O is/O registered/O to/O a/O Southampton/ORGANIZATION address/O and/O was/O ticketed/O at/O 11.45/O am/O on/O February/O 15/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Pennies/O make/O Palm/LOCATION Bay/LOCATION man/O 's/O fine/O point/O Miffed/O landowner/O carts/O 31,050/O one-cent/O coins/O to/O City/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION to/O settle/O fine/O Apr./O 21/O ,/O 2012/O Disgruntled/O man/O pays/O fine/O with/O 30,000/O pennies/O Disgruntled/O man/O pays/O fine/O with/O 30,000/O pennies/O :/O Jay/PERSON Sperry/PERSON paid/O a/O $/O 310/O fine/O to/O Palm/LOCATION Bay/LOCATION with/O pennies/O on/O Friday/O in/O protest/O of/O what/O he/O says/O was/O an/O unfair/O code/O violation/O fine/O ./O 
By/O Malcolm/PERSON Denemark/PERSON and/O Breuse/PERSON Hickman/PERSON Posted/O April/O 20/O ,/O 2012/O Written/O by/O Susanne/PERSON Cervenka/PERSON Jay/PERSON Sperry/PERSON of/O Palm/LOCATION Bay/LOCATION prepares/O his/O pennies/O to/O pay/O a/O code/O enforcement/O fine/O ./O 
Purchase/O Image/O */O PALM/O BAY/O */O We/O ll/O start/O at/O the/O end/O of/O the/O story/O ./O 
Jay/PERSON Sperry/PERSON walked/O into/O Palm/LOCATION Bay/LOCATION City/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION with/O three/O buckets/O full/O of/O pennies/O Friday/O afternoon/O ./O 
That/O s/O the/O end/O of/O the/O story/O ./O 
Or/O so/O Sperry/ORGANIZATION hopes/O ./O 
But/O the/O tale/O of/O the/O 31,050/O pennies/O actually/O began/O late/O last/O year/O ./O 
Sperry/ORGANIZATION owns/O a/O vacant/O lot/O on/O Myrtle/ORGANIZATION Oak/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION ./O 
A/O proliferation/O of/O Brazilian/O pepper/O trees/O on/O the/O lot/O led/O a/O neighbor/O to/O call/O the/O city/O s/O Code/O Compliance/O office/O ./O 
After/O receiving/O a/O notice/O from/O the/O code/O folks/O ,/O Sperry/ORGANIZATION contacted/O the/O office/O and/O his/O neighbors/O to/O see/O exactly/O what/O their/O concerns/O were/O ./O 
Finding/O that/O the/O neighbors/O were/O worried/O that/O the/O invasive/O pepper/O trees/O were/O spilling/O onto/O their/O land/O ,/O Sperry/ORGANIZATION went/O out/O to/O the/O lot/O and/O cut/O the/O trees/O down/O himself/O ./O 
The/O neighbors/O were/O happy/O ,/O a/O fact/O they/O confirmed/O to/O FLORIDA/LOCATION TODAY/O ./O 
Sperry/ORGANIZATION contacted/O Code/O Compliance/O to/O find/O out/O what/O he/O needed/O to/O do/O next/O to/O close/O the/O matter/O out/O ./O 
He/O said/O code/O officials/O told/O him/O to/O fax/O a/O signed/O letter/O from/O the/O neighbors/O ./O 
He/O did/O so/O promptly/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
End/O of/O story/O ?/O 
Not/O yet/O ./O 
Remember/O ,/O we/O haven/O t/O gotten/O back/O to/O the/O pennies/O yet/O ./O 
Weeks/O later/O ,/O Sperry/ORGANIZATION got/O a/O bill/O for/O $/O 310.50/O from/O the/O city/O ./O 
That/O s/O how/O much/O Palm/LOCATION Bay/LOCATION wanted/O for/O clearing/O a/O 25-foot/O wide/O swath/O around/O the/O perimeter/O of/O the/O vacant/O lot/O ./O 
Palm/LOCATION Bay/LOCATION code/O requires/O such/O a/O buffer/O around/O the/O edges/O of/O vacant/O lots/O ,/O though/O neighbors/O can/O waive/O the/O requirement/O ./O 
But/O the/O city/O says/O it/O never/O received/O Sperry/ORGANIZATION s/O faxed/O copy/O of/O the/O neighbors/O letter/O ,/O so/O it/O sent/O a/O city/O crew/O out/O to/O mow/O back/O the/O edges/O of/O the/O lot/O ./O 
That/O move/O perplexed/O the/O neighbors/O ./O 
They/O told/O a/O code/O official/O ,/O before/O the/O mowing/O ,/O that/O they/O were/O fine/O with/O the/O lot/O as/O it/O was/O ./O 
That/O $/O 310.50/O left/O Sperry/ORGANIZATION miffed/O that/O he/O was/O still/O facing/O a/O bill/O after/O he/O had/O talked/O with/O the/O city/O to/O make/O sure/O he/O was/O taking/O the/O right/O steps/O ./O 
All/O along/O ,/O it/O wasn/O t/O like/O I/O was/O trying/O to/O be/O a/O bum/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
It/O just/O seems/O odd/O to/O me/O that/O when/O you/O have/O been/O in/O contact/O with/O them/O they/O would/O at/O least/O let/O you/O know/O they/O were/O going/O to/O go/O out/O and/O mow/O it/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O back/O to/O the/O 170/O pounds/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
Sperry/ORGANIZATION figured/O he/O couldn/O t/O fight/O City/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ,/O but/O maybe/O he/O could/O kick/O it/O in/O the/O shins/O ./O 
-LRB-/O Page/O 2/O of/O 2/O -RRB-/O So/O ,/O he/O called/O his/O bank/O and/O arranged/O to/O withdraw/O $/O 300/O ./O 
In/O pennies/O ./O 
It/O took/O the/O bank/O several/O days/O to/O get/O the/O 600/O rolls/O together/O ./O 
Meanwhile/O ,/O he/O scooped/O another/O $/O 10.50/O in/O pennies/O out/O of/O his/O coin/O jar/O at/O home/O ./O 
After/O picking/O them/O up/O at/O his/O bank/O ,/O he/O began/O unrolling/O the/O coins/O and/O tossing/O them/O in/O his/O buckets/O ./O 
Truth/O be/O told/O ,/O Sperry/ORGANIZATION didn/O t/O bust/O open/O all/O 600/O rolls/O ,/O only/O about/O $/O 200/O worth/O ./O 
That/O was/O enough/O to/O make/O his/O point/O ,/O he/O thought/O ./O 
Apparently/O ,/O he/O thought/O right/O ./O 
Sperry/ORGANIZATION s/O pennies/O weren/O t/O immediately/O accepted/O when/O he/O tried/O to/O drop/O them/O off/O at/O the/O Code/O Compliance/O office/O Friday/O ./O 
Supervisor/O William/PERSON Martinez/PERSON initially/O told/O Sperry/ORGANIZATION that/O the/O city/O would/O bill/O him/O to/O have/O the/O coins/O counted/O plus/O any/O discrepancy/O ./O 
But/O after/O a/O tense/O exchange/O and/O a/O phone/O call/O to/O supervisors/O ,/O Martinez/PERSON said/O the/O city/O would/O cover/O the/O cost/O of/O counting/O the/O change/O ,/O but/O Sperry/PERSON would/O be/O responsible/O if/O there/O was/O a/O shortfall/O ./O 
Sperry/ORGANIZATION joined/O city/O staff/O as/O they/O took/O it/O to/O another/O bank/O to/O have/O the/O change/O counted/O ./O 
I/O was/O just/O trying/O to/O make/O my/O point/O ,/O Sperry/ORGANIZATION told/O city/O staff/O ./O 
Martinez/PERSON replied/O :/O Point/O well/O made/O ./O 
Pennies/O make/O Palm/LOCATION Bay/LOCATION man/O 's/O fine/O point/O An/O apparent/O communication/O lag/O left/O a/O Palm/LOCATION Bay/LOCATION property/O owner/O with/O a/O $/O 300/O bill/O from/O code/O enforcement/O ./O 
He/O paid/O it/O in/O pennies/O to/O protest/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Legal/O tender/O ?/O 
Man/O who/O paid/O accountant/O 's/O #/O 800/O bill/O in/O coppers/O is/O ordered/O by/O judge/O to/O `/O pay/O up/O properly/O '/O By/O Suzannah/PERSON Hills/PERSON </O //O home/search/O ./O 
html?s/O =/O &/O authornamef/O =/O Suzannah/O +/O Hills/O >/O Published/O :/O 04:31/O EST/O ,/O 15/O May/O 2012/O |/O Updated/O :/O 04:31/O EST/O ,/O 15/O May/O 2012/O Stunned/O :/O Accountant/O Phillip/PERSON Lawrence/PERSON sued/O his/O client/O Robert/PERSON Fitzpatrick/PERSON who/O tried/O to/O pay/O a/O #/O 800/O bill/O with/O boxes/O of/O 1p/O and/O 2p/O coins/O A/O disgruntled/O client/O who/O paid/O a/O bill/O with/O #/O 800/O of/O loose/O change/O after/O a/O row/O with/O his/O accountant/O has/O been/O ordered/O to/O pay/O his/O debt/O `/O properly/O '/O by/O a/O court/O judge/O ./O 
Care/O home/O owner/O Robert/PERSON Fitzpatrick/PERSON dumped/O five/O crates/O of/O coppers/O -/O weighing/O a/O back-breaking/O 166kg/O -/O in/O his/O accountant/O Philip/PERSON Lawrence/PERSON 's/O front/O garden/O ,/O in/O Colchester/LOCATION ,/O Essex/LOCATION ./O 
But/O a/O judge/O has/O now/O ruled/O that/O the/O debt/O has/O not/O been/O properly/O paid/O and/O ordered/O Mr/O Fitzpatrick/PERSON to/O pay/O by/O more/O conventional/O means/O ./O 
Mr/O Fitzpatrick/PERSON failed/O to/O make/O the/O final/O direct/O debit/O payment/O of/O a/O credit/O agreement/O last/O year/O ,/O Colchester/ORGANIZATION County/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION heard/O ./O 
So/O he/O decided/O to/O leave/O the/O coppers/O in/O the/O garden/O of/O Philip/PERSON Lawrence/PERSON ,/O a/O co-director/O at/O Colchester-based/O Baverstocks/O accountants/O ,/O and/O considered/O the/O debt/O paid/O ./O 
But/O on/O Friday/O Mr/O Lawrence/PERSON successfully/O sued/O Mr/O Fitzpatrick/PERSON and/O his/O care/O home/O business/O ,/O Fitzpatrick/ORGANIZATION Total/ORGANIZATION Home/ORGANIZATION Care/ORGANIZATION ,/O in/O Earls/O Colne/O ,/O because/O debts/O over/O #/O 10/O can/O not/O be/O paid/O using/O coppers/O ./O 
District/O judge/O Charles/PERSON Molle/PERSON heard/O how/O the/O 166kg/O of/O change/O was/O left/O in/O Mr/O Lawrence/PERSON 's/O garden/O while/O he/O was/O away/O on/O business/O on/O November/O 30/O and/O December/O 1/O last/O year/O ./O 
He/O ordered/O Mr/O Fitzpatrick/PERSON to/O pay/O the/O accountants/O #/O 1,118.62/O ./O 
Short/O changed/O :/O Accountant/O Philip/PERSON Lawrence/PERSON ,/O pictured/O with/O the/O boxes/O of/O coins/O ,/O won/O a/O court/O case/O forcing/O his/O client/O to/O pay/O him/O `/O properly/O '/O as/O debts/O over/O #/O 10/O can/O not/O be/O paid/O with/O coppers/O Short/PERSON changed/O :/O Accountant/O Philip/PERSON Lawrence/PERSON ,/O pictured/O with/O the/O boxes/O of/O coins/O ,/O won/O a/O court/O case/O forcing/O his/O client/O to/O pay/O him/O `/O properly/O '/O as/O debts/O over/O #/O 10/O can/O not/O be/O paid/O with/O coppers/O Mr/O Lawrence/PERSON said/O :/O '/O I/O was/O not/O there/O when/O the/O boxes/O were/O delivered/O and/O did/O not/O sign/O for/O them/O ./O 
`/O My/O partner/O phoned/O me/O to/O ask/O if/O I/O was/O expecting/O a/O delivery/O and/O when/O I/O said/O I/O was/O n't/O she/O open/O the/O boxes/O ,/O only/O to/O find/O five/O boxes/O full/O of/O these/O coins/O ./O 
It/O was/O quite/O remarkable/O ./O '/O 
The/O boxes/O were/O full/O of/O 1p/O and/O 2p/O coins/O with/O several/O 5p/O coins/O ,/O which/O Mr/O Lawrence/PERSON loaded/O into/O the/O boot/O of/O his/O car/O the/O following/O morning/O ./O 
He/O took/O the/O coins/O to/O the/O firm/O 's/O office/O ,/O in/O Butt/LOCATION Lane/LOCATION ,/O where/O they/O have/O stayed/O since/O ./O 
Mr/O Fitzpatrick/PERSON did/O not/O attend/O Colchester/ORGANIZATION County/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION and/O declined/O to/O comment/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Taxis/O plan/O five/O cents/O protest/O July/O 24/O 2012/O at/O 05:37/O pm/O By/O Giordano/PERSON Stolley/PERSON Comment/O on/O this/O story/O iol/O news/O pic/O five/O cent/O coin/O 5c/O SUPPLIED/O Toll/O cashiers/O near/O Ladysmith/LOCATION could/O find/O themselves/O counting/O five/O cent/O coins/O from/O every/O minibus/O taxi/O passing/O through/O the/O plaza/O on/O Wednesday/O ./O 
Durban/LOCATION -/O Toll/O cashiers/O near/O Ladysmith/LOCATION could/O find/O themselves/O counting/O five/O cent/O coins/O from/O every/O minibus/O taxi/O passing/O through/O the/O plaza/O on/O Wednesday/O ./O 
This/O would/O form/O part/O of/O a/O protest/O by/O the/O KwaZulu-Natal/LOCATION taxi/O industry/O against/O the/O government/O 's/O taxi/O recapitalisation/O programme/O ,/O spokesmen/O said/O on/O Tuesday/O ./O 
KwaZulu-Natal/ORGANIZATION Transport/ORGANIZATION Alliance/ORGANIZATION chairman/O Eugene/PERSON Hadebe/PERSON said/O the/O five/O cent/O protest/O would/O be/O held/O at/O the/O Tugela/O toll/O plaza/O on/O the/O N3/O near/O Ladysmith/LOCATION ./O 
He/O urged/O taxi/O drivers/O to/O stock/O up/O on/O five/O cent/O coins/O to/O pay/O their/O toll/O fees/O ./O 
Taxi/O owners/O would/O also/O march/O on/O KwaZulu-Natal/LOCATION premier/O Zweli/PERSON Mkhize/PERSON 's/O office/O to/O hand/O over/O a/O memorandum/O of/O grievances/O ./O 
They/O were/O also/O dissatisfied/O with/O the/O provincial/O transport/O department/O 's/O administration/O and/O issuing/O of/O operating/O licences/O ./O 
Another/O grievance/O was/O the/O government/O 's/O decision/O to/O recognise/O the/O SA/ORGANIZATION National/ORGANIZATION Taxi/ORGANIZATION Council/ORGANIZATION -LRB-/O Santaco/ORGANIZATION -RRB-/O as/O the/O sole/O representative/O of/O the/O taxi/O industry/O ./O 
Hadebe/PERSON told/O a/O meeting/O of/O various/O taxi/O alliances/O at/O Durban/LOCATION 's/O Curries/O Fountain/O stadium/O that/O permission/O had/O been/O granted/O for/O the/O march/O in/O Pietermaritzburg/LOCATION ./O 
He/O said/O Santaco/PERSON did/O not/O represent/O his/O association/O or/O others/O ./O 
Concerned/O Taxi/O Operators/O chairman/O Thami/PERSON Ngcongo/PERSON said/O :/O ``/O They/O are/O the/O only/O people/O being/O recognised/O by/O government/O ./O 
They/O are/O not/O leading/O us/O ./O 
They/O are/O taking/O decisions/O without/O our/O consent/O ./O ''/O 
Earlier/O on/O Tuesday/O ,/O KwaZulu-Natal/LOCATION transport/O spokesman/O Kwanele/PERSON Ncalane/PERSON said/O the/O provincial/O government/O had/O ,/O as/O part/O of/O an/O agreement/O with/O Santaco/PERSON ,/O decided/O to/O approach/O the/O national/O government/O in/O an/O attempt/O to/O get/O it/O to/O delay/O the/O taxi/O recapitalisation/O programme/O in/O the/O province/O ./O 
Ncalane/PERSON said/O this/O had/O been/O agreed/O at/O a/O meeting/O between/O the/O provincial/O department/O and/O Santaco/LOCATION ./O 
``/O We/O decided/O that/O we/O needed/O to/O approach/O the/O national/O department/O of/O transport/O to/O consider/O the/O moratorium/O of/O implementing/O the/O taxi/O recapitalisation/O programme/O -LRB-/O TRP/O -RRB-/O ,/O so/O that/O we/O can/O engage/O with/O taxi/O operators/O ./O ''/O 
The/O R7/O .7/O billion/O TRP/O was/O first/O announced/O in/O 1999/O and/O came/O into/O effect/O in/O October/O 2006/O ./O 
It/O was/O intended/O to/O replace/O the/O country/O 's/O ageing/O minibus/O taxi/O fleet/O with/O safe/O ,/O modern/O vehicles/O ./O 
In/O terms/O of/O the/O TRP/ORGANIZATION ,/O taxi/O owners/O would/O each/O be/O paid/O R50/O ,000/O to/O have/O a/O vehicle/O scrapped/O ./O 
The/O owner/O could/O then/O use/O this/O money/O to/O exit/O the/O industry/O ,/O or/O as/O a/O deposit/O on/O a/O newer/O ,/O safer/O vehicle/O ./O 
Currently/O the/O amount/O paid/O is/O R63/O ,100/O per/O taxi/O ./O 
The/O TRP/ORGANIZATION was/O supposed/O to/O be/O introduced/O in/O KwaZulu-Natal/LOCATION in/O September/O ./O 
Ncalane/PERSON said/O the/O transport/O department/O would/O ask/O for/O an/O extension/O of/O six/O months/O to/O hold/O talks/O with/O taxi/O operators/O ./O 
He/O dismissed/O taxi/O operators/O '/O claims/O that/O the/O government/O wanted/O to/O scrap/O all/O Siyaya/O taxis/O ./O 
Siyaya/O minibus/O taxis/O ,/O originally/O known/O as/O Hi-Aces/O ,/O were/O built/O by/O Toyota/ORGANIZATION SA/O until/O the/O end/O of/O 2007/O ./O 
``/O When/O government/O compensates/O taxi/O operators/O they/O can/O not/O use/O that/O money/O to/O buy/O a/O vehicle/O that/O was/O bought/O in/O 2006/O and/O the/O years/O before/O ,/O ''/O Ncalane/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O There/O are/O certain/O provisions/O in/O the/O National/O Transport/O Act/O that/O talk/O about/O compliance/O of/O vehicles/O to/O be/O deemed/O roadworthy/O ./O ''/O 
He/O said/O that/O often/O the/O delays/O in/O issuing/O operating/O licences/O came/O about/O as/O a/O result/O of/O taxi/O owners/O not/O providing/O correct/O documentation/O ,/O or/O obtaining/O the/O necessary/O municipal/O approval/O for/O the/O route/O they/O would/O be/O operating/O ./O 
Ncalane/PERSON said/O there/O was/O no/O need/O for/O taxi/O operators/O to/O march/O on/O Wednesday/O as/O the/O department/O was/O in/O talks/O with/O Santaco/PERSON ./O 
However/O ,/O later/O on/O Tuesday/O afternoon/O ,/O he/O said/O the/O government/O was/O attempting/O to/O hold/O a/O meeting/O with/O the/O other/O taxi/O alliances/O ./O 
It/O was/O not/O immediately/O clear/O how/O commuters/O would/O be/O affected/O ./O 
Hadebe/PERSON and/O other/O Curries/O Fountain/O stadium/O speakers/O urged/O drivers/O not/O to/O stay/O away/O ,/O but/O to/O rather/O take/O commuters/O to/O work/O before/O joining/O the/O protest/O march/O in/O Pietermaritzburg/LOCATION ./O 
N3/O Toll/O Concession/O spokesman/O Con/PERSON Roux/PERSON said/O it/O would/O have/O extra/O staff/O on/O duty/O to/O help/O count/O the/O coins/O ./O 
-/O Sapa/ORGANIZATION unique_identifier/O Mass./LOCATION ./O 
Man/O Pays/O Off/O Mortgage/O With/O Pennies/O July/O 6/O ,/O 2012/O By/O LYNEKA/PERSON LITTLE/O via/O Good/O Morning/O America/O PHOTO/O :/O Tom/PERSON and/O Sandra/PERSON Daigle/PERSON show/O off/O the/O pennies/O they/O brought/O to/O the/O bank/O to/O make/O their/O final/O mortgage/O payment/O ./O 
Tom/PERSON and/O Sandra/PERSON Daigle/PERSON show/O off/O the/O pennies/O they/O brought/O to/O the/O bank/O to/O make/O their/O final/O mortgage/O payment/O ./O 
Derek/PERSON McLean/MetroWestDailyNews/PERSON ./O 
com/O A/O Milford/LOCATION ,/O Mass./LOCATION ,/O man/O saved/O his/O pennies/O to/O pay/O off/O his/O mortgage/O --/O literally/O ./O 
He/O carted/O more/O than/O 62,000/O pennies/O to/O the/O bank/O to/O make/O his/O last/O payment/O ./O 
``/O Thirty-five/O years/O ago/O when/O my/O wife/O and/O I/O took/O out/O our/O mortgage/O for/O our/O first/O home/O I/O happened/O to/O pick/O up/O a/O penny/O in/O a/O parking/O lot/O ,/O ''/O Thomas/PERSON Daigle/PERSON told/O ABC/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION ./O 
``/O I/O said/O ,/O I/O 'm/O going/O to/O pay/O our/O last/O mortgage/O in/O pennies/O ./O '/O ''/O 
And/O ,/O that/O 's/O exactly/O he/O did/O ./O 
In/O all/O ,/O that/O 's/O about/O 427/O pounds/O of/O pennies/O at/O 145/O pennies/O to/O the/O pound/O ,/O though/O pennies/O minted/O after/O 1982/O weigh/O in/O at/O 181/O to/O the/O pound/O ./O 
Daigle/PERSON says/O he/O did/O n't/O weigh/O them/O ./O 
The/O 60-year-old/O ,/O who/O would/O place/O his/O change/O and/O keys/O in/O a/O bowl/O each/O night/O ,/O would/O sift/O through/O the/O change/O and/O save/O his/O pennies/O ./O 
On/O a/O rainy/O or/O snowy/O night/O in/O central/O Massachusetts/LOCATION ,/O Daigle/PERSON would/O roll/O three/O to/O five/O packs/O of/O pennies/O and/O place/O them/O in/O a/O box/O in/O the/O basement/O ./O 
Along/O with/O the/O pennies/O in/O a/O box/O downstairs/O ,/O Daigle/PERSON would/O keep/O a/O scrap/O of/O paper/O with/O a/O running/O tab/O of/O the/O amount/O of/O rolls/O stored/O in/O the/O boxes/O downstairs/O ./O 
``/O After/O a/O few/O years/O of/O rolling/O pennies/O ,/O I/O said/O this/O is/O a/O doable/O thing/O to/O pay/O my/O mortgage/O off/O in/O pennies/O ,/O ''/O said/O Daigle/PERSON ./O 
In/O April/O ,/O the/O co-owner/O of/O Joseph/PERSON and/O Thomas/PERSON Opticians/PERSON brought/O the/O boxes/O of/O pennies/O around/O to/O the/O back/O at/O Milford/ORGANIZATION Federal/ORGANIZATION Savings/ORGANIZATION and/ORGANIZATION Loan/ORGANIZATION Association/ORGANIZATION and/O made/O his/O final/O payment/O on/O his/O 35th/O wedding/O anniversary/O ./O 
Daigle/PERSON warned/O the/O bank/O before/O coming/O in/O with/O the/O coppers/O ./O 
A/O long-time/O customer/O ,/O Daigle/PERSON opened/O a/O savings/O account/O at/O the/O bank/O when/O he/O was/O 10/O years/O old/O using/O money/O he/O made/O from/O mowing/O lawns/O ./O 
At/O the/O time/O ,/O one/O of/O his/O lawn/O customers/O was/O a/O teller/O named/O Mary/PERSON ,/O who/O worked/O at/O the/O bank/O ./O 
``/O When/O it/O was/O time/O to/O get/O married/O and/O buy/O a/O house/O ,/O this/O is/O the/O bank/O we/O wanted/O to/O use/O ,/O ''/O said/O Daigle/PERSON ,/O who/O married/O his/O high/O school/O sweetheart/O Sandra/PERSON in/O 1977/O ./O 
``/O We/O 're/O a/O local/O community/O bank/O and/O we/O 've/O been/O in/O business/O for/O many/O years/O ,/O ''/O a/O spokesperson/O for/O Milford/ORGANIZATION Federal/ORGANIZATION Savings/ORGANIZATION and/ORGANIZATION Loan/ORGANIZATION Association/ORGANIZATION told/O ABC/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION ./O 
``/O We/O are/O celebrating/O our/O 125th/O birthday/O this/O year/O ./O ''/O 
Thomas/PERSON Daigle/PERSON ``/O has/O been/O a/O customer/O of/O ours/O for/O a/O very/O long/O time/O and/O we/O were/O very/O pleased/O that/O he/O was/O able/O to/O accomplish/O his/O goals/O ./O 
It/O was/O a/O proud/O day/O for/O him/O ./O 
We/O are/O happy/O about/O that/O ,/O ''/O the/O spokesperson/O continued/O ./O 
He/O said/O his/O wife/O Sandra/PERSON merely/O shakes/O her/O head/O and/O says/O ``/O that/O 's/O my/O husband/O ,/O ''/O when/O asked/O about/O the/O penny/O savings/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O a/O man/O of/O my/O word/O and/O I/O 'm/O a/O man/O of/O commitment/O ,/O ''/O said/O Daigle/PERSON ./O 
``/O There/O is/O one/O thing/O you/O have/O in/O life/O :/O it/O 's/O your/O word/O ./O 
If/O you/O say/O you/O 're/O going/O to/O do/O something/O ,/O do/O it/O ./O ''/O 
Daigle/PERSON says/O he/O 's/O no/O longer/O saving/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O I/O never/O saved/O anything/O in/O my/O life/O other/O than/O pennies/O ,/O ''/O he/O added/O ./O 
While/O coming/O in/O to/O the/O office/O ,/O Daigle/PERSON says/O he/O stumbled/O upon/O a/O penny/O and/O picked/O it/O up/O ./O 
He/O said/O he/O 's/O hoping/O his/O lunch/O total/O is/O an/O odd/O number/O so/O that/O can/O get/O rid/O of/O it/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O saving/O nothing/O ,/O ''/O said/O Daigle/PERSON ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O not/O leaving/O my/O children/O with/O any/O kind/O of/O mess/O to/O clean/O away/O ./O ''/O 
He/O continued/O ,/O ``/O I/O 'm/O collecting/O grandchildren/O ./O 
I/O have/O four/O grandchildren/O ./O 
I/O live/O for/O them/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Thomas/PERSON Daigle/PERSON ,/O Massachusetts/LOCATION Man/O ,/O Pays/O Off/O Mortgage/O With/O Pennies/O AP/O Posted/O :/O 07/06/2012/O 9:20/O am/O EDT/O Updated/O :/O 07/06/2012/O 9:22/O am/O EDT/O Daigle/PERSON ,/O Massachusetts/LOCATION Man/O ,/O Pays/O Off/O Mortgage/O With/O Pennies/O >/O MILFORD/LOCATION ,/O Mass./LOCATION --/O A/O Massachusetts/LOCATION man/O who/O pledged/O to/O make/O the/O last/O mortgage/O payment/O on/O his/O home/O with/O pennies/O has/O fulfilled/O that/O promise/O ./O 
After/O warning/O his/O bank/O ,/O Thomas/PERSON Daigle/PERSON dropped/O off/O about/O 62,000/O pennies/O weighing/O 800/O pounds/O in/O two/O boxes/O for/O the/O final/O payment/O on/O the/O Milford/LOCATION home/O he/O and/O his/O wife/O ,/O Sandra/PERSON ,/O bought/O in/O 1977/O ./O 
He/O started/O saving/O his/O pennies/O when/O he/O moved/O in/O ./O 
The/O optician/O says/O his/O wife/O laughed/O whenever/O he/O would/O pick/O up/O a/O penny/O he/O found/O on/O the/O ground/O and/O say/O it/O was/O going/O to/O the/O mortgage/O ./O 
Daigle/PERSON says/O he/O 's/O just/O glad/O to/O have/O the/O coins/O out/O of/O his/O house/O ./O 
___/O unique_identifier/O Personal/O Finance/O Q&A/O :/O The/O Man/O Who/O Paid/O Off/O His/O Mortgage/O With/O 62,000/O Pennies/O By/O David/PERSON Wescott/PERSON July/O 11/O ,/O 2012/O ------------------------------------------------------------------------/O Q&A/O :/O The/O Man/O Who/O Paid/O Off/O His/O Mortgage/O With/O 62,000/O Pennies/O Photograph/O by/O Rex/O Ziak/Getty/O Images/O On/O the/O day/O of/O his/O 35/O ^/O th/O wedding/O anniversary/O ,/O Thomas/PERSON Daigle/PERSON ,/O an/O optician/O from/O Milford/LOCATION ,/O Mass./LOCATION ,/O walked/O into/O a/O local/O bank/O to/O make/O his/O final/O mortgage/O payment/O ./O 
Instead/O of/O carrying/O a/O checkbook/O ,/O Daigle/PERSON came/O armed/O with/O 62,000/O pennies/O stored/O in/O military-grade/O steel/O boxes/O ./O 
The/O total/O weight/O was/O more/O than/O 400/O pounds/O ./O 
The/O idea/O of/O paying/O off/O his/O house/O in/O pennies/O has/O been/O a/O recurring/O joke/O in/O the/O Daigle/PERSON household/O for/O more/O than/O three/O decades/O ./O 
Daigle/PERSON ,/O 60/O ,/O has/O been/O counting/O ,/O organizing/O ,/O and/O storing/O the/O pennies/O in/O his/O basement/O ,/O diligently/O wrapping/O them/O in/O paper/O rolls/O ./O 
Milford/ORGANIZATION Savings/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION Loan/ORGANIZATION Association/ORGANIZATION ,/O where/O they/O were/O deposited/O ,/O was/O apparently/O pleased/O with/O the/O inundation/O of/O change/O ./O 
Remarkably/O ,/O all/O the/O coins/O had/O been/O counted/O correctly/O ./O 
*/O Why/O did/O you/O make/O your/O final/O mortgage/O payment/O in/O pennies/O ?/O 
*/O It/O was/O a/O commitment/O I/O made/O to/O my/O wife/O ,/O Sandra/PERSON ./O 
After/O we/O signed/O our/O mortgage/O ,/O when/O we/O were/O on/O our/O way/O home/O ,/O I/O found/O a/O penny/O on/O the/O ground/O ./O 
I/O told/O my/O wife/O ,/O ``/O A/O penny/O toward/O our/O mortgage/O ./O ''/O 
She/O laughed/O ./O 
I/O told/O her/O we/O were/O going/O to/O pay/O our/O final/O mortgage/O payment/O in/O pennies/O ,/O and/O she/O did/O n't/O believe/O me/O ./O 
I/O wanted/O to/O show/O her/O I/O was/O a/O man/O of/O my/O word/O ,/O and/O it/O was/O a/O pretty/O extensive/O ongoing/O joke/O ./O 
I/O started/O putting/O pennies/O in/O a/O change/O bowl/O in/O the/O hallway/O ./O 
The/O quarters/O and/O nickels/O --/O you/O use/O those/O to/O buy/O coffee/O ./O 
But/O the/O pennies/O ?/O 
I/O just/O kept/O storing/O them/O ./O 
On/O winter/O weekends/O I/O would/O take/O some/O time/O to/O roll/O pennies/O ./O 
Why/O not/O ?/O 
My/O kids/O liked/O it/O ,/O and/O we/O 'd/O do/O it/O together/O ./O 
There/O is/O n't/O a/O whole/O lot/O to/O do/O on/O snowy/O winter/O weekends/O in/O Massachusetts/LOCATION ./O 
*/O Where/O 'd/O you/O store/O them/O ?/O 
*/O When/O there/O were/O too/O many/O for/O a/O change/O bowl/O ,/O I/O started/O keeping/O them/O in/O a/O glass/O orange/O juice/O bottle/O --/O they/O do/O n't/O even/O make/O those/O anymore/O ./O 
I/O 'd/O roll/O the/O pennies/O into/O groups/O of/O 50/O on/O my/O workbench/O in/O the/O basement/O ./O 
When/O there/O got/O to/O be/O too/O many/O ,/O I/O 'd/O store/O the/O rolled/O pennies/O in/O a/O wooden/O grape/O crate/O --/O the/O kind/O you/O get/O when/O you/O buy/O grapes/O in/O bulk/O ./O 
Things/O just/O kept/O going/O ,/O and/O then/O soon/O enough/O ,/O when/O I/O 'd/O pick/O up/O the/O crate/O ,/O the/O bottom/O would/O fall/O out/O ./O 
I/O 'd/O have/O to/O screw/O it/O back/O together/O ./O 
One/O day/O I/O was/O looking/O through/O a/O catalog/O selling/O hydraulics/O parts/O ./O 
They/O were/O advertising/O some/O steel/O military/O boxes/O --/O the/O kind/O of/O things/O you/O see/O at/O army/O surplus/O stores/O ./O 
The/O ad/O said/O they/O were/O great/O for/O storing/O things/O ./O 
I/O decided/O to/O get/O one/O ,/O and/O since/O I/O noticed/O the/O shipping/O and/O handling/O would/O be/O the/O same/O ,/O changed/O my/O order/O to/O get/O two/O ./O 
*/O Did/O you/O ever/O find/O any/O rare/O pennies/O that/O might/O be/O worth/O more/O than/O 1/O cents/O ?/O 
*/O No/O ,/O that/O was/O n't/O my/O concern/O or/O interest/O ./O 
As/O long/O as/O it/O was/O a/O penny/O and/O could/O be/O rolled/O into/O a/O group/O of/O 50/O ,/O that/O was/O fine/O ./O 
*/O So/O how/O 'd/O you/O get/O them/O to/O the/O bank/O ?/O 
*/O I/O had/O the/O pennies/O in/O one/O of/O the/O steel/O boxes/O ,/O and/O there/O was/O no/O way/O I/O could/O lift/O it/O ./O 
They/O weighed/O about/O 400/O pounds/O altogether/O ./O 
I/O split/O them/O up/O and/O was/O able/O to/O get/O them/O in/O the/O back/O of/O my/O SUV/O ./O 
Once/O the/O pennies/O were/O in/O ,/O along/O with/O the/O steel/O boxes/O ,/O my/O wife/O ,/O who/O is/O disabled/O ,/O came/O along/O ./O 
Her/O wheel/O chair/O went/O on/O top/O of/O the/O boxes/O ,/O and/O we/O headed/O to/O the/O bank/O ./O 
*/O What/O was/O the/O Milford/ORGANIZATION Federal/ORGANIZATION Savings/ORGANIZATION &/ORGANIZATION Loan/ORGANIZATION 's/O reaction/O ?/O 
*/O It/O 's/O a/O small/O town/O ,/O and/O I/O know/O the/O people/O who/O work/O at/O the/O savings/O &/O loan/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O an/O optician/O ,/O and/O many/O of/O them/O come/O to/O me/O for/O my/O work/O ./O 
They/O certainly/O knew/O we/O were/O coming/O ./O 
It/O was/O my/O wife/O 's/O and/O -LSB-/O my/O -RSB-/O 35/O ^/O th/O wedding/O anniversary/O ,/O the/O final/O payment/O on/O our/O mortgage/O ,/O and/O the/O bank/O was/O celebrating/O their/O 125/O ^/O th/O year/O in/O business/O ./O 
I/O 've/O had/O an/O account/O there/O since/O I/O was/O 10/O --/O I/O used/O to/O deposit/O the/O money/O I/O made/O mowing/O lawns/O at/O that/O bank/O ./O 
It/O took/O them/O two/O days/O to/O deposit/O the/O pennies/O -LRB-/O they/O had/O to/O remove/O the/O paper/O wrappers/O -RRB-/O ,/O but/O they/O seemed/O happy/O for/O me/O and/O for/O what/O I/O had/O accomplished/O ./O 
*/O Now/O that/O the/O joke/O 's/O over/O ,/O will/O you/O collect/O something/O else/O ?/O 
*/O I/O 'm/O done/O with/O the/O collecting/O ,/O in/O that/O I/O reached/O that/O goal/O ./O 
I/O would/O like/O to/O keep/O collecting/O grandchildren/O --/O I/O now/O have/O four/O ./O 
It/O 's/O been/O a/O great/O project/O for/O my/O family/O ,/O and/O I/O think/O there/O 's/O a/O good/O example/O in/O it/O ./O 
When/O you/O find/O a/O penny/O on/O the/O ground/O and/O pick/O it/O up/O ,/O it/O 's/O an/O instant/O that/O brings/O back/O memories/O of/O childhood/O ./O 
It/O 's/O a/O special/O moment/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Asda/ORGANIZATION stops/O woman/O paying/O for/O weekly/O shop/O with/O #/O 2/O coins/O -/O so/O what/O are/O your/O rights/O when/O paying/O with/O coins/O ?/O 
By/O Andrew/PERSON Oxlade/PERSON Published/O :/O 08:11/O EST/O ,/O 10/O September/O 2012/O |/O Updated/O :/O 08:29/O EST/O ,/O 10/O September/O 2012/O A/O woman/O was/O turned/O away/O from/O the/O checkout/O at/O her/O local/O Asda/ORGANIZATION store/O when/O she/O tried/O to/O pay/O for/O her/O #/O 100/O weekly/O shop/O in/O #/O 2/O coins/O ./O 
She/O is/O the/O latest/O to/O have/O been/O pulled/O up/O for/O trying/O to/O settle/O a/O bill/O with/O coins/O ./O 
But/O Joanne/PERSON Bath/PERSON ,/O of/O Gosport/LOCATION ,/O Hampshire/LOCATION ,/O had/O the/O law/O on/O her/O side/O ./O 
She/O has/O had/O an/O instant/O apology/O from/O the/O company/O ,/O owned/O by/O US/LOCATION giant/O WalMart/ORGANIZATION ,/O and/O was/O given/O a/O #/O 15/O gift/O voucher/O ./O 
Joanne/PERSON was/O left/O fuming/O after/O staff/O refused/O to/O accept/O the/O 50/O #/O 2/O coins/O and/O told/O her/O to/O come/O back/O with/O notes/O ./O 
