Insurance/O company/O pays/O elderly/O man/O 's/O $/O 21,000/O settlement/O with/O coins/O A/O California/LOCATION insurance/O company/O ,/O apparently/O none/O too/O happy/O about/O losing/O a/O court/O battle/O ,/O paid/O an/O elderly/O man/O 's/O settlement/O with/O loose/O change/O ./O 
In/O 2012/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O a/O 76-year-old/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION man/O ,/O filed/O suit/O against/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O after/O an/O employee/O with/O the/O company/O allegedly/O assaulted/O Carrasco/PERSON ./O 
The/O suit/O was/O finally/O settled/O in/O June/O of/O this/O year/O when/O the/O company/O agreed/O to/O pay/O Carrasco/PERSON $/O 21,000/O ./O 
Instead/O of/O sending/O Carrasco/PERSON a/O check/O however/O ,/O eight/O employees/O with/O the/O company/O arrived/O at/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O 's/O office/O carrying/O more/O than/O 16/O five-gallon/O buckets/O full/O of/O pennies/O ,/O dimes/O ,/O nickels/O and/O quarters/O ./O 
Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON ,/O attorney/O for/O Carrasco/PERSON ,/O stated/O Carrasco/PERSON recently/O had/O hernia/O surgery/O and/O would/O be/O unable/O to/O lift/O even/O one/O of/O the/O buckets/O ,/O much/O less/O carry/O all/O of/O them/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON went/O on/O to/O tell/O CBS/ORGANIZATION Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION :/O ''/O ``/O There/O 's/O over/O 16/O buckets/O of/O quarters/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O pennies/O ./O 
It/O 's/O going/O to/O take/O us/O at/O least/O ,/O conservatively/O ,/O one/O week/O to/O count/O that/O whole/O amount/O of/O money/O ./O ''/O ''/O 
Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O pays/O 76-year-old/O man/O $/O 21,000/O settlement/O with/O buckets/O of/O pennies/O ,/O dimes/O ,/O nickels/O and/O quarters/O ./O 
When/O speaking/O to/O NBC/ORGANIZATION Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ,/O Carrasco/PERSON asked/O why/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O why/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O ``/O did/O n't/O like/O their/O customers/O ./O ''/O 
He/O went/O on/O to/O say/O :/O ''/O ``/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ./O 
We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ./O ''/O ''/O 
The/O story/O has/O gone/O viral/O on/O Twitter/O ,/O with/O many/O calling/O for/O a/O boycott/O of/O the/O company/O ./O 
The/O company/O 's/O Yelp/O page/O has/O also/O been/O flooded/O with/O criticism/O ,/O with/O one/O person/O saying/O :/O ''/O ``/O Are/O you/O looking/O to/O be/O abused/O ,/O humiliated/O ,/O and/O demeaned/O by/O an/O insurance/O company/O ?/O 
Then/O look/O no/O further/O than/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O !/O ''/O ''/O 
Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O did/O not/O respond/O to/O an/O email/O request/O for/O comment/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Insurance/O company/O pays/O elderly/O man/O 's/O settlement/O in/O buckets/O of/O coins/O Wow/O .../O There/O 's/O childish/O behaviour/O and/O then/O there/O 's/O this/O ./O 
A/O Californian/O insurance/O company/O has/O paid/O a/O 73-year-old/O man/O a/O settlement/O owed/O to/O him/O in/O buckets/O of/O change/O ./O 
Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON filed/O a/O lawsuit/O against/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O company/O back/O in/O 2012/O ,/O claiming/O he/O had/O been/O physically/O assaulted/O by/O one/O of/O their/O employees/O ./O 
The/O company/O agreed/O to/O a/O settlement/O with/O Andres/PERSON in/O June/O and/O they/O decided/O to/O pay/O him/O in/O the/O form/O of/O a/O cheque/O -/O along/O with/O buckets/O and/O buckets/O of/O coins/O ./O 
The/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O ,/O quarters/O and/O pennies/O add/O up/O to/O more/O than/O $/O 15,700/O -LRB-/O $/O 21,000/O -RRB-/O ./O 
Mr/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O lawyer/O told/O KNBC/ORGANIZATION that/O Andres/PERSON has/O just/O had/O a/O hernia/O operation/O and/O there/O was/O no/O way/O he/O would/O be/O able/O to/O lift/O one/O of/O five-gallon/O buckets/O ,/O let/O alone/O the/O dozens/O left/O by/O eight/O employees/O of/O the/O company/O ./O 
``/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ,/O ''/O Carrasco/PERSON said/O in/O a/O statement/O ./O 
``/O We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ./O ''/O 
The/O company/O had/O no/O comment/O to/O make/O when/O asked/O but/O their/O Yelp/O page/O has/O been/O inundated/O with/O negative/O reviews/O since/O the/O story/O broke/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Insurance/O Company/O Pays/O Elderly/O Man/O 's/O Settlement/O in/O Coins/O Funny/O :/O A/O Packers/ORGANIZATION fan/O wins/O 20/O bucks/O from/O a/O Bears/O fan/O when/O Green/ORGANIZATION Bay/ORGANIZATION beats/O Chicago/LOCATION again/O ,/O and/O the/O Bears/O fan/O pays/O him/O in/O all/O pennies/O ./O 
Not/O funny/O :/O An/O elderly/O man/O is/O assaulted/O by/O an/O insurance/O company/O employee/O and/O they/O pay/O their/O entire/O $/O 21,000/O settlement/O to/O him/O in/O loose/O change/O ,/O with/O one/O bucket/O so/O heavy/O that/O he/O ca/O n't/O lift/O it/O ./O 
insurance/O company/O pays/O man/O in/O all/O coins/O But/O according/O to/O CBS/ORGANIZATION Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ,/O that/O is/O exactly/O what/O happened/O to/O a/O 76-year-old/O man/O in/O East/ORGANIZATION Los/ORGANIZATION Angeles/ORGANIZATION recently/O when/O he/O finally/O received/O his/O settlement/O money/O from/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION as/O a/O result/O of/O an/O alleged/O assault/O on/O the/O old/O man/O by/O one/O of/O their/O employees/O two/O years/O ago/O ./O 
It/O took/O eight/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O employees/O to/O drop/O off/O more/O than/O 16/O buckets/O of/O loose/O quarters/O ,/O dimes/O ,/O nickels/O and/O pennies/O at/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O 's/O office/O ,/O and/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O said/O it/O will/O probably/O take/O more/O than/O a/O week/O to/O count/O it/O to/O make/O sure/O it/O 's/O all/O there/O ./O 
We/O 're/O unsure/O what/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O has/O up/O their/O sleeves/O for/O an/O encore/O ./O 
Perhaps/O something/O like/O paying/O an/O old/O woman/O one/O of/O their/O employees/O pushed/O out/O of/O her/O wheelchair/O a/O few/O years/O ago/O in/O Nepalese/O coins/O ?/O 
That/O would/O be/O sufficient/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Insurance/O company/O pays/O in/O coins/O Adriana/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Services/ORGANIZATION in/O California/LOCATION have/O angered/O a/O man/O by/O paying/O him/O his/O $/O 15,100/O settlement/O in/O coinage/O ./O 
The/O company/O delivered/O buckets/O full/O of/O dimes/O ,/O quarters/O and/O nickels/O to/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON 's/O lawyer/O Mr/PERSON Gallo/PERSON at/O his/O office/O ./O 
The/O dispute/O had/O been/O over/O an/O alleged/O assault/O claim/O from/O Mr/O Carrasco/PERSON against/O the/O insurance/O company/O following/O a/O prior/O argument/O over/O his/O car/O insurance/O ./O 
The/O company/O paid/O out/O but/O clearly/O were/O not/O very/O happy/O about/O it/O ./O 
There/O are/O around/O 17/O buckets/O and/O his/O lawyers/O added/O ;/O ``/O They/O probably/O -LRB-/O each/O -RRB-/O weigh/O anywhere/O between/O 70/O to/O 100/O pounds/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O assuming/O ,/O because/O I/O ca/O n't/O lift/O them/O ./O 
It/O 's/O insulting/O to/O my/O client/O ./O 
He/O 's/O 76-years-old/O ;/O he/O just/O had/O a/O hernia/O operation/O ,/O ''/O he/O added/O ./O 
``/O He/O feels/O that/O he/O was/O n't/O treated/O as/O a/O human/O being/O ./O ''/O 
Following/O what/O happened/O Mr/O Carrasco/PERSON has/O asked/O the/O company/O to/O take/O back/O the/O coins/O and/O instead/O write/O him/O a/O cheque/O for/O the/O amount/O ./O 
unique_identifier/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Company/ORGANIZATION Pays/O Man/O $/O 21,000/O With/O Buckets/O Of/O Loose/O Change/O Money/O is/O money/O --/O but/O it/O 's/O a/O whole/O lot/O easier/O to/O receive/O a/O bunch/O of/O it/O with/O a/O check/O or/O even/O cash/O ,/O than/O entirely/O in/O loose/O change/O ./O 
That/O 's/O how/O one/O California/LOCATION man/O said/O an/O insurance/O company/O paid/O him/O $/O 21,000/O in/O a/O legal/O settlement/O ,/O dropping/O off/O more/O than/O 16/O five-gallon/O buckets/O filled/O with/O coins/O ./O 
The/O 73-year-old/O man/O filed/O a/O lawsuit/O in/O 2012/O against/O an/O employee/O of/O the/O insurance/O company/O ,/O claiming/O he/O 'd/O been/O physically/O assaulted/O ,/O reports/O NBC/ORGANIZATION Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ./O 
After/O the/O two/O parties/O reached/O a/O settlement/O ,/O the/O insurance/O company/O paid/O up/O :/O The/O man/O 's/O attorney/O says/O eight/O employees/O of/O the/O insurance/O company/O showed/O up/O to/O his/O office/O in/O a/O van/O bearing/O five-gallon/O containers/O full/O of/O coins/O ,/O and/O left/O them/O in/O the/O waiting/O room/O ./O 
``/O There/O 's/O over/O 16/O buckets/O of/O quarters/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O pennies/O ./O 
It/O 's/O going/O to/O take/O us/O at/O least/O ,/O conservatively/O ,/O one/O week/O to/O count/O that/O whole/O amount/O of/O money/O ,/O ''/O the/O attorney/O told/O CBS/ORGANIZATION Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION ,/O with/O his/O client/O --/O who/O recently/O had/O a/O hernia/O operation/O and/O ca/O n't/O lift/O much/O --/O adding/O ,/O ``/O It/O 's/O too/O heavy/O ./O ''/O 
``/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O -LSB-/O the/O insurance/O company/O -RSB-/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O in/O a/O statement/O ./O 
``/O We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Company/ORGANIZATION Pays/ORGANIZATION Man/ORGANIZATION 's/O Settlement/O With/O $/O 21,000/O in/O Coins/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON reached/O a/O settlement/O with/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION ,/ORGANIZATION Inc./ORGANIZATION this/O past/O June/O following/O a/O lawsuit/O he/O filed/O in/O 2012/O in/O which/O he/O alleged/O an/O employee/O of/O the/O company/O physically/O assaulted/O him/O ./O 
The/O company/O paid/O his/O settlement/O with/O a/O check/O but/O also/O ,/O his/O attorney/O claims/O ,/O in/O buckets/O of/O change/O that/O amount/O to/O more/O than/O $/O 21,000/O ./O 
Carrasco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O told/O NBC/ORGANIZATION Los/ORGANIZATION Angeles/ORGANIZATION that/O eight/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O employees/O pulled/O up/O in/O a/O van/O to/O his/O office/O and/O unloaded/O multiple/O five-gallon/O buckets/O full/O of/O quarters/O ,/O dimes/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O and/O pennies/O ./O 
Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 73/O ,/O had/O just/O undergone/O surgery/O for/O a/O hernia/O ,/O and/O was/O still/O too/O weak/O to/O lift/O any/O of/O the/O buckets/O of/O change/O ./O 
``/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O ,/O is/O this/O the/O way/O you/O treat/O everyone/O ?/O ''/O 
Carrasco/PERSON said/O in/O a/O statement/O ./O 
``/O Why/O do/O n't/O you/O like/O your/O clients/O ?/O ''/O 
As/O the/O //O Atlanta/LOCATION Journal-Constitution/O //O points/O out/O ,/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O 's/O Yelp/O page/O has/O been/O attacked/O with/O negative/O reviews/O ./O 
From/O one/O review/O :/O I/O wish/O I/O could/O 've/O given/O them/O NO/O stars/O from/O the/O way/O they/O treated/O my/O uncle/O Andres/PERSON C/PERSON ./O 
How/O dare/O you/O call/O yourself/O a/O place/O of/O business/O ./O 
These/O people/O are/O nothing/O but/O money/O hungry/O idiots/O ./O 
They/O care/O only/O for/O money/O and/O not/O any/O of/O their/O customers/O ./O 
My/O advice/O ,/O go/O with/O someone/O else/O ./O 
These/O crooks/O will/O get/O their/O karma/O in/O due/O time/O ./O 
``/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ,/O ''/O Carrasco/PERSON said/O in/O his/O statement/O ./O 
``/O We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Insurance/O company/O pays/O settlement/O in/O buckets/O of/O loose/O change/O Stories/O of/O abuse/O continue/O as/O public/O expresses/O disdain/O for/O insulting/O move/O by/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION to/O elderly/O injured/O man/O --/O a/O lesson/O in/O how/O to/O stop/O insurance/O abuse/O in/O the/O future/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON with/O loose/O change/O settlement/O from/O Adrianas/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION I/O just/O started/O writing/O about/O a/O client/O of/O Michigan/O Auto/O Law/O attorney/O Tom/PERSON James/PERSON ,/O who/O went/O to/O an/O IME/O and/O was/O ordered/O a/O urine/O test/O to/O see/O if/O she/O was/O taking/O her/O medications/O as/O prescribed/O ./O 
The/O insurance/O company/O ,/O Bristol/ORGANIZATION West/ORGANIZATION ,/O then/O refused/O to/O pay/O for/O the/O urine/O test/O that/O they/O sent/O her/O to/O because/O it/O was/O unrelated/O to/O her/O car/O accident/O !/O 
And/O then/O I/O heard/O about/O what/O Adriana/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION just/O did/O to/O an/O elderly/O injured/O man/O ,/O by/O paying/O him/O in/O buckets/O of/O loose/O change/O -LRB-/O my/O own/O 2/O cents/O on/O this/O one/O below/O -RRB-/O ./O 
But/O as/O an/O attorney/O who/O 's/O dealt/O with/O nearly/O every/O insurance/O company/O in/O Michigan/LOCATION representing/O car/O accident/O victims/O ,/O I/O thought/O I/O 've/O seen/O just/O about/O all/O of/O the/O dirty/O tricks/O the/O insurance/O industry/O will/O pull/O to/O get/O out/O of/O paying/O claims/O --/O everything/O from/O the/O ``/O Delay/O ,/O Deny/O ,/O Defend/O ''/O tactic/O to/O Farm/ORGANIZATION Bureau/ORGANIZATION and/O State/ORGANIZATION Farm/ORGANIZATION trying/O to/O require/O a/O man/O to/O have/O insurance/O on/O his/O motorized/O wheelchair/O as/O a/O way/O of/O denying/O his/O claim/O for/O medical/O benefits/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O I/O wonder/O if/O this/O latest/O story/O is/O a/O race/O to/O the/O bottom/O by/O the/O insurance/O industry/O ./O 
In/O states/O like/O Michigan/LOCATION ,/O insurers/O do/O this/O because/O they/O can/O ./O 
Michigan/LOCATION is/O one/O of/O the/O few/O states/O without/O bad/O faith/O laws/O or/O punitive/O damages/O that/O can/O protect/O people/O from/O insurance/O company/O abuse/O ./O 
But/O what/O happened/O in/O this/O latest/O incident/O with/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O and/O the/O loose/O change/O is/O different/O --/O more/O of/O an/O obscene/O gesture/O than/O insurance/O company/O bad/O faith/O ./O 
This/O is/O certainly/O an/O ugly/O new/O low/O ./O 
Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON filed/O a/O lawsuit/O in/O 2012/O against/O Adriana/ORGANIZATION 's/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION ,/ORGANIZATION Inc./ORGANIZATION alleging/O he/O was/O physically/O assaulted/O by/O one/O of/O the/O company/O 's/O employees/O ./O 
After/O agreeing/O to/O a/O settlement/O with/O Mr./O Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 73/O ,/O in/O June/O ,/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O decided/O to/O deliver/O the/O funds/O in/O the/O form/O of/O a/O check/O --/O as/O well/O as/O $/O 21,000/O in/O quarters/O ,/O dimes/O ,/O nickels/O and/O pennies/O ,/O according/O to/O a/O recent/O story/O on/O NBC/ORGANIZATION ,/O ``/O Company/O Pays/O Settlement/O in/O Buckets/O of/O Loose/O Change/O ./O ''/O 
When/O the/O time/O to/O pony/O up/O for/O the/O settlement/O came/O ,/O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O said/O eight/O of/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O employees/O arrived/O at/O Mr./O Carasco/PERSON 's/O attorney/O 's/O office/O in/O a/O van/O with/O five-gallon/O buckets/O full/O of/O coins/O ./O 
They/O dumped/O them/O in/O the/O waiting/O room/O and/O left/O ./O 
That/O 's/O why/O I/O wrote/O above/O this/O reminds/O me/O more/O of/O an/O obscene/O gesture/O by/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O ./O 
You/O actually/O have/O to/O work/O pretty/O hard/O to/O get/O five-gallon/O buckets/O of/O coins/O ,/O and/O then/O a/O van/O and/O eight/O employees/O to/O even/O do/O this/O to/O a/O person/O ./O 
How/O utterly/O petty/O and/O disrespectful/O of/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O to/O treat/O this/O man/O in/O such/O a/O way/O ./O 
Like/O many/O insurance/O companies/O ,/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O had/O no/O problem/O taking/O Mr./O Carrasco/PERSON 's/O money/O for/O his/O premium/O ./O 
But/O when/O it/O came/O time/O to/O pay/O the/O claim/O that/O the/O insurance/O company/O agreed/O to/O ,/O well/O ,/O let/O 's/O just/O say/O ,/O it/O acted/O less/O than/O honorably/O ./O 
Arm/O extended/O ./O 
Make/O fist/O ./O 
Extend/O middle/O finger/O to/O Mr./O Carrasco/PERSON ./O 
What/O kind/O of/O professionalism/O and/O regard/O does/O this/O show/O ?/O 
People/O might/O say/O I/O 'm/O jaded/O or/O cynical/O because/O I/O 'm/O an/O insurance/O attorney/O and/O I/O see/O acts/O like/O the/O urine/O test/O I/O wrote/O about/O or/O other/O insurance/O company/O horror/O stories/O all/O the/O time/O ./O 
But/O it/O is/O n't/O just/O me/O ./O 
Many/O of/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O own/O customers/O and/O others/O have/O taken/O to/O Yelp/O to/O let/O their/O displeasure/O be/O known/O ./O 
Why/O do/O these/O insurance/O company/O horror/O stories/O keep/O happening/O ?/O 
They/O keep/O happening/O because/O these/O insurance/O companies/O are/O making/O record/O profits/O ./O 
Just/O look/O at/O what/O Allstate/ORGANIZATION -LRB-/O of/O Delay/O ,/O Deny/O ,/O and/O Defend/O -RRB-/O fame/O made/O last/O year/O ,/O or/O State/ORGANIZATION Farm/ORGANIZATION ,/O or/O so/O many/O others/O ./O 
They/O happen/O because/O insurance/O companies/O get/O away/O with/O it/O ,/O and/O they/O are/O not/O being/O punished/O by/O consumers/O because/O the/O hundreds/O of/O millions/O of/O dollars/O in/O advertising/O they/O spend/O create/O a/O false/O reality/O that/O these/O insurance/O companies/O care/O ./O 
They/O are/O ``/O like/O a/O good/O neighbor/O ''/O or/O -LSB-/O insert/O favorite/O insurance/O company/O tagline/O here/O -RSB-/O ./O 
But/O perhaps/O the/O public/O eruption/O of/O anger/O that/O has/O taken/O place/O on/O Yelp/O and/O other/O social/O media/O sites/O after/O what/O happened/O to/O Mr./O Carrasco/PERSON can/O serve/O as/O a/O lesson/O ./O 
I/O write/O about/O these/O stories/O ,/O and/O I/O publish/O a/O list/O every/O year/O or/O so/O of/O my/O worst/O insurance/O companies/O based/O upon/O the/O personal/O experiences/O I/O have/O as/O an/O attorney/O here/O and/O what/O I/O see/O ./O 
But/O perhaps/O attorneys/O like/O myself/O and/O aggrieved/O accident/O victims/O should/O be/O reaching/O out/O to/O the/O media/O as/O well/O ,/O and/O sending/O these/O real-life/O examples/O of/O insurance/O company/O abuse/O to/O news/O reporters/O ./O 
And/O perhaps/O ,/O just/O perhaps/O ,/O if/O the/O outcry/O on/O social/O media/O is/O loud/O enough/O ,/O and/O if/O the/O reviews/O on/O sites/O like/O Yelp/O become/O big/O enough/O ,/O maybe/O this/O will/O force/O these/O companies/O to/O do/O what/O they/O should/O be/O doing/O anyways/O in/O exchange/O for/O taking/O our/O premium/O dollars/O ./O 
Treat/O people/O the/O right/O way/O ./O 
Do/O the/O right/O thing/O ./O 
unique_identifier/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Company/ORGANIZATION Settles/O Claim/O In/O $/O 21K/O Of/O Loose/O Coins/O An/O insurance/O company/O has/O paid/O off/O a/O $/O 21,000/O settlement/O to/O an/O elderly/O east/O LA/LOCATION man/O in/O buckets/O of/O loose/O coins/O ./O 
Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O 76/O ,/O filed/O a/O lawsuit/O against/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O two/O years/O ago/O after/O he/O was/O allegedly/O assaulted/O by/O one/O of/O its/O employees/O ./O 
The/O company/O finally/O agreed/O to/O settle/O the/O case/O recently/O and/O paid/O Carrasco/PERSON in/O buckets/O of/O spare/O change/O ./O 
``/O There/O 's/O over/O 16/O buckets/O of/O quarters/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O pennies/O ./O 
It/O 's/O going/O to/O take/O us/O at/O least/O ,/O conservatively/O ,/O one/O week/O to/O count/O that/O whole/O amount/O of/O money/O ,/O ''/O attorney/O Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O It/O 's/O too/O heavy/O ,/O ''/O Carrasco/PERSON added/O ./O 
Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O did/O not/O return/O calls/O for/O comment/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Insurance/O news/O made/O when/O a/O settlement/O was/O paid/O entirely/O in/O quarters/O A/O prominent/O businessman/O in/O Illinois/LOCATION disagreed/O with/O the/O payout/O from/O his/O son/O 's/O auto/O policy/O and/O retaliated/O in/O a/O unique/O way/O ./O 
In/O retaliation/O for/O what/O an/O Illinois/LOCATION businessman/O felt/O was/O not/O a/O fair/O outcome/O in/O an/O auto/O payout/O following/O the/O death/O of/O his/O son/O ,/O he/O is/O making/O insurance/O news/O by/O paying/O a/O portion/O of/O the/O final/O settlement/O using/O thousands/O upon/O thousands/O of/O pounds/O of/O quarters/O ./O 
This/O ,/O according/O to/O one/O of/O the/O attorneys/O who/O was/O involved/O in/O the/O auto/O payout/O case/O ./O 
The/O attorney/O ,/O Douglas/PERSON Dorris/PERSON ,/O provided/O confirmation/O that/O when/O Roger/PERSON Herrin/PERSON came/O to/O the/O law/O firm/O to/O pay/O for/O a/O portion/O of/O the/O settlement/O ,/O he/O was/O armed/O with/O 75/O bags/O ,/O each/O of/O which/O contained/O 4,000/O quarters/O ./O 
Each/O bag/O weighed/O 48/O pounds/O and/O totaled/O $/O 75,000/O and/O 3,600/O pounds/O total/O ./O 
In/O order/O to/O haul/O the/O load/O away/O ,/O the/O firm/O was/O required/O to/O hire/O a/O Brinks/O truck/O ,/O upon/O which/O point/O the/O coins/O all/O needed/O to/O be/O counted/O ./O 
Insurance/O News/O payment/O in/O quarters/O Herrin/PERSON made/O this/O insurance/O news/O making/O move/O in/O protest/O of/O the/O settlement/O that/O required/O him/O to/O pay/O ./O 
Herrin/PERSON is/O a/O retired/O podiatrist/O who/O is/O 76/O years/O old/O ./O 
His/O company/O owns/O three/O nursing/O homes/O in/O Illinois/LOCATION and/O he/O remains/O a/O member/O of/O the/O Southern/ORGANIZATION Illinois/ORGANIZATION University/ORGANIZATION </O http://siu.edu//O >/O board/O of/O trustees/O ./O 
He/O has/O also/O previously/O served/O on/O other/O state/O government/O boards/O ./O 
Among/O them/O was/O the/O Illinois/ORGANIZATION Finance/ORGANIZATION Authority/ORGANIZATION ./O 
This/O insurance/O news/O followed/O a/O case/O in/O which/O Herrin/PERSON 's/O adolescent/O son/O ,/O Michael/PERSON ,/O was/O killed/O in/O a/O car/O accident/O in/O June/O 2001/O ./O 
Michael/PERSON had/O been/O a/O passenger/O in/O a/O Jeep/O Cherokee/O ,/O when/O a/O truck/O ran/O a/O stop/O sign/O and/O struck/O the/O vehicle/O in/O which/O he/O was/O riding/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O court/O 's/O records/O ./O 
Michael/PERSON was/O killed/O when/O he/O was/O thrown/O from/O the/O vehicle/O ./O 
Two/O other/O teens/O in/O the/O Jeep/O --/O Ross/PERSON Duncan/PERSON and/O Jared/PERSON Head/PERSON --/O were/O also/O injured/O ,/O as/O was/O Duncan/PERSON 's/O mother/O ,/O who/O was/O the/O driver/O at/O the/O time/O ./O 
Court/O records/O also/O showed/O that/O there/O were/O a/O number/O of/O different/O types/O of/O coverage/O in/O Michael/PERSON Herrin/PERSON 's/O estate/O ,/O totaling/O about/O $/O 5.5/O million/O ./O 
The/O insurance/O news/O a/O settlement/O offer/O of/O $/O 1.65/O million/O was/O accepted/O by/O Roger/PERSON Herrin/PERSON on/O behalf/O of/O the/O estate/O ./O 
Another/O $/O 800,000/O in/O coverage/O came/O from/O the/O Jeep/O owner/O 's/O policy/O ,/O and/O the/O truck/O 's/O policy/O added/O another/O $/O 100,000/O in/O coverage/O ,/O of/O which/O Herrin/PERSON was/O awarded/O $/O 677,851/O by/O a/O judge/O ./O 
However/O ,/O the/O insurance/O news/O escalated/O when/O an/O appellate/O court/O determined/O that/O Herrin/PERSON 's/O estate/O was/O not/O entitled/O to/O money/O from/O the/O Jeep/O owners/O '/O coverage/O under/O Illinois/LOCATION law/O because/O it/O had/O already/O received/O a/O much/O larger/O payout/O ./O 
A/O settlement/O was/O then/O reached/O in/O which/O Herrin/PERSON was/O required/O to/O pay/O back/O money/O to/O the/O other/O victims/O in/O the/O accident/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Insurer/O pays/O off/O lawsuit/O with/O thousands/O in/O coins/O Los/LOCATION Angeles-area/LOCATION man/O had/O accused/O the/O company/O of/O assault/O in/O 2012/O A/O California/LOCATION insurance/O company/O paid/O off/O a/O lawsuit/O by/O delivering/O $/O 21,000/O in/O buckets/O of/O coins/O to/O a/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION attorney/O 's/O office/O ./O 
Eight/O representatives/O with/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O Insurance/O left/O 16/O to/O 18/O orange/O paint/O buckets/O filled/O with/O quarters/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O pennies/O in/O Antonio/PERSON Gallo/PERSON 's/O office/O as/O part/O of/O a/O settlement/O that/O had/O to/O be/O paid/O by/O July/O 25/O ,/O the/O Los/LOCATION Angeles/LOCATION Times/O reported/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON 's/O client/O ,/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON ,/O had/O accused/O an/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O employee/O of/O assaulting/O him/O when/O he/O tried/O to/O buy/O insurance/O ./O 
The/O lawsuit/O was/O filed/O in/O 2012/O ./O 
Gallo/PERSON thought/O the/O coin/O payment/O was/O a/O joke/O ,/O but/O was/O told/O the/O company/O would/O not/O be/O issuing/O a/O check/O when/O he/O called/O them/O ./O 
He/O said/O Carrasco/PERSON ,/O a/O 72-year-old/O retired/O bus/O driver/O ,/O ``/O feels/O like/O he/O is/O disrepected/O ./O ''/O 
The/O coins/O are/O now/O being/O counted/O at/O a/O local/O bank/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Irate/O woman/O pays/O taxes/O with/O 30/O kilos/O in/O coins/O A/O young/O Frenchwoman/O dumped/O thousands/O of/O centime/O coins/O on/O her/O local/O tax/O office/O to/O pay/O off/O her/O bill/O and/O protest/O against/O a/O French/O system/O that/O overtaxes/O its/O people/O ./O 
She/O also/O explained/O her/O actions/O by/O saying/O ,/O ``/O I/O am/O French/O and/O I/O love/O to/O complain/O !/O ''/O 
*/O A/O Frenchwoman/O furious/O over/O what/O she/O considered/O an/O outrageous/O tax/O bill/O ,/O settled/O the/O last/O $/O 207/O of/O her/O debt/O with/O 30/O kilos/O in/O coins/O ,/O even/O breaking/O open/O her/O pink/O piggy/O bank/O at/O the/O tax/O office/O counter/O to/O come/O up/O with/O a/O few/O last/O pennies/O ./O 
``/O To/O pay/O my/O taxes/O on/O time/O ,/O I/O had/O to/O sell/O my/O car/O ,/O ''/O Audrey/PERSON D./PERSON ,/O who/O did/O n't/O give/O her/O full/O name/O ,/O told/O Sud-Ouest/ORGANIZATION newspaper/O ./O 
Her/O impromptu/O protest/O began/O when/O she/O tried/O to/O pay/O her/O $/O 1,107/O tax/O bill/O in/O cash/O to/O authorities/O in/O the/O Alpine/O town/O of/O Sallanches/LOCATION ,/O but/O was/O told/O she/O could/O only/O pay/O $/O 300/O euros/O per/O day/O in/O `/O liquide/O '/O ./O 
She/O owed/O the/O sum/O on/O the/O average/O monthly/O salary/O of/O $/O 1,400/O she/O 'd/O made/O in/O 2013/O ./O 
For/O the/O fourth/O and/O final/O payment/O ,/O the/O 28-year-old/O unemployed/O hotel/O worker/O turned/O up/O with/O $/O 207/O euros/O in/O rolls/O of/O one/O -/O ,/O two/O -/O and/O five-centime/O coins/O ,/O which/O a/O friend/O who/O works/O in/O a/O bank/O had/O helpfully/O supplied/O ./O 
She/O also/O took/O along/O her/O piggy/O bank/O ,/O which/O she/O smashed/O open/O at/O the/O counter/O to/O round/O up/O the/O sum/O ./O 
It/O took/O officials/O more/O than/O two/O hours/O to/O count/O the/O coins/O ./O 
The/O tax/O centre/O workers/O initially/O gave/O her/O a/O frosty/O reception/O but/O soon/O saw/O the/O comic/O side/O of/O things/O and/O started/O taking/O photos/O of/O the/O counting/O operation/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O not/O against/O paying/O taxes/O ./O 
But/O I/O do/O n't/O think/O we/O should/O have/O to/O pay/O so/O much/O ,/O ''/O said/O Audrey/PERSON ,/O echoing/O complaints/O from/O across/O France/LOCATION at/O the/O Socialist/O President/O François/PERSON Hollande/PERSON 's/O high-tax/O policies/O ./O 
She/O said/O she/O had/O written/O an/O open/O letter/O to/O the/O president/O to/O complain/O ``/O about/O this/O government/O which/O takes/O us/O for/O idiots/O and/O also/O simply/O because/O I/O am/O French/O and/O I/O love/O to/O complain/O !/O ''/O 
France/LOCATION has/O a/O global/O reputation/O for/O its/O high/O taxes/O ./O 
A/O recent/O study/O by/O liberal/O minded/O Brussels-based/O think/O tank/O the/O Molinari/ORGANIZATION Economic/ORGANIZATION Institute/ORGANIZATION study/O found/O that/O the/O real/O tax/O rate/O for/O an/O average/O worker/O in/O France/LOCATION in/O 2014/O stands/O at/O 57.17/O %/O ,/O well/O above/O the/O EU/LOCATION average/O of/O 45.27/O %/O ./O 
The/O French/O are/O also/O having/O to/O dedicate/O a/O larger/O portion/O of/O their/O earnings/O to/O paying/O off/O the/O taxes/O ./O 
The/O Molinari/PERSON study/O found/O that/O the/O ``/O day/O of/O fiscal/O liberation/O ''/O for/O French/O workers/O --/O the/O day/O when/O they/O have/O earned/O enough/O to/O pay/O their/O tax/O bill/O for/O the/O year/O --/O fell/O on/O July/O 28th/O ,/O two/O days/O later/O than/O the/O year/O before/O ./O 
However/O some/O doubted/O the/O veracity/O of/O that/O study/O by/O an/O organisation/O that/O has/O been/O highly/O critical/O of/O France/LOCATION 's/O taxation/O policies/O ./O 
A/O separate/O study/O by/O Eurostat/ORGANIZATION in/O June/O revealed/O that/O France/LOCATION had/O the/O third/O highest/O tax/O burden/O in/O Europe/LOCATION behind/O Denmark/LOCATION and/O Belgium/LOCATION ./O 
unique_identifier/O Jacksonville/LOCATION car/O dealer/O gives/O woman/O refund/O in/O pennies/O When/O ordered/O by/O the/O state/O to/O refund/O a/O customer/O 's/O $/O 400/O ,/O a/O Jacksonville/LOCATION Florida/LOCATION car/O dealer/O ,/O called/O Holiday/ORGANIZATION Motors/ORGANIZATION ,/O offered/O the/O refund/O in/O bags/O of/O pennies/O and/O small/O change/O ./O 
Jacksonville/LOCATION car/O dealer/O gives/O woman/O refund/O in/O pennies/O When/O ordered/O by/O the/O state/O to/O refund/O a/O customer/O 's/O $/O 400/O ,/O a/O Jacksonville/LOCATION Florida/LOCATION car/O dealer/O ,/O called/O Holiday/ORGANIZATION Motors/ORGANIZATION ,/O offered/O the/O refund/O in/O bags/O of/O pennies/O and/O small/O change/O ./O 
Car/O dealer/O pays/O customer/O $/O 400/O refund/O with/O pennies/O Ken/PERSON Amaro/PERSON ,/O First/ORGANIZATION Coast/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION Irena/PERSON Mujakovic/PERSON purchased/O this/O 2003/O Saab/ORGANIZATION from/O Holiday/ORGANIZATION Motors/ORGANIZATION in/O January/O ./O 
She/O now/O regrets/O her/O decision/O ./O 
The/O international/O college/O student/O said/O she/O did/O n't/O expect/O the/O problems/O she/O encountered/O ./O 
``/O It/O had/O transmission/O problems/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
``/O The/O message/O said/O gearbox/O malfunction/O ./O ''/O 
They/O repaired/O the/O vehicle/O and/O sold/O her/O a/O warranty/O ./O 
Then/O the/O transmission/O went/O out/O again/O ./O 
``/O First/O time/O I/O paid/O $/O 300/O ./O 
Second/O time/O ,/O they/O asked/O me/O for/O $/O 400/O ./O 
saying/O how/O the/O warranty/O does/O n't/O cover/O labor/O ,/O ''/O said/O Mujakovic/PERSON ,/O ``/O I/O though/O it/O unfair/O because/O nobody/O said/O that/O to/O me/O ./O ''/O 
She/O filed/O a/O complaint/O with/O the/O DMV/ORGANIZATION 's/O district/O office/O ./O 
The/O state/O agency/O investigated/O and/O told/O the/O dealer/O to/O give/O her/O a/O refund/O ./O 
``/O That/O 's/O actually/O money/O that/O I/O borrowed/O to/O pay/O them/O because/O I/O do/O n't/O have/O it/O ./O 
My/O tuition/O is/O very/O expensive/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
This/O week/O when/O she/O went/O to/O pick/O up/O her/O refund/O ,/O she/O was/O surprised/O ./O 
She/O said/O the/O dealer/O had/O two/O bags/O of/O coins/O and/O some/O dollar/O bills/O ./O 
``/O There/O were/O some/O one/O dollar/O bills/O ,/O but/O mostly/O pennies/O ,/O like/O two/O full/O bags/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
She/O left/O the/O bags/O at/O the/O dealership/O ./O 
She/O said/O she/O did/O n't/O know/O if/O it/O is/O the/O correct/O amount/O ,/O and/O did/O n't/O have/O time/O to/O sit/O there/O and/O count/O every/O penny/O ./O 
``/O I/O 'm/O so/O mad/O with/O them/O ,/O ''/O she/O said/O ./O 
Ed/PERSON Di/PERSON Miranda/PERSON runs/O the/O dealership/O ./O 
``/O The/O warranty/O did/O not/O cover/O labor/O and/O I/O failed/O to/O write/O that/O in/O and/O that/O was/O her/O loophole/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
When/O asked/O if/O the/O coins/O are/O retaliation/O for/O her/O complaint/O ,/O he/O said/O business/O has/O been/O slow/O ,/O that/O he/O 's/O pulling/O money/O to/O give/O her/O a/O refund/O ,/O that/O it/O is/O what/O it/O is/O ./O 
``/O I/O am/O doing/O what/O DMV/ORGANIZATION asked/O me/O to/O do/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ``/O it/O is/O legal/O tender/O ./O ''/O 
Di/PERSON Miranda/PERSON said/O only/O about/O $/O 85/O are/O in/O coins/O and/O the/O rest/O are/O in/O dollar/O bills/O ./O 
He/O said/O it/O is/O money/O he/O emptied/O from/O various/O containers/O where/O he/O keeps/O spare/O change/O ./O 
He/O said/O as/O far/O as/O he/O 's/O concerned/O he/O has/O complied/O with/O the/O Department/ORGANIZATION of/ORGANIZATION Motor/ORGANIZATION Vehicle/ORGANIZATION order/O ./O 
The/O money/O is/O waiting/O at/O the/O dealership/O for/O pick/O up/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Jason/PERSON Robert/PERSON West/PERSON Paid/O $/O 25/O Medical/O Bill/O In/O Pennies/O ,/O Got/O Fined/O $/O 140/O For/O Disorderly/O Conduct/O Jason/PERSON Robert/PERSON West/PERSON got/O a/O lesson/O in/O common/O cents/O ./O 
The/O 40-year-old/O Vernal/O ,/O Utah/LOCATION ,/O man/O paid/O a/O disputed/O $/O 25/O medical/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ./O 
But/O he/O wound/O up/O having/O to/O cough/O up/O an/O extra/O $/O 140/O for/O the/O surly/O way/O he/O did/O it/O ,/O according/O to/O reports/O ./O 
A/O judge/O ruled/O Thursday/O that/O West/LOCATION alarmed/O the/O Basin/O Clinic/O staff/O and/O patients/O enough/O to/O merit/O a/O disorderly/O conduct/O conviction/O --/O and/O the/O fine/O ./O 
According/O to/O testimony/O reported/O by/O KSL-TV/ORGANIZATION ,/O West/PERSON entered/O the/O office/O in/O May/O 2011/O and/O verbally/O abused/O the/O receptionist/O over/O the/O bill/O and/O caused/O worry/O by/O apologizing/O in/O advance/O for/O what/O he/O was/O about/O to/O do/O as/O he/O reached/O into/O a/O bag/O ./O 
He/O then/O dumped/O the/O pennies/O on/O the/O desk/O ./O 
They/O landed/O with/O a/O thud/O as/O loud/O as/O a/O gun/O shot/O ,/O scattering/O on/O the/O desk/O and/O floor/O ./O 
Perhaps/O West/O could/O have/O taken/O a/O cue/O from/O those/O who/O settle/O up/O in/O memorable/O ways/O ,/O but/O still/O manage/O to/O maintain/O their/O dignity/O ./O 
In/O July/O ,/O Thomas/PERSON Daigle/PERSON of/O Milford/LOCATION ,/O Mass./LOCATION ,/O made/O the/O last/O mortgage/O payment/O on/O his/O home/O with/O 62,000/O pennies/O and/O did/O n't/O throw/O a/O hissy/O ./O 
Earlier/O this/O month/O ,/O a/O man/O paid/O a/O $/O 137/O traffic/O ticket/O with/O 137/O dollar/O bills/O folded/O into/O origami/O pigs/O ./O 
Even/O the/O cop/O -LRB-/O pig/O ,/O get/O it/O ?/O -RRB-/O 
who/O ticketed/O him/O appreciated/O the/O effort/O ./O 
But/O West/O 's/O theatrics/O entertained/O no/O one/O the/O day/O he/O spilled/O the/O copper/O coinage/O ./O 
``/O I/O ca/O n't/O understand/O why/O a/O reasonable/O person/O would/O do/O that/O ,/O ''/O Vernal/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Justice/ORGANIZATION Court/ORGANIZATION Judge/O Ray/PERSON Richards/PERSON said/O ./O 
West/O has/O 30/O days/O to/O decide/O whether/O to/O ask/O for/O a/O new/O trial/O ,/O the/O //O Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION //ORGANIZATION wrote/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Keep/O the/O change/O when/O paying/O Millcreek/ORGANIZATION bills/O Do/O n't/O break/O out/O your/O piggy/O bank/O to/O pay/O bills/O at/O the/O Millcreek/LOCATION Township/LOCATION Municipal/LOCATION Building/LOCATION ./O 
The/O township/O supervisors/O ,/O along/O with/O the/O Millcreek/LOCATION water/O and/O sewer/O authorities/O ,/O have/O passed/O separate/O measures/O that/O limit/O the/O amount/O of/O coins/O that/O can/O be/O used/O to/O pay/O bills/O or/O fees/O ./O 
The/O action/O was/O taken/O after/O a/O Millcreek/LOCATION woman/O paid/O most/O of/O her/O estimated/O $/O 200/O sewer/O bill/O on/O March/O 20/O with/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O quarters/O ,/O said/O David/PERSON Sterrett/PERSON ,/O executive/O director/O of/O the/O Millcreek/LOCATION sewer/O and/O water/O authorities/O ./O 
The/O woman/O ,/O whom/O Sterrett/PERSON did/O not/O identify/O ,/O asked/O employees/O whether/O they/O accepted/O payment/O in/O the/O form/O of/O coins/O ./O 
When/O they/O said/O they/O did/O ,/O she/O picked/O up/O a/O shoe/O box/O full/O of/O coins/O and/O lifted/O it/O onto/O the/O counter/O in/O the/O office/O ./O 
She/O used/O a/O few/O bills/O for/O part/O of/O the/O payment/O ,/O but/O most/O of/O it/O was/O in/O coins/O ,/O Sterrett/PERSON said/O ./O 
It/O took/O about/O one/O hour/O for/O four/O employees/O to/O count/O the/O money/O ,/O sort/O it/O and/O put/O the/O coins/O into/O sleeves/O that/O could/O be/O taken/O to/O a/O bank/O ,/O Sterrett/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O They/O had/O never/O encountered/O a/O similar/O situation/O ,/O ''/O he/O said/O ./O 
The/O sewer/O authority/O passed/O a/O resolution/O that/O same/O afternoon/O ,/O during/O its/O regularly/O scheduled/O meeting/O ,/O to/O limit/O the/O number/O of/O coins/O that/O could/O be/O used/O for/O payment/O ,/O Sterrett/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O water/O authority/O adopted/O the/O same/O language/O during/O its/O meeting/O March/O 26/O ./O 
The/O two/O boards/O '/O resolutions/O state/O that/O they/O will/O not/O accept/O any/O more/O than/O $/O 10/O in/O unrolled/O coins/O as/O payment/O ,/O and/O no/O more/O than/O $/O 20/O in/O rolled/O coins/O in/O sleeves/O per/O bill/O payment/O ./O 
If/O any/O rolled/O coins/O are/O used/O ,/O the/O customer/O must/O be/O responsible/O for/O the/O rolls/O by/O placing/O his/O or/O her/O name/O and/O telephone/O number/O on/O each/O roll/O ./O 
Any/O bank/O fees/O charged/O to/O the/O authorities/O for/O using/O coins/O will/O be/O passed/O along/O to/O the/O customer/O ,/O the/O resolutions/O also/O state/O ./O 
Sterrett/PERSON said/O he/O asked/O Millcreek/LOCATION supervisors/O to/O adopt/O a/O similar/O policy/O for/O consistency/O among/O the/O township/O and/O the/O authorities/O ./O 
Supervisors/O adopted/O virtually/O the/O same/O policy/O ,/O with/O some/O additional/O language/O ,/O for/O payment/O of/O such/O fees/O as/O streetlight/O assessments/O and/O parks/O and/O recreation/O programs/O ,/O Supervisor/O Brian/PERSON McGrath/PERSON said/O ./O 
Sterrett/PERSON said/O ,/O ``/O We/O coined/O the/O -LRB-/O phrase/O -RRB-/O `/O loose/O coin/O policy/O ./O '/O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Kids/O get/O detention/O for/O penny/O prank/O Parents/O in/O New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION are/O firing/O back/O at/O school/O officials/O for/O what/O they/O say/O is/O excessive/O punishment/O for/O a/O innocent/O prank/O ./O 
More/O than/O two/O dozen/O eighth/O graders/O were/O given/O two/O days/O of/O detention/O after/O they/O paid/O for/O their/O lunches/O entirely/O in/O pennies/O ./O 
It/O happened/O in/O Whitehouse/LOCATION Station/LOCATION ./O 
Eyewitness/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION reporter/O Carolina/PERSON Lied/PERSON has/O the/O story/O ./O 
Some/O kids/O brought/O 200/O pennies/O to/O pay/O for/O their/O lunches/O Thursday/O ./O 
They/O walked/O away/O with/O detention/O slips/O instead/O of/O lunches/O ./O 
Student/O Amanda/PERSON Wolfenden/PERSON never/O thought/O a/O bunch/O of/O coins/O would/O put/O her/O and/O 24/O of/O her/O classmates/O in/O hot/O water/O ./O 
The/O Readington/ORGANIZATION Middle/ORGANIZATION School/ORGANIZATION eighth/O graders/O put/O together/O the/O penny/O prank/O in/O mere/O minutes/O ,/O and/O now/O they/O 're/O looking/O at/O two/O days/O of/O detention/O ./O 
``/O When/O the/O lunch/O ladies/O caught/O wind/O that/O we/O were/O all/O trying/O to/O pay/O in/O pennies/O ,/O they/O were/O very/O aggravated/O and/O thought/O they/O were/O disrespected/O ,/O ''/O Wolfenden/PERSON said/O ./O 
The/O students/O arranged/O the/O prank/O through/O text/O messages/O ,/O online/O blogs/O and/O the/O good/O old/O fashioned/O telephone/O line/O ./O 
But/O what/O they/O thought/O was/O a/O joke/O was/O anything/O but/O to/O the/O lunch/O staff/O who/O had/O to/O count/O the/O coins/O ./O 
``/O I/O do/O n't/O think/O it/O was/O their/O intention/O to/O do/O much/O harm/O ,/O but/O there/O 's/O consequences/O for/O the/O behavior/O when/O other/O kids/O are/O inconvenienced/O that/O way/O and/O could/O n't/O get/O through/O the/O lunch/O line/O ,/O ''/O Superintendent/O Dr./O Jorden/PERSON Schiff/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O Or/O the/O lunch/O ladies/O having/O to/O count/O thousands/O of/O pennies/O ./O ''/O 
``/O There/O 's/O no/O rule/O in/O the/O rule/O book/O that/O states/O that/O pennies/O ca/O n't/O be/O used/O to/O buy/O lunches/O ,/O ''/O eighth-grader/O Sarah/PERSON Henschel/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O We/O never/O thought/O they/O would/O do/O this/O ./O 
We/O thought/O they/O would/O give/O us/O a/O silent/O lunch/O or/O just/O yell/O at/O us/O ./O ''/O 
But/O some/O parents/O are/O sticking/O by/O their/O kids/O ,/O saying/O the/O punishment/O is/O too/O harsh/O ./O 
``/O Two/O detentions/O is/O way/O too/O much/O ,/O ''/O dad/O Tom/PERSON Henschel/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O They/O do/O n't/O get/O anything/O out/O of/O it/O ./O ''/O 
The/O kids/O say/O a/O half/O an/O hour/O is/O not/O enough/O time/O for/O 250/O students/O to/O get/O through/O the/O line/O and/O eat/O lunch/O ./O 
They/O say/O they/O just/O wanted/O to/O send/O a/O message/O ,/O one/O penny/O at/O a/O time/O ./O 
The/O superintendent/O says/O the/O district/O responded/O ,/O one/O detention/O at/O a/O time/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Kids/O Shut/O Down/O School/O Lunch/O By/O Paying/O With/O Pennies/O In/O an/O effort/O to/O draw/O attention/O to/O their/O dislike/O of/O a/O shortened/O lunch/O period/O ,/O some/O seventh/O -/O and/O eighth-grade/O New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION students/O paid/O for/O their/O lunch/O in/O pennies/O ,/O causing/O school/O officials/O to/O overreact/O ./O 
Last/O week/O in/O Readington/LOCATION Township/LOCATION ,/O New/LOCATION Jersey/LOCATION ,/O 29/O middle/O school/O students/O decided/O to/O pay/O for/O their/O $/O 2/O lunchwith/O 200/O pennies/O ,/O as/O a/O way/O to/O attract/O attention/O to/O a/O policy/O they/O disagree/O with/O a/O shortened/O 30-minute/O ``/O lunch/O hour/O ./O ''/O 
In/O what/O can/O only/O be/O described/O as/O sketchy/O details/O ,/O the/O Associated/ORGANIZATION Press/ORGANIZATION relates/O that/O it/O started/O out/O as/O a/O ``/O prank/O ,/O ''/O but/O that/O it/O turned/O into/O a/O ``/O protest/O ./O ''/O 
It/O did/O slow/O the/O lunch/O line/O to/O a/O slow/O crawl/O ./O 
School/O ``/O do-as-you-are-told-or-else/O ''/O officials/O decided/O that/O it/O was/O neither/O funny/O nor/O a/O protest/O ,/O and/O that/O the/O students/O ``/O disrespected/O ''/O lunch/O aides/O and/O therefore/O needed/O to/O be/O put/O on/O detention/O for/O two/O days/O ./O 
There/O has/O been/O more/O than/O a/O little/O fallout/O since/O the/O story/O went/O public/O ,/O with/O one/O headline/O shouting/O ``/O Free/O the/O Readington/ORGANIZATION 29/O ./O ''/O 
The/O school/O has/O since/O rescinded/O its/O orders/O for/O detention/O for/O those/O students/O whose/O parents/O don/O t/O wish/O it/O ,/O as/O many/O parents/O deemed/O the/O punishment/O too/O harsh/O ./O 
Superintendent/O Jorden/PERSON Schiff/PERSON commented/O that/O he/O was/O ``/O concerned/O ''/O about/O all/O the/O national/O media/O attention/O ,/O hence/O the/O reason/O for/O the/O reprieve/O ./O 
Well/O ,/O since/O schools/O are/O where/O lessons/O are/O learned/O ,/O let/O s/O look/O at/O just/O what/O lessons/O were/O learned/O here/O and/O who/O learned/O them/O ./O 
The/O students/O learned/O that/O using/O legitimate/O legal/O tender/O to/O pay/O for/O their/O lunches/O is/O still/O legal/O and/O legitimate/O ,/O as/O they/O were/O not/O punished/O for/O that/O ./O 
They/O also/O learned/O that/O some/O school/O officials/O are/O confused/O about/O the/O term/O ``/O disrespect/O ,/O ''/O and/O that/O said/O officials/O equate/O it/O with/O ``/O non-conformity/O ,/O ''/O terms/O the/O kids/O didn/O t/O have/O confused/O at/O all/O ,/O as/O there/O was/O no/O evidence/O that/O the/O students/O were/O disorderly/O or/O behaved/O offensively/O ,/O they/O just/O paid/O for/O their/O lunches/O in/O an/O unusual/O manner/O ./O 
They/O also/O learned/O that/O a/O little/O bit/O of/O quiet/O ,/O calm/O ,/O clever/O civil/O disobedience/O can/O go/O a/O long/O way/O ./O 
On/O the/O negative/O side/O ,/O in/O the/O aftermath/O students/O learned/O that/O school/O officials/O can/O and/O do/O backpeddle/O ,/O don/O t/O have/O to/O admit/O they/O are/O wrong/O ,/O and/O that/O they/O also/O use/O public/O relations/O and/O marketing/O techniques/O to/O cover/O their/O backsides/O ./O 
The/O school/O district/O s/O website/O has/O a/O press/O release/O where/O we/O find/O out/O that/O a/O new/O ``/O student/O activism/O club/O ''/O is/O being/O formed/O to/O give/O students/O a/O forum/O to/O express/O themselves/O something/O this/O bunch/O of/O kids/O doesn/O t/O need/O ,/O and/O probably/O something/O they/O instinctively/O know/O wo/O n't/O do/O them/O a/O bit/O of/O good/O ./O 
Students/O ,/O it/O says/O ,/O must/O learn/O to/O balance/O ``/O the/O right/O to/O protest/O with/O the/O expectation/O that/O all/O members/O of/O the/O school/O community/O honor/O the/O rights/O of/O others/O and/O treat/O each/O other/O respectfully/O ,/O ''/O evidence/O of/O a/O new/O lesson/O filled/O as/O it/O is/O with/O sophistry/O and/O double-speak/O ./O 
School/O officials/O learned/O that/O they/O haven/O t/O completely/O dulled/O the/O intellects/O of/O all/O of/O their/O students/O ,/O nor/O absorbed/O them/O into/O total/O blind/O subservience/O ,/O as/O the/O kids/O plan/O appears/O to/O have/O been/O carefully/O thought/O out/O and/O implemented/O ./O 
The/O school/O learned/O that/O even/O though/O they/O are/O an/O arm/O of/O the/O state/O ,/O they/O still/O have/O to/O be/O somewhat/O responsive/O to/O the/O local/O community/O 's/O standards/O and/O wishes/O ,/O and/O that/O publicity/O can/O be/O a/O bad/O thing/O ./O 
Parents/O should/O have/O learned/O from/O the/O kids/O this/O time/O about/O how/O to/O draw/O attention/O to/O oppressive/O policies/O while/O remaining/O within/O the/O letter/O and/O spirit/O of/O the/O law/O ./O 
And/O hopefully/O the/O parents/O learned/O that/O they/O must/O be/O much/O more/O vigilant/O when/O it/O comes/O to/O state-sponsored/O education/O ,/O various/O school/O policies/O ,/O the/O treatment/O meted/O out/O to/O children/O who/O don/O t/O conform/O ,/O and/O the/O soft-soaping/O that/O goes/O on/O after/O the/O fact/O ,/O to/O negate/O the/O damage/O already/O done/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O California/LOCATION man/O empties/O grandkids/O '/O piggy/O banks/O to/O pay/O his/O $/O 14,000/O property/O tax/O bill/O in/O CHANGE/O */O Larry/PERSON Gasper/PERSON shocked/O tellers/O at/O a/O Redding/LOCATION bank/O branch/O when/O he/O showed/O up/O with/O a/O wheelbarrow/O full/O of/O coins/O and/O dollar/O bills/O */O Said/O he/O 'd/O hit/O tough/O times/O financially/O so/O his/O friends/O and/O family/O decided/O to/O chip/O in/O to/O help/O get/O him/O out/O of/O debt/O Most/O people/O think/O spare/O change/O just/O weighs/O them/O down/O ./O 
But/O one/O California/LOCATION man/O put/O his/O to/O good/O use/O -/O saving/O up/O enough/O coins/O and/O dollar/O bills/O to/O pay/O his/O hefty/O $/O 14,000/O property/O tax/O bill/O ./O 
Larry/PERSON Gasper/PERSON shocked/O tellers/O at/O a/O Redding/LOCATION bank/O branch/O when/O he/O showed/O up/O with/O a/O wheelbarrow/O full/O of/O change/O this/O week/O ./O 
Coins/O :/O Larry/PERSON Gasper/PERSON ,/O pictured/O ,/O shocked/O tellers/O at/O a/O Redding/LOCATION bank/O branch/O when/O he/O showed/O up/O with/O not/O just/O pockets/O full/O of/O change/O -/O but/O a/O wheelbarrow/O full/O The/O grandfather/O said/O he/O 'd/O hit/O tough/O times/O financially/O so/O his/O friends/O and/O family/O decided/O to/O chip/O in/O to/O help/O get/O him/O out/O of/O debt/O ./O 
They/O gave/O Gasper/PERSON whatever/O they/O could/O afford/O ,/O in/O coins/O and/O dollar/O bills/O ./O '/O 
I/O had/O to/O borrow/O some/O money/O ,/O '/O he/O told/O ABC/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION ./O 
The/O grandfather/O said/O he/O 'd/O hit/O tough/O times/O financially/O so/O his/O friends/O and/O family/O decided/O to/O chip/O in/O to/O help/O get/O him/O out/O of/O debt/O ./O 
Tough/O times/O :/O The/O grandfather/O ,/O right/O ,/O said/O he/O 'd/O hit/O tough/O times/O financially/O so/O his/O friends/O and/O family/O decided/O to/O chip/O in/O to/O help/O get/O him/O out/O of/O debt/O He/O added/O that/O that/O he/O 'd/O skipped/O mortgage/O payments/O on/O the/O house/O he/O lives/O in/O to/O make/O up/O the/O balance/O and/O also/O raided/O piggy/O banks/O to/O fill/O the/O barrow/O with/O change/O ./O 
`/O I/O 've/O missed/O a/O few/O payments/O on/O my/O home/O to/O pay/O for/O my/O taxes/O for/O this/O piece/O of/O property/O ./O 
`/O My/O grandkids/O '/O piggy/O banks/O ,/O my/O daughters/O '/O piggy/O banks/O ,/O my/O money/O ,/O my/O change/O and/O a/O lot/O of/O people/O have/O offered/O to/O help/O a/O bit/O ./O '/O 
Heavy/O :/O Gasper/PERSON said/O he/O rolled/O all/O the/O money/O ,/O pictured/O ,/O himself/O before/O packing/O the/O $/O 14,000/O in/O the/O back/O of/O his/O car/O and/O driving/O to/O the/O bank/O Counting/O :/O A/O video/O of/O the/O transaction/O shows/O the/O teller/O 's/O jaw/O drop/O before/O she/O calls/O over/O a/O colleague/O to/O witness/O the/O bizarre/O transaction/O and/O the/O two/O begin/O to/O count/O the/O mountain/O of/O change/O Gasper/PERSON said/O he/O rolled/O all/O the/O money/O himself/O before/O packing/O the/O $/O 14,000/O in/O the/O back/O of/O his/O car/O and/O driving/O to/O the/O bank/O ./O 
A/O video/O of/O the/O transaction/O shows/O the/O teller/O 's/O jaw/O drop/O before/O she/O calls/O over/O a/O colleague/O to/O witness/O the/O bizarre/O transaction/O ./O 
The/O two/O then/O begin/O to/O count/O the/O mountain/O of/O change/O ./O 
Gasper/PERSON said/O he/O was/O relieved/O to/O no/O longer/O have/O the/O debt/O -/O or/O change/O -/O weighing/O him/O down/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Letters/O :/O Paying/O With/O Pennies/O Re/O ``/O Dear/O Starbucks/O :/O A/O Penny/O for/O Your/O Thoughts/O ''/O -LRB-/O Strategies/O ,/O Jan./O 15/O -RRB-/O ,/O which/O described/O how/O Starbucks/ORGANIZATION had/O raised/O the/O cost/O of/O a/O tall/O cup/O of/O coffee/O in/O Manhattan/LOCATION to/O $/O 2.01/O ,/O after/O tax/O :/O I/O have/O a/O totally/O different/O reaction/O to/O that/O not-so-round/O price/O ./O 
Every/O day/O I/O leave/O my/O apartment/O with/O a/O scooped-up/O handful/O of/O change/O ,/O hoping/O to/O use/O it/O when/O paying/O for/O odd-priced/O items/O ./O 
How/O satisfying/O to/O buy/O a/O bag/O of/O clementines/O for/O $/O 6.99/O and/O plunk/O down/O 99/O cents/O on/O the/O counter/O :/O it/O lightens/O my/O pocket/O and/O I/O get/O four/O almost/O weightless/O singles/O back/O from/O a/O $/O 10/O bill/O ./O 
Starbucks/ORGANIZATION should/O be/O congratulated/O for/O helping/O us/O recycle/O our/O coins/O and/O reduce/O our/O mounds/O of/O change/O ./O 
Allan/PERSON Ripp/PERSON Manhattan/LOCATION ,/O Jan./O 16/O To/O the/O Editor/O :/O If/O you/O 're/O thinking/O of/O buying/O a/O cup/O of/O coffee/O at/O a/O Manhattan/ORGANIZATION Starbucks/ORGANIZATION ,/O here/O 's/O a/O whimsical/O idea/O :/O Go/O to/O the/O bank/O and/O exchange/O $/O 2/O for/O four/O rolls/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
Pour/O them/O into/O a/O clear/O plastic/O bag/O ./O 
Then/O go/O to/O Starbucks/ORGANIZATION and/O order/O your/O tall/O cup/O of/O coffee/O ./O 
When/O the/O barista/O tells/O you/O the/O price/O ,/O hand/O her/O the/O bag/O --/O with/O an/O added/O penny/O and/O a/O smile/O ./O 
Samm/PERSON Carlton/PERSON Waquoit/PERSON ,/O Mass./LOCATION ,/O Jan./O 15/O A/O version/O of/O this/O letter/O appeared/O in/O print/O on/O January/O 22/O ,/O 2012/O ,/O on/O page/O BU2/O of/O the/O New/LOCATION York/LOCATION edition/O with/O the/O headline/O :/O Paying/O With/O Pennies/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Libertarian/O Florida/LOCATION woman/O pays/O $/O 11,000/O in/O taxes/O with/O $/O 1/O bills/O in/O protest/O of/O local/O government/O */O */O `/O Save/O your/O own/O money/O '/O :/O Julann/PERSON Roe/PERSON says/O she/O does/O n't/O like/O tax/O increases/O or/O paying/O for/O other/O people/O 's/O retirement/O */O */O */O The/O Dade/LOCATION City/LOCATION insurance/O company/O owner/O was/O paying/O taxes/O on/O her/O $/O 700,000/O 41-acre/O estate/O */O */O */O '/O I/O do/O not/O feel/O obligated/O to/O pay/O for/O your/O retirement/O '/O :/O Roe/PERSON 's/O act/O of/O protest/O came/O after/O Pasco/LOCATION County/LOCATION voted/O for/O 3/O percent/O employee/O pay/O increase/O */O Julann/PERSON Roe/PERSON says/O she/O does/O n't/O like/O tax/O increases/O or/O paying/O for/O other/O people/O 's/O retirement/O so/O she/O paid/O her/O tax/O pill/O in/O singles/O out/O of/O protest/O Julann/PERSON Roe/PERSON says/O she/O does/O n't/O like/O tax/O increases/O or/O paying/O for/O other/O people/O 's/O retirement/O so/O she/O paid/O her/O tax/O pill/O in/O singles/O out/O of/O protest/O A/O Libertarian/O and/O outspoken/O critic/O of/O her/O Florida/LOCATION county/O 's/O government/O paid/O her/O $/O 11,075.44/O tax/O bill/O in/O dollar/O bills/O ,/O plus/O 44/O pennies/O ,/O in/O protest/O of/O an/O employee/O pay/O increase/O ./O 
Julann/PERSON Roe/PERSON brought/O the/O stash/O of/O cash/O to/O the/O county/O office/O complex/O on/O Monday/O ./O 
Pasco/ORGANIZATION County/ORGANIZATION Tax/ORGANIZATION Collector/ORGANIZATION Mike/PERSON Fasano/PERSON says/O it/O took/O several/O employees/O more/O than/O an/O hour/O to/O count/O and/O verify/O it/O ./O 
`/O I/O was/O wondering/O how/O she/O got/O that/O many/O dollar/O bills/O ,/O '/O Fasano/PERSON said/O ./O 
`/O I/O doubt/O any/O bank/O would/O have/O that/O many/O singles/O on/O hand/O ./O '/O 
Fasano/PERSON did/O n't/O fault/O her/O math/O ,/O though/O ./O 
`/O It/O was/O correct/O ,/O he/O said/O ./O 
`/O Down/O to/O the/O penny/O ./O '/O 
Roe/PERSON 's/O 41-acre/O estate/O in/O Dade/LOCATION City/LOCATION is/O valued/O at/O $/O 711,447/O ./O 
It/O includes/O a/O 4,014-square-foot/O home/O with/O a/O covered/O pool/O ,/O Jacuzzi/PERSON and/O outdoor/O fireplace/O ./O 
There/O is/O also/O a/O detached/O garage/O and/O horse/O stables/O worth/O $/O 118,300/O ,/O according/O to/O theTampa/O Tribune/O ./O 
Roe/PERSON has/O attended/O multiple/O public/O hearings/O this/O year/O to/O speak/O against/O the/O budget/O ,/O which/O saw/O employee/O pay/O raises/O for/O the/O first/O time/O in/O five/O years/O ./O 
To/O the/O penny/O :/O Pasco/LOCATION County/LOCATION tax/O collector/O Mike/PERSON Fasano/PERSON says/O it/O took/O his/O office/O an/O hour/O to/O count/O out/O Roe/PERSON 's/O 11,075/O dollar/O bills/O and/O forty/O four/O pennies/O `/O I/O do/O not/O feel/O obligated/O to/O pay/O for/O any/O wage/O increase/O for/O any/O county/O employee/O ,/O '/O she/O said/O at/O a/O September/O meeting/O ./O 
Roe/PERSON ,/O whose/O family/O owns/O an/O insurance/O company/O ,/O said/O she/O should/O n't/O have/O to/O pay/O to/O take/O care/O of/O the/O employees/O after/O they/O reach/O retirement/O age/O ./O 
`/O I/O do/O not/O feel/O obligated/O to/O pay/O for/O your/O retirement/O ,/O either/O ./O 
Save/O your/O own/O money/O for/O your/O own/O retirement/O ,/O '/O she/O said/O ./O 
Dolla/O '/O bills/O ,/O ya/O 'll/O :/O '/O I/O was/O wondering/O how/O she/O got/O that/O many/O dollar/O bills/O ,/O `/O Fasano/PERSON quipped/O ./O '/O 
I/O doubt/O any/O bank/O would/O have/O that/O many/O singles/O on/O hand/O '/O '/O I/O do/O not/O feel/O obligated/O to/O pay/O for/O any/O wage/O increase/O for/O any/O county/O employee/O '/O :/O Roe/PERSON was/O protesting/O a/O recent/O 3/O percent/O pay/O increase/O for/O all/O employees/O in/O Pasco/LOCATION County/LOCATION ,/O including/O those/O at/O this/O government/O office/O ./O 
It/O was/O their/O first/O in/O over/O 5/O years/O She/O also/O opposed/O a/O since-defeated/O gas/O tax/O increase/O ./O 
`/O The/O public/O is/O not/O your/O slush/O fund/O ,/O '/O she/O continued/O ./O 
`/O Stay/O within/O your/O means/O because/O we/O do/O n't/O want/O anymore/O taxes/O ./O '/O 
Fasano/PERSON said/O Roe/PERSON 's/O visit/O to/O the/O tax/O collector/O was/O anything/O but/O typical/O but/O was/O quick/O to/O point/O out/O that/O ,/O thanks/O to/O tax/O dollars/O ,/O his/O office/O was/O there/O to/O serve/O her/O ./O 
`/O We/O 're/O here/O to/O serve/O anyone/O who/O comes/O into/O our/O office/O ,/O '/O he/O said/O ./O 
`/O We/O 've/O had/O people/O pay/O in/O cash/O before/O ,/O but/O to/O have/O a/O property/O tax/O bill/O over/O $/O 11,000/O is/O not/O average/O ./O '/O 
unique_identifier/O Insurance/O company/O pays/O 21,000/O dollar/O settlement/O to/O senior/O citizen/O in/O coins/O Insurance/O companies/O always/O rank/O pretty/O highly/O on/O the/O list/O of/O businesses/O that/O people/O genuinely/O do/O n't/O like/O to/O deal/O with/O ,/O and/O it/O seems/O that/O one/O firm/O in/O California/LOCATION has/O no/O problem/O with/O adding/O to/O that/O reputation/O ./O 
In/O what/O can/O only/O be/O described/O in/O the/O internet/O parlance/O of/O our/O times/O as/O a/O ``/O dick/O move/O ,/O bro/O ''/O ,/O Adriana/ORGANIZATION s/ORGANIZATION Insurance/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION ,/ORGANIZATION Inc./ORGANIZATION from/O California/LOCATION recently/O payed/O a/O settlement/O of/O $/O 21,000/O -LRB-/O just/O over/O 15,700/O -RRB-/O to/O a/O 73-year-old/O man/O in/O coins/O ./O 
The/O settlement/O had/O to/O do/O with/O a/O suit/O that/O Andres/PERSON Carrasco/PERSON had/O taken/O against/O the/O company/O after/O he/O claimed/O that/O he/O was/O physically/O assaulted/O by/O one/O of/O their/O employees/O ,/O but/O things/O during/O the/O proceedings/O obviously/O got/O a/O little/O bit/O petty/O ,/O as/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O decided/O that/O this/O was/O the/O best/O way/O to/O hand/O over/O what/O they/O owed/O ./O 
The/O senior/O citizen/O and/O the/O company/O came/O to/O an/O agreement/O in/O June/O ,/O but/O he/O was/O left/O shocked/O when/O eight/O employees/O from/O the/O firm/O showed/O up/O to/O his/O attorney/O 's/O office/O in/O a/O van/O with/O five/O gallon/O containers/O full/O of/O coins/O in/O hand/O and/O left/O them/O at/O reception/O ./O 
Having/O just/O undergone/O a/O hernia/O operation/O ,/O there/O was/O no/O question/O that/O he/O would/O be/O able/O to/O lift/O even/O one/O of/O the/O buckets/O ,/O and/O his/O lawyer/O said/O that/O ``/O there/O are/O 16/O buckets/O of/O quarters/O ,/O nickels/O ,/O dimes/O and/O pennies/O ./O 
It/O s/O going/O to/O take/O us/O at/O least/O ,/O conservatively/O ,/O one/O week/O to/O count/O that/O whole/O amount/O of/O money/O ./O ''/O 
They/O 're/O obviously/O hoping/O that/O there/O really/O is/O no/O such/O thing/O as/O bad/O publicity/O ,/O but/O Carrasco/PERSON said/O in/O a/O statement/O that/O ``/O I/O am/O disappointed/O by/O the/O way/O Adriana/PERSON 's/O treats/O their/O customers/O and/O the/O elderly/O ./O 
We/O might/O be/O poor/O ,/O but/O we/O are/O people/O too/O ''/O ,/O which/O is/O probably/O not/O a/O tagline/O they/O want/O on/O their/O advertising/O ./O 
Unsurprisingly/O ,/O they/O have/O declined/O to/O comment/O to/O the/O media/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Watch/O as/O this/O Australian/O man/O pays/O a/O parking/O fine/O in/O pennies/O Parking/O fines/O are/O a/O bit/O like/O speeding/O tickets/O ,/O in/O the/O sense/O that/O if/O you/O do/O n't/O speed/O ,/O you/O wo/O n't/O get/O a/O ticket/O ,/O if/O you/O do/O n't/O park/O illegally/O ,/O you/O wo/O n't/O get/O a/O ticket/O ./O 
However/O we/O 've/O all/O been/O given/O a/O ticket/O at/O one/O point/O or/O another/O that/O we/O felt/O was/O completely/O unjustified/O ,/O maybe/O 1/O or/O 2/O minutes/O late/O ,/O I/O mean/O we/O 're/O all/O trying/O to/O get/O on/O in/O the/O world/O right/O ,/O what/O 's/O the/O harm/O in/O getting/O back/O to/O your/O car/O a/little/O bit/O //O late/O ?/O 
And/O normally/O it/O 's/O these/O tickets/O that/O really/O get/O you/O riled/O up/O ./O 
Well/O this/O Australian/O man/O from/O Adelaide/LOCATION was/O so/O disgruntled/O by/O his/O $/O 60/O parking/O fine/O that/O he/O took/O out/O the/O necessary/O money/O to/O pay/O the/O fine/O ,/O then/O went/O straight/O to/O the/O bank/O to/O have/O it/O changed/O into/O the/O smallest/O increments/O possible/O ,/O 5/O cent/O coins/O ,/O 1,200/O of/O them/O ./O 
Now/O as/O much/O as/O I/O can/O empathise/O with/O a/O furious/O motorist/O and/O his/O hilarious/O way/O of/O dealing/O with/O a/O fine/O ,/O I/O ca/O n't/O help/O but/O feel/O that/O maybe/O he/O should/O n't/O have/O been/O so/O aggressive/O with/O the/O lady/O behind/O the/O desk/O at/O the/O council/O ,/O as/O she/O was/O just/O doing/O her/O job/O ,/O perhaps/O the/O best/O way/O would/O have/O been/O to/O politely/O hand/O over/O the/O bag/O rather/O than/O push/O the/O pennies/O onto/O her/O desk/O ,/O what/O do/O you/O guys/O think/O ?/O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O arrested/O ,/O cuffed/O after/O using/O $/O 2/O bills/O A/O man/O trying/O to/O pay/O a/O fee/O using/O $/O 2/O bills/O was/O arrested/O ,/O handcuffed/O and/O taken/O to/O jail/O after/O clerks/O at/O a/O Best/O Buy/O store/O questioned/O the/O currency/O 's/O legitimacy/O and/O called/O police/O ./O 
According/O to/O an/O account/O in/O the/O Baltimore/ORGANIZATION Sun/ORGANIZATION ,/O 57-year-old/O Mike/PERSON Bolesta/PERSON was/O shocked/O to/O find/O himself/O taken/O to/O the/O Baltimore/LOCATION County/LOCATION lockup/O in/O Cockeysville/LOCATION ,/O Md./LOCATION ,/O where/O he/O was/O handcuffed/O to/O a/O pole/O for/O three/O hours/O while/O the/O U.S./ORGANIZATION Secret/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION was/O called/O to/O weigh/O in/O on/O the/O case/O ./O 
Bolesta/PERSON told/O the/O Sun/O :/O ``/O I/O am/O 6/O feet/O 5/O inches/O tall/O ,/O and/O I/O felt/O like/O 8/O inches/O high/O ./O 
To/O be/O handcuffed/O ,/O to/O have/O all/O those/O people/O looking/O on/O ,/O to/O be/O cuffed/O to/O a/O pole/O --/O and/O to/O know/O you/O have/O n't/O done/O anything/O wrong/O ./O 
And/O me/O ,/O with/O a/O brother/O ,/O Joe/PERSON ,/O who/O spent/O 33/O years/O on/O the/O city/O police/O force/O ./O 
It/O was/O humiliating/O ./O ''/O 
After/O Best/O Buy/O personnel/O reportedly/O told/O Bolesta/PERSON he/O would/O not/O be/O charged/O for/O the/O installation/O of/O a/O stereo/O in/O his/O son/O 's/O car/O ,/O he/O received/O a/O call/O from/O the/O store/O saying/O it/O was/O in/O fact/O charging/O him/O the/O fee/O ./O 
As/O a/O means/O of/O protest/O ,/O Bolesta/PERSON decided/O to/O pay/O the/O $/O 114/O bill/O using/O 57/O crisp/O ,/O new/O $/O 2/O bills/O ./O 
As/O the/O owner/O of/O Capital/ORGANIZATION City/ORGANIZATION Student/ORGANIZATION Tours/ORGANIZATION ,/O the/O Baltimore/LOCATION resident/O has/O a/O hearty/O supply/O of/O the/O uncommon/O currency/O ./O 
He/O often/O gives/O the/O bills/O to/O students/O who/O take/O his/O tours/O for/O meal/O money/O ./O 
``/O The/O kids/O do/O n't/O see/O that/O many/O $/O 2/O bills/O ,/O so/O they/O think/O this/O is/O the/O greatest/O thing/O in/O the/O world/O ,/O ''/O Bolesta/PERSON says/O ./O 
``/O They/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O spend/O `/O em/O ./O 
They/O want/O to/O save/O `/O em/O ./O 
I/O 've/O been/O doing/O this/O since/O I/O started/O the/O company/O ./O 
So/O I/O 'm/O thinking/O ,/O `/O I/O 'll/O stage/O my/O little/O comic/O protest/O ./O 
I/O 'll/O pay/O the/O $/O 114/O with/O $/O 2/O bills/O ./O 
'''/O Bolesta/PERSON explained/O what/O happened/O when/O he/O presented/O the/O bills/O to/O the/O cashier/O at/O Best/ORGANIZATION Buy/O Feb./O 20/O ./O 
``/O She/O looked/O at/O the/O $/O 2/O bills/O and/O told/O me/O ,/O `/O I/O do/O n't/O have/O to/O take/O these/O if/O I/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O ./O '/O 
I/O said/O ,/O `/O If/O you/O do/O n't/O ,/O I/O 'm/O leaving/O ./O 
I/O 've/O tried/O to/O pay/O my/O bill/O twice/O ./O 
You/O do/O n't/O want/O these/O bills/O ,/O you/O can/O sue/O me/O ./O '/O 
So/O she/O took/O the/O money/O --/O like/O she/O 's/O doing/O me/O a/O favor/O ./O ''/O 
Bolesta/PERSON says/O the/O cashier/O marked/O each/O bill/O with/O a/O pen/O ./O 
Other/O store/O employees/O began/O to/O gather/O ,/O a/O few/O of/O them/O asking/O ,/O ``/O Are/O these/O real/O ?/O ''/O 
``/O Of/O course/O they/O are/O ,/O ''/O Bolesta/PERSON said/O ./O 
``/O They/O 're/O legal/O tender/O ./O ''/O 
According/O to/O the/O Sun/O report/O ,/O the/O police/O arrest/O report/O noted/O one/O employee/O noticed/O some/O smearing/O of/O ink/O on/O the/O bills/O ./O 
That/O 's/O when/O the/O cops/O were/O called/O ./O 
One/O officer/O reportedly/O noticed/O the/O bills/O ran/O in/O sequential/O order/O ./O 
Said/PERSON Bolesta/PERSON :/O ``/O I/O told/O them/O ,/O `/O I/O 'm/O a/O tour/O operator/O ./O 
I/O 've/O got/O thousands/O of/O these/O bills/O ./O 
I/O get/O them/O from/O my/O bank/O ./O 
You/O got/O a/O problem/O ,/O call/O the/O bank/O ./O '/O 
I/O 'm/O sitting/O there/O in/O a/O chair/O ./O 
The/O store/O 's/O full/O of/O people/O watching/O this/O ./O 
All/O of/O a/O sudden/O ,/O he/O 's/O standing/O me/O up/O and/O handcuffing/O me/O behind/O my/O back/O ,/O telling/O me/O ,/O `/O We/O have/O to/O do/O this/O until/O we/O get/O it/O straightened/O out/O ./O '/O 
``/O Meanwhile/O ,/O everybody/O 's/O looking/O at/O me/O ./O 
I/O 've/O lived/O here/O 18/O years/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O hoping/O my/O kids/O do/O n't/O walk/O in/O and/O see/O this/O ./O 
And/O I/O 'm/O saying/O ,/O `/O I/O ca/O n't/O believe/O you/O 're/O doing/O this/O ./O 
I/O 'm/O paying/O with/O legal/O American/O money/O ./O 
'''/O Bolesta/O was/O taken/O to/O the/O lockup/O ,/O where/O he/O sat/O handcuffed/O to/O a/O pole/O and/O in/O leg/O irons/O while/O the/O Secret/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION was/O called/O ./O 
``/O At/O this/O point/O ,/O ''/O he/O says/O ,/O ``/O I/O 'm/O a/O mass/O murderer/O ./O ''/O 
Secret/ORGANIZATION Service/ORGANIZATION agent/O Leigh/PERSON Turner/PERSON eventually/O arrived/O and/O declared/O the/O bills/O legitimate/O ,/O adding/O ,/O according/O to/O the/O police/O report/O ,/O ``/O Sometimes/O ink/O on/O money/O can/O smear/O ./O ''/O 
Commenting/O on/O the/O incident/O ,/O Baltimore/LOCATION County/LOCATION police/O spokesman/O Bill/PERSON Toohey/PERSON told/O the/O Sun/O :/O ``/O It/O 's/O a/O sign/O that/O we/O 're/O all/O a/O little/O nervous/O in/O the/O post-9/O //O 11/O world/O ./O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O attempts/O to/O buy/O car/O with/O $/O 16,000/O in/O coins/O ,/O gets/O bored/O and/O uses/O card/O instead/O A/O Shandong/LOCATION man/O tried/O to/O buy/O a/O car/O with/O five/O tons/O of/O coins/O ,/O but/O got/O frustrated/O at/O how/O long/O it/O took/O staff/O to/O count/O the/O money/O and/O paid/O with/O his/O card/O instead/O ,/O //O Global/ORGANIZATION Times/ORGANIZATION //O reports/O ./O 
The/O dealership/O in/O Liaocheng/LOCATION told/O reporters/O that/O the/O man/O wanted/O to/O buy/O a/O 100,000/O yuan/O -LRB-/O $/O 16,000/O -RRB-/O car/O with/O begs/O of/O one/O yuan/O coins/O he/O 'd/O brought/O along/O with/O him/O ./O 
``/O He/O supposedly/O had/O five/O tons/O in/O there/O ,/O ''/O one/O employee/O said/O ,/O ``/O but/O only/O gave/O us/O 50,000/O yuan/O because/O he/O was/O going/O to/O buy/O more/O cars/O at/O other/O dealers/O ./O ''/O 
Every/O available/O employee/O was/O roped/O in/O to/O help/O count/O the/O coins/O ,/O but/O the/O buyer/O started/O getting/O impatient/O ./O 
Eventually/O he/O paid/O the/O balance/O on/O his/O bank/O card/O ./O 
The/O dealership/O was/O still/O left/O with/O a/O couple/O tons/O in/O coins/O ,/O which/O they/O have/O to/O deposit/O at/O the/O bank/O in/O 2,000/O yuan/O increments/O every/O day/O ./O 
In/O October/O ,/O two/O Chinese/O tourists/O were/O arrested/O in/O Paris/LOCATION after/O they/O tried/O to/O settle/O their/O bill/O with/O a/O portion/O of/O 3,500/O one/O euro/O coins/O they/O had/O stashed/O in/O their/O hotel/O room/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O Attempts/O to/O Pay/O $/O 6,400/O Tax/O with/O Kiddie/ORGANIZATION Pool/ORGANIZATION Full/ORGANIZATION of/O Pennies/O God/O bless/O our/O friends/O to/O the/O North/O ./O 
If/O you/O ca/O n't/O have/O a/O sense/O of/O humor/O about/O this/O stuff/O ,/O you/O 're/O likely/O to/O do/O something/O stupid/O like/O ,/O say/O ,/O join/O the/O Tea/ORGANIZATION Party/ORGANIZATION :/O A/O Quebec/LOCATION man/O ,/O fed/O up/O with/O his/O skyrocketing/O property/O taxes/O ,/O carted/O more/O than/O 200,000/O pennies/O down/O to/O City/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION to/O pay/O his/O bill/O ./O 
But/O he/O was/O denied/O ,/O and/O asked/O to/O simply/O cut/O a/O cheque/O ./O 
Normand/PERSON Czepial/PERSON of/O Ripon/LOCATION ,/O Que/O ./O 
--/O less/O than/O an/O hour/O 's/O drive/O northeast/O of/O Gatineau/LOCATION --/O arrived/O at/O City/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION on/O Wednesday/O with/O a/O children/O 's/O pool/O filled/O with/O 213,625/O pennies/O ./O 
Now/O we/O 're/O wondering/O -/O did/O Normand/PERSON roll/O into/O his/O bank/O that/O morning/O to/O make/O the/O withdrawal/O and/O demand/O the/O smallest/O denomination/O possible/O or/O had/O he/O been/O saving/O all/O the/O copper/O coins/O his/O entire/O life/O for/O this/O exact/O moment/O ?/O 
Whichever/O it/O is/O ,/O we/O applaud/O this/O particular/O brand/O of/O //O awesome/O //O ./O 
The/O only/O beef/O we/O have/O this/O move/O is/O that/O he/O used/O the/O kiddie/O pool/O to/O schelp/O the/O pennies/O down/O to/O City/LOCATION Hall/LOCATION ./O 
What/O the/O hell/O ,/O man/O ?/O 
Depriving/O your/O kids/O of/O fun/O in/O the/O //O middle/O of/O summer/O ?/O 
//O Sure/O you/O 're/O a/O little/O bit/O of/O smartass/O -LRB-/O which/O we/O like/O -RRB-/O but/O it/O appears/O also/O a/O bit/O of/O dick/O in/O the/O Dad/O Department/O ./O 
Not/O cool/O ./O 
Czepial/PERSON 's/O property/O tax/O bill/O reportedly/O rose/O by/O nearly/O $/O 4,000/O dollars/O last/O year/O to/O $/O 6,400/O ./O 
Czepial/O tried/O to/O pay/O with/O pennies/O to/O protest/O the/O hike/O ./O 
Ripon/LOCATION Mayor/O Luc/PERSON Desjardins/PERSON was/O surprised/O to/O see/O the/O stunt/O ,/O but/O had/O to/O tell/O Czepial/O to/O find/O another/O way/O to/O pay/O his/O bill/O ./O 
Under/O the/O Currency/O Act/O ,/O nobody/O is/O obliged/O to/O accept/O more/O than/O 25/O pennies/O as/O payment/O for/O any/O product/O or/O service/O ./O 
Normand/PERSON Czepial/PERSON ,/O unfortunately/O ,/O was/O 213,600/O over/O the/O limit/O ./O 
Even/O the/O Toronto/LOCATION Sun/LOCATION is/O throwing/O around/O the/O jokes/O !/O 
Everyone/O that/O is/O threatening/O to/O move/O to/O Canada/LOCATION given/O a/O particular/O election/O of/O -LSB-/O insert/O hated/O political/O figure/O -RSB-/O should/O take/O note/O that/O it/O sounds/O kinda/O fun/O up/O there/O !/O 
Man/O tries/O to/O pay/O tax/O with/O 200,000/O pennies/O -LSB-/O Toronto/ORGANIZATION Sun/ORGANIZATION via/O TaxProf/O -RSB-/O unique_identifier/O Man/O Attempts/O To/O Pay/O Hospital/O Bill/O With/O Pennies/O A/O few/O dollar/O bills/O would/O have/O kept/O one/O Utah/LOCATION man/O out/O of/O trouble/O with/O the/O law.Jason/O West/O reportedly/O walked/O into/O a/O Salt/LOCATION Lake/LOCATION City/LOCATION clinic/O on/O May/O 27th/O to/O dispute/O a/O 25-dollar/O bill/O ./O 
The/O 38-year-old/O allegedly/O asked/O if/O they/O accepted/O cash/O ,/O and/O then/O proceeded/O to/O poor/O 25-hundred/O pennies/O on/O the/O counter/O ./O 
Authorities/O tell/O the/O ``/O Desert/O News/O ''/O that/O West/LOCATION 's/O behavior/O served/O ``/O no/O legitimate/O purpose/O ,/O ''/O and/O only/O upset/O the/O staff/O at/O the/O clinic/O ./O 
West/O has/O since/O been/O cited/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O and/O ordered/O to/O pay/O 140-dollar/O fine/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O charged/O for/O paying/O with/O pennies/O A/O US/LOCATION man/O paid/O for/O a/O disputed/O medical/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O A/O US/LOCATION man/O has/O been/O cited/O on/O a/O charge/O of/O disorderly/O conduct/O after/O paying/O for/O a/O disputed/O medical/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ./O 
The/O Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION of/O Salt/LOCATION Lake/LOCATION City/LOCATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION ,/O reports/O that/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON went/O to/O Basin/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION in/O Vernal/LOCATION on/O May/O 27/O prepared/O to/O dispute/O an/O outstanding/O 25/O US/LOCATION dollar/O bill/O ./O 
Assistant/O Vernal/O police/O chief/O Keith/PERSON Campbell/PERSON said/O that/O after/O asking/O staff/O members/O whether/O they/O accepted/O cash/O ,/O West/O dumped/O 2,500/O pennies/O on/O the/O counter/O and/O demanded/O that/O staff/O count/O them/O ./O 
Mr/O Campbell/PERSON said/O the/O incident/O upset/O staff/O because/O pennies/O were/O strewn/O about/O the/O counter/O and/O floor/O ,/O and/O West/LOCATION 's/O action/O served/O ``/O no/O legitimate/O purpose/O ''/O ./O 
Police/O later/O issued/O the/O 38-year-old/O West/O a/O citation/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O ./O 
That/O carries/O a/O fine/O of/O as/O much/O as/O 140/O US/O dollars/O ./O 
Or/O 14,000/O pennies/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O Cited/O By/O Police/O After/O He/O Pays/O $/O 25/O Medical/O Bill/O In/O Pennies/O Money/O is/O money/O ,/O right/O ?/O 
Even/O if/O it/O 's/O 2,500/O pennies/O dumped/O on/O a/O counter/O to/O pay/O a/O $/O 25/O bill/O ?/O 
Yeah/O ,/O but/O that/O does/O n't/O mean/O people/O get/O mad/O when/O you/O chuck/O a/O bunch/O of/O change/O at/O them/O ./O 
A/O man/O in/O Vernal/LOCATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION did/O n't/O think/O he/O owed/O Basin/O Clinic/O $/O 25/O ,/O and/O they/O said/O he/O did/O ./O 
So/O he/O did/O the/O mature/O thing/O and/O unloaded/O 2,500/O pennies/O on/O the/O counter/O 's/O clinic/O ,/O demanding/O they/O count/O it/O ./O 
That/O upset/O the/O staff/O ,/O who/O thought/O his/O bratty/O behavior/O served/O ``/O no/O legitimate/O purpose/O ,/O ''/O so/O the/O cops/O were/O called/O as/O the/O man/O left/O the/O office/O ./O 
The/O police/O cited/O him/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O ,/O an/O infraction/O ,/O which/O carries/O a/O potential/O fine/O of/O $/O 140/O ./O 
Who/O wants/O to/O bet/O he/O 's/O showing/O up/O to/O his/O court/O hearing/O with/O 140,000/O shiny/O copper/O pennies/O ?/O 
Police/O cite/O Vernal/ORGANIZATION man/O accused/O of/O paying/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O unique_identifier/O Man/O Cited/O for/O Disorderly/O Conduct/O for/O Paying/O $/O 25/O Medical/O Bill/O with/O 2,500/O Pennies/O I/O do/O n't/O get/O this/O one/O ./O 
Are/O n't/O pennies/O legal/O tender/O US/LOCATION currency/O ?/O 
Are/O n't/O 100/O pennies/O worth/O just/O the/O same/O as/O a/O $/O 1/O bill/O ?/O 
Is/O $/O 25/O not/O the/O same/O as/O 2,500/O pennies/O ?/O 
So/O why/O ,/O then/O ,/O was/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON ,/O a/O 38-year-old/O man/O from/O Vernal/LOCATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION ,/O charged/O with/O disorderly/O conduct/O for/O paying/O a/O $/O 25/O medical/O bill/O with/O pennies/O ?/O 
Well/O ,/O it/O 's/O a/O bit/O more/O complicated/O than/O that/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O //O Christian/O Science/O Monitor/O //O and/O the/O //O Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION ,/O //O West/LOCATION went/O to/O the/O Basin/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION in/O Vernal/LOCATION to/O dispute/O a/O $/O 25/O doctor/O 's/O bill/O ./O 
Anticipating/O losing/O his/O argument/O ,/O the/O peeved/O patient/O brought/O along/O 2,500/O pennies/O ./O 
When/O he/O did/O n't/O get/O his/O way/O ,/O West/O dumped/O the/O pennies/O --/O 14/O pounds/O -LRB-/O 6.35/O kg/O ./O -RRB-/O 
worth/O --/O on/O the/O counter/O and/O demanded/O that/O clinic/O employees/O count/O it/O ./O 
``/O The/O pennies/O were/O strewn/O about/O the/O counter/O and/O the/O floor/O ,/O ''/O the/O assistant/O police/O chief/O told/O the/O //O News/O ./O 
//O Therein/O lies/O the/O root/O of/O the/O disorderly/O conduct/O charge/O ,/O as/O ridiculous/O as/O it/O may/O seem/O ./O 
However/O ,/O private/O businesses/O do/O not/O have/O to/O accept/O coins/O if/O they/O do/O n't/O want/O to/O ./O 
That/O 's/O why/O businesses/O can/O legally/O refuse/O bills/O over/O $/O 20/O if/O they/O so/O desire/O ./O 
If/O that/O seems/O unfair/O ,/O perhaps/O that/O 's/O because/O it/O is/O ./O 
As/O for/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON ,/O he/O could/O face/O a/O fine/O of/O up/O to/O $/O 140/O ./O 
Hopefully/O he/O 'll/O pay/O in/O pennies/O !/O 
West/O is/O n't/O the/O first/O person/O to/O try/O to/O pay/O a/O bill/O with/O thousands/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
Just/O this/O March/O ,/O Thierry/PERSON Cahez/PERSON paid/O a/O $/O 6,500/O credit/O card/O bill/O with/O a/O mind-numbing/O 650,000/O pennies/O ./O 
That/O 's/O 3,640/O pounds/O -LRB-/O 1,651/O kg/O ./O -RRB-/O 
--/O nearly/O two/O tons/O --/O worth/O ./O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O cited/O for/O paying/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O Settling/O a/O disputed/O bill/O with/O pennies/O or/O other/O small/O change/O is/O occasionally/O used/O as/O a/O form/O of/O protest/O ./O 
But/O is/O it/O smart/O or/O effective/O ?/O 
What/O 's/O one/O way/O to/O get/O your/O jollies/O while/O paying/O a/O disputed/O bill/O ?/O 
Satisfy/O the/O debt/O with/O pennies/O --/O lots/O of/O them/O ./O 
Or/O maybe/O not/O ./O 
A/O Vernal/O ,/O Utah/LOCATION ,/O man/O faces/O a/O charge/O of/O disorderly/O conduct/O for/O paying/O a/O $/O 25/O medical/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ,/O according/O to/O police/O ./O 
``/O After/O asking/O if/O they/O accepted/O cash/O ,/O -LRB-/O Jason/PERSON -RRB-/O West/O dumped/O 2,500/O pennies/O onto/O the/O counter/O and/O demanded/O that/O they/O count/O it/O ,/O ''/O Vernal/O assistant/O police/O chief/O Keith/PERSON Campbell/PERSON told/O the/O Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION ./O 
``/O The/O pennies/O were/O strewn/O about/O the/O counter/O and/O the/O floor/O ./O ''/O 
West/O left/O after/O staffers/O at/O the/O health/O clinic/O threatened/O to/O call/O the/O police/O ,/O who/O later/O wrote/O a/O citation/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O ,/O police/O said/O ./O 
The/O maximum/O fine/O is/O $/O 140/O ./O 
Others/O have/O employed/O similar/O tactics/O without/O legal/O consequence/O ./O 
It/O appears/O the/O citation/O in/O the/O Utah/LOCATION case/O was/O due/O to/O the/O mess/O that/O was/O made/O --/O not/O the/O payment/O of/O the/O bill/O with/O very/O small/O change/O ./O 
However/O ,/O merchants/O and/O others/O can/O decide/O NOT/O to/O accept/O pennies/O as/O payment/O ,/O Snopes.com/LOCATION wrote/O while/O addressing/O this/O false/O claim/O :/O ``/O U.S./LOCATION law/O specifies/O that/O merchants/O do/O not/O have/O to/O accept/O more/O than/O 100/O pennies/O as/O payment/O ./O ''/O 
Pennies/O are/O legal/O tender/O ,/O yes/O ./O 
But/O no/O law/O requires/O merchants/O to/O accept/O them/O ./O 
``/O Businesses/O are/O free/O to/O accept/O or/O reject/O pennies/O as/O they/O see/O fit/O ,/O ''/O Snopes/PERSON wrote/O ./O 
Do/O you/O think/O paying/O with/O pennies/O or/O other/O small/O coins/O is/O an/O effective/O means/O of/O protest/O ?/O 
Or/O are/O you/O just/O creating/O lots/O of/O additional/O work/O for/O bureaucrats/O and/O clerks/O who/O have/O to/O process/O the/O payment/O ?/O 
-LRB-/O Suggestion/O :/O If/O you/O 're/O compelled/O to/O do/O this/O ,/O at/O least/O count/O and/O roll/O the/O coins/O first/O ./O -RRB-/O 
unique_identifier/O Man/O Faces/O 14,000/O Cent/O Fine/O For/O Paying/O Bill/O With/O Pennies/O ./O 
In/O Vernal/LOCATION ,/O Utah/LOCATION 38/O year/O old/O Jason/PERSON West/PERSON has/O been/O cited/O for/O disorderly/O conduct/O after/O paying/O a/O disputed/O medical/O bill/O with/O 2,500/O pennies/O ./O 
According/O to/O the/O Deseret/ORGANIZATION News/ORGANIZATION of/LOCATION Salt/LOCATION Lake/LOCATION City/LOCATION ,/O West/LOCATION disputed/O a/O $/O 25.00/O medical/O bill/O at/O Basin/ORGANIZATION Medical/ORGANIZATION Clinic/ORGANIZATION recently/O and/O after/O asking/O if/O they/O accepted/O cash/O ,/O dumped/O 2,500/O pennies/O on/O the/O counter/O and/O demanded/O the/O staff/O count/O them/O ./O 
Assistant/O Vernal/O Police/O Chief/O Keith/PERSON Campbell/PERSON said/O that/O the/O act/O served/O ``/O no/O legitimate/O purpose/O ''/O and/O upset/O the/O staff/O because/O pennies/O were/O strewn/O all/O over/O the/O counter/O and/O floor/O ./O 
Police/O later/O charged/O West/O with/O a/O misdemeanor/O disorderly/O conduct/O charge/O and/O he/O now/O faces/O a/O fine/O of/O $/O 140.00/O ./O 
He/O might/O want/O to/O start/O saving/O his/O pennies/O so/O he/O can/O pay/O his/O fine/O ./O 
Speaking/O of/O saving/O pennies/O .../O Recently/O ,/O I/O went/O into/O a/O convenience/O store/O here/O in/O town/O and/O when/O the/O clerk/O went/O to/O give/O me/O my/O change/O back/O she/O short/O changed/O me/O .04/O saying/O they/O were/O out/O of/O pennies/O ./O 
Now/O ,/O .04/O is/O no/O big/O deal/O but/O it/O did/O kind/O of/O irk/O me/O the/O store/O would/O short/O change/O customers/O like/O that/O ./O 
Seems/O to/O me/O ,/O it/O 's/O the/O store/O 's/O fault/O they/O ran/O out/O of/O pennies/O ,/O not/O mine/O ./O 
If/O anyone/O should/O take/O the/O loss/O it/O should/O be/O them/O ./O 
So/O are/O they/O going/O to/O do/O the/O same/O thing/O if/O they/O run/O out/O of/O nickels/O ?/O 
dimes/O ?/O 
ones/O ??/O 
Just/O does/O n't/O seem/O right/O to/O me/O ./O 
As/O Bill/PERSON O'Reilly/PERSON would/O say/O .../O ``/O what/O say/O you/O ?/O ''/O 
unique_identifier/O 
